<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Game of Thrones on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/game-of-thrones/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Game of Thrones on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/game-of-thrones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones - Horror of the Ironborn</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-of-thrones---horror-of-the-ironborn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-of-thrones---horror-of-the-ironborn/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will go to conquer the seas. Control your ship by moving it across the water in any direction. If you meet an enemy ship on the way, boldly attack it by selecting the desired function from the menu of the bottom panel. Your task is to completely destroy the opponent&amp;rsquo;s ships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones 3 - Martells</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-of-thrones-3---martells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-of-thrones-3---martells/</guid>
      <description>So, you are waiting for another adventure based on your favorite series. This time at the disposal of users will be a warship with dragons on sails. In the process of passing, you will have to establish the dominance of your clan over the sea. The first stage will be educational. True, all the tips are given in English, but it&amp;rsquo;s easy to figure it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones 4 - House Bet</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-of-thrones-4---house-bet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-of-thrones-4---house-bet/</guid>
      <description>The game will appeal to fans of knights and tournaments. At the very beginning, you can choose the mode: for one or for two users. In the process of passing, you will have to take part in the tournament of equestrian knights. The most interesting thing is that both riders and horses suffer in fights, although they have to fight with blunt weapons. There is a lot of blood in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones Tournament in Harrenhal</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-of-thrones-tournament-in-harrenhal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-of-thrones-tournament-in-harrenhal/</guid>
      <description>If you love virtual battles, it&amp;rsquo;s time to launch this wonderful game. Here you will find an exciting process, during which you will need to fight with rivals, strong and not very strong. Try to cope with all the opponents that come against you. It will be really interesting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill Monsters</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kill-monsters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kill-monsters/</guid>
      <description>After launching this game, an exciting minecraft-style adventure awaits you. Control a brave warrior and fight zombies coming from all sides. Just hit them with your sword while avoiding enemy hits. The game will continue until you lose all health points.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
