<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Battles on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/battles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Battles on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/battles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apache City War</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/apache-city-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/apache-city-war/</guid>
      <description>The game is already the seventh sequel to the excellent strategic shooter of the Second World War. In each mission, you must destroy all tanks, vehicles and other enemy objects as part of the land army. You have to control only one tank, the rest of the unit&amp;rsquo;s vehicles fight along with you automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combat Pixel Arena 3D Fury Man</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/combat-pixel-arena-3d-fury-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/combat-pixel-arena-3d-fury-man/</guid>
      <description>battle arena</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Craft Sharp Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/craft-sharp-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/craft-sharp-shooter/</guid>
      <description>At your disposal is a naval base with ships, submarines and aircraft. The enemy is advancing, so stay on the defensive by controlling the cannons with the up and down arrow keys. Upgrade, grow your fleet and send it on a campaign to destroy the enemy port.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminal</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/criminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/criminal/</guid>
      <description>The Battle game offers you to command a squad of elite fighters. The success of a military operation rarely depends on the skill and professionalism of a single soldier. In emergency and not very situations, the commander plays the most important role. Become them for the duration of each game operation, assembling your own squad and brilliantly completing assigned tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fighting Planes</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fighting-planes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fighting-planes/</guid>
      <description>You are entrusted with a special task - to control a powerful military fighter, to destroy enemy military equipment. You have to complete a series of missions, each of which will be an order of magnitude more difficult than the previous one. Help is nowhere to be found. You have to rely only on yourself and your aircraft. Shoot accurately, don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid of sharp turns and try not to get hit by enemy bullets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heroes Of Myths Warriors Of Gods</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/heroes-of-myths-warriors-of-gods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/heroes-of-myths-warriors-of-gods/</guid>
      <description>In ancient times, the most valuable resource of human tribes was the territory, it was for it that the most bloody battles between tribes took place. And even when the winner was firmly established on any land, there was always a risk that someone would try to capture it. Your kingdom is already quite wealthy and ready to fend for itself. But you have to defend yourself from many invaders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hostage Rescue 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hostage-rescue-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hostage-rescue-2/</guid>
      <description>World War II is now on your computer screen. Get ready to take part in the most real military operations. And, of course, win. But you have to make an effort. Become smarter, bolder, more enterprising and far-sighted than all your enemies. And also learn to shoot accurately and think through a plan of action a few steps ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman vs Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-vs-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-vs-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Try to survive in a world overrun by zombies. You have to protect the base from the invasion of hordes of vile monsters. The walking dead do not know fatigue and fear, so the battle will be long. The game provides an opportunity to improve the skills of your fighters, heal comrades-in-arms, use many other useful features, which makes the battles incredibly interesting and varied.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
