<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Card on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/card/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Card on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/card/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Mat Solitaire online for free</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-mat-solitaire-online-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-mat-solitaire-online-for-free/</guid>
      <description>Online game Mat Solitaire play for free invites everyone. It has fairly simple rules. The screen displays seven stacks of a different number of cards, the top of which are open. A little higher is the remaining deck and empty spaces for placing the collected combinations. There will be four of them in total, according to the number of suits. First you need to find and move aces there, and then continue the sequence: twos, threes, and so on, until the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solitaire Strike game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/solitaire-strike-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/solitaire-strike-game/</guid>
      <description>Card fun awaits you in this exciting game. The screen will display a curly layout in which all cards except the extreme ones are closed. The goal is to remove cards of the same rank. This must be done until the screen is completely clear. After that, a new level will open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worms game - more or less</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/worms-game---more-or-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/worms-game---more-or-less/</guid>
      <description>This fun game invites gamers to use their intuition. A card will be displayed on the screen, and you need to guess which one will follow it - older or younger. The correct answer will bring bonus points, and if you make a mistake, you will lose a life. If you make a mistake three times in a row, you lose, and the game ends immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
