<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robots for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/robots-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Robots for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/robots-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Battle Robot Samurai Age</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/battle-robot-samurai-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/battle-robot-samurai-age/</guid>
      <description>During the game for two Blast it 7 you have to go to the distant future and become a participant in exciting competitions. Choose one of the robots and go to the playing field, where you have to measure your strength against 3 competitors. Try to destroy them with the help of bombs that you will lay out in a fantastic labyrinth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cowboy VS Robots</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cowboy-vs-robots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cowboy-vs-robots/</guid>
      <description>Robots for 2 game is an exciting hybrid of shooter and rpg, designed for two players. Together with your partner, you will control a pair of robots, whose task is to complete all levels, helping each other to shoot enemies. The principle of the game resembles the famous Fireboy and Watergirl series, but there are differences. Your characters can shoot at the enemy, the enemy also fires back. There are not so many logical difficulties in the game - more action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robbie</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/robbie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/robbie/</guid>
      <description>In the future, when the usual fights in the ring will be boring for everyone, and technological progress will make almost any dream come true, people will create a new kind of entertainment for themselves. These are robot battles where you can put your bot in the arena and he will have to fight with many other enemies to win the tournament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Robo Fighter 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-robo-fighter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-robo-fighter-2/</guid>
      <description>Games for two Shooting robots offer you to control two bots of various modifications, which must complete an urgent task. They need to find the hatch through which the exit from the galactic station is carried out. The game is designed for 2 people, so you can invite a friend. Get ready for some serious challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
