<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For children 4 years old on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-4-years-old/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For children 4 years old on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-4-years-old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Shooter Raccoon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-shooter-raccoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-shooter-raccoon/</guid>
      <description>Here is a good example of what shooting games for 4 year olds can be like. Here, no one kills anyone, and the main character is SpongeBob, adored by kids. Now he dressed up as a pirate and trains in shooting. He needs to shoot down targets with a pistol. In this case, all shells ricochet, and the game resembles billiards. With its help, you can develop a child&amp;rsquo;s eye and spatial thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circus Hidden Objects</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/circus-hidden-objects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/circus-hidden-objects/</guid>
      <description>A very fun game. In it you have to entertain the audience in the circus, controlling the clown. He stands on the ball and stay on it is already a difficult task. You also need to catch objects falling from the ceiling. The more the clown moves, the more the ball swings under him. For the allotted time you need to Crazy Games a certain number of points to go to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cube City Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cube-city-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cube-city-racing/</guid>
      <description>Passing the game Racing for children 4 years old without the help of adults is unlikely to be possible. In any case, for the launch and the first race, the participation of dad or older brother is simply necessary. In principle, everything is standard: the races take place on the highway. Along the way, you need to collect prizes: coins and nitrous oxide. The former will help you upgrade between races.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/desert-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/desert-racing/</guid>
      <description>This car game for 4 year olds will undoubtedly be interesting for kids, but difficult to complete. Therefore, the participation of adults is required. But first, let&amp;rsquo;s get to the point. The toy is invited to take part in the adventures of a cute red car. Her entire journey is divided into several stages. On each of them you need to complete some tasks. Unlike any other car game, they involve driving lifts and other mechanisms, all while the car is in motion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dora Spot The Difference</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dora-spot-the-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dora-spot-the-difference/</guid>
      <description>Looking for simple games for kids 4 years old? You found what you were looking for! This toy will perfectly entertain the child, and most importantly, will accelerate his development. All that is needed is to fill the contours of the picture with suitable fragments. The result is a beautiful drawing with one or another animal. The only drawback is a small number of blanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Cafe</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-cafe/</guid>
      <description>And again with us the beloved and unique Sponge Bob! Today he works in a bakery and oversees the pizza making process. The process is mechanized, but the machines are old and often turned off. Bob needs to run between them and turn them on in time, and throw the damaged products from the conveyor into the trash. If he can&amp;rsquo;t do his job, he&amp;rsquo;ll be fired!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Candy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweet-candy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweet-candy/</guid>
      <description>During the game for children 4 years old Balls, your child will be able to feel like a bully. After all, only hooligans burst flying balls from spitting tubes. In more detail, everything looks like this: the main character must spit pieces of newspaper through a tube folded from paper and knock down as many balls as possible. The goal is to Crazy Games the maximum number of points.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
