<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hairstyles on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/hairstyles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hairstyles on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/hairstyles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ariana Grande Inspired Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ariana-grande-inspired-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ariana-grande-inspired-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>Princess Anna always tries to take care of herself in order to look attractive. This time you will be in the role of the girl&amp;rsquo;s personal beautician. At your disposal will be a variety of useful tools that should be used for their intended purpose in order to restore the attractiveness of the skin of the face and hair of the heroine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Elsa School Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-elsa-school-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-elsa-school-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you have to work on the appearance of a girl who is going to school. First, take care of her hair, wash her hair and style it. Next comes the turn of makeup and dress. The game features a wide range of all wardrobe items. The girl will be beautiful!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbara Fashion Hair Saloon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/barbara-fashion-hair-saloon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/barbara-fashion-hair-saloon/</guid>
      <description>The Barbie Hairstyle game invites you to dress up as a pretty girl. The process consists of several stages. First you need to find in the room all the items that you need for work. Next, you can begin to form a stylish hairstyle. Finally, the final stage is makeup and outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleopatra Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cleopatra-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cleopatra-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>During this game you will turn into a real hairdresser. The task is to make the girl a great hairstyle. Arm yourself with scissors, cut off all unnecessary, curl curls or, on the contrary, straighten your hair. After the hairstyle is ready, decide on its color. And don&amp;rsquo;t forget the makeup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denim Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/denim-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/denim-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game for girls And hairstyles and dress up you will meet a charming Japanese girl. The task is to work on the image of this cute girl. Choose a hairstyle, various elements of the outfit, as well as accessories, without which it is difficult to imagine a Japanese woman. For example, she will definitely need a fan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabulous Back 2 School Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fabulous-back-2-school-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fabulous-back-2-school-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you will need to work on the gorgeous hair of cutie Apple White. Follow the detailed hints of the game, use all the necessary tools that will allow you to end up with a great hairstyle. First you will need to wash your hair and treat it with special products. And then you can lay them down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Sister Christmas Hairstyle Design</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/frozen-sister-christmas-hairstyle-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/frozen-sister-christmas-hairstyle-design/</guid>
      <description>An interesting Hairstyles game invites you to try on the role of a hairdresser. In front of you is a girl whose hair just needs to be worked on. First, wash them and dry them, and then you can start shaping your hair. You can straighten your hair or curl curls - for this, the screen has all the necessary tools. If you want, you can change the hair color by choosing any paint color you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Girl Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/galaxy-girl-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/galaxy-girl-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>The Crazy Hairstyle game invites you to the hairdresser. In the waiting room, customers are already waiting who want to fix their hair. Choose who you want to work with: a guy or a girl. Then start the exciting process of shaping the hairstyle. At your disposal are all the necessary hairdressing tools that will help you get an attractive result. Style your hair the way you want, after which you can change its color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gothic Princess Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gothic-princess-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gothic-princess-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to work on the image of an informal girl. She likes emo style, and you need to build on it. First, process the hair of the heroine of the game and make a hairstyle that will look spectacular. Next, you will need to apply makeup and choose the cutest emo outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gradvation Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gradvation-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gradvation-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>Addictive game Do Hairstyles will instantly turn you into a hairdresser. A girl came to you wanting to fix her hair. Your task is to work on them, getting a nice hairstyle as a result. The game for girls consists of several stages. First, use hairdressing tools to shape the style. At your disposal are scissors, curlers, ironing. After the hairstyle is ready, proceed to dyeing the hair. There are many different shades here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessies Stylish Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessies-stylish-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessies-stylish-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>The game Hairstyles for evaluation will instantly turn you into a hairdresser. In it, you can do a variety of styling, using the available tools for this. To get started, choose the hairstyle you want to work on. Next, it remains to wash your hair, dry it and begin to shape the styling. Follow the hints of the game to get the planned result in the end. And when you finish with one hairstyle, you can always move on to another option to try your hand there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kendall Hair Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kendall-hair-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kendall-hair-salon/</guid>
      <description>Not a single star can be imagined in a disheveled form. In this game, you will turn into charming Rihanna&amp;rsquo;s hairdresser. So far, her hair does not look too attractive, so you need to quickly fix the situation. A variety of hairdressing tools will help you with this. Use them as you please.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kristoffs Hair Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kristoffs-hair-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kristoffs-hair-salon/</guid>
      <description>While playing Do Your Own Hair you will meet a cute girl. She decided to change the image, and you have to help in this charmer. To get started, work on her hair, using the proposed tools for this: hair dryer, scissors, curlers, iron. It is also worth adding cute hair accessories and changing the color. But the game for girls is not limited to hairstyles alone, in it you can also take care of the makeup of the heroine and choose her outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ladybug Halloween Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ladybug-halloween-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ladybug-halloween-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>Become a hairdresser for a while and make the heroine of the game an excellent fashionable hairstyle. First you need to wash her hair and apply useful products to them. Next, shape the styling and choose a pretty color of curls that is perfect for a fashionista. The final stage is applying makeup and choosing a stylish outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Late To School Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/late-to-school-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/late-to-school-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>Help cute Rapunzel to clean up. Your task is to make her a great hairdo, as well as choose an outfit and jewelry. First, take care of the heroine&amp;rsquo;s hair. Wash and dry them, then use hairdressing tools to get the cutest result possible. You can even cut the princess&amp;rsquo;s hair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latina Princess Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/latina-princess-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/latina-princess-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>Any student of the school of monsters wants to look attractive, and Bonita Femur was no exception. Work on her unusual multi-colored hair to eventually shape them into a cute hairstyle. Arm yourself with scissors, curlers and other useful tools - with their help, styling will be unique. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget your make-up and attire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Princess Hair Treatment</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-princess-hair-treatment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-princess-hair-treatment/</guid>
      <description>During this game you will meet cute little girl Daisy. She wants to get a new hairstyle, but you have to help her. The game consists of several stages, and at each of them it is proposed to perform a number of tasks. You need to deal with them in a limited time. Hurry up if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to upset the girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Princess Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-princess-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-princess-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>Go to the underwater depths to work on the appearance of the little mermaid. Choose her hairstyle, outfit, tail. Decide also on the decorations that are presented on the screen in large quantities. Try to achieve the most harmonious combination of elements of appearance, which will allow the mermaid to look perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minion Wedding Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/minion-wedding-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/minion-wedding-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you will see a minion girl with something strange going on on her head. Your task is to make her an attractive hairstyle. Various hairdressing tools are at your disposal. Take any and apply as directed. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget about a beautiful shade of hair dye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moody Ally Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/moody-ally-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/moody-ally-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you have to turn into a children&amp;rsquo;s hairdresser. Your client will be a little girl who, like adult women, wants to look attractive. But working with children is more problematic, the baby may burst into tears, and at such moments you will have to be distracted and console her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noelles Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/noelles-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/noelles-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you have to work in a hairdresser. Clients come here all the time to change their hairstyle. Your task is to give the girls exactly what they want. Try to act as quickly as possible, otherwise clients may get angry because of the long wait and leave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polynesian Princess Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/polynesian-princess-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/polynesian-princess-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will find yourself in a hairdressing salon, where all the necessary tools have already been prepared. Your client will be a charming girl with long hair who wants to get an original hairstyle. Follow the hints of the game and use all the indicated items to achieve the perfect result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony Girl Hair Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-girl-hair-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-girl-hair-salon/</guid>
      <description>A sweet girl decided to radically change her hairstyle. Choose one of the options that you like the most and get to work. The task is to finally get the intended result, that is, the hairstyle that is shown in the sample picture. You&amp;rsquo;ve got all the tools you need!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Bridal Hairstyle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-bridal-hairstyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-bridal-hairstyle/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game, you are invited to create unique hairstyles using several components for this. You can also change the color of your hair, picking up even the most unexpected shades. There are three sliders for this. By moving them around, you can find cool color options! Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to dress up the girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess New Look Haircut</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-new-look-haircut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-new-look-haircut/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game, you will find yourself in a hairdressing salon, where a cute girl is already waiting for you. She decided to change her hairstyle, and you need to help in this matter, turning into a real hair master. Choose one of the hairstyle options, then apply the necessary tools to achieve the shown result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Braided Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/school-braided-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/school-braided-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>During the game Hairstyles for medium hair you will turn into a hairdresser who has to help the girl. Your task is to work on the image of the heroine of the game. To begin with, use various products to wash your hair and restore its beauty. Do your hair and choose a cute outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selena Gomez Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/selena-gomez-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/selena-gomez-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>The heroine of the game flies to rest, and she needs a new hairstyle, as well as high-quality makeup. Help the charming girl deal with these questions. Choose the right hairstyle and apply your favorite decorative cosmetics. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to try on the outfit and accessories to complete your stylish look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Braided Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/summer-braided-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/summer-braided-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>While playing Braid Hairstyles you will learn how to make attractive braids. Choose one of the available options and get started. Just follow the prompts that appear on the screen in order to achieve the desired result in the end. For hairdressing activities you will have all the necessary tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Barbara Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-barbara-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-barbara-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will find yourself in a hairdressing salon, where a pretty girl is already waiting. You need to work on her hair using a variety of tools that are in the salon. Shape a fashionable hairstyle, change the heroine&amp;rsquo;s hair color if necessary to get the most attractive result.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
