<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>zombies vs cars on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/zombies-vs-cars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in zombies vs cars on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/zombies-vs-cars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game crush zombies 1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-crush-zombies-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-crush-zombies-1/</guid>
      <description>A terrible thing is happening on the streets of the city: they are filled with the living dead, who have risen from their graves. During the game Crush zombies 1 you need to try to escape by leaving the dangerous place in a car. Crush zombies that get in your way to get money and use them to buy improvements for your car. At the beginning of the game, you will have very little fuel, but after the upgrade, the volume of the tank will increase, and you will be able to drive longer distances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie crush game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-crush-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-crush-game/</guid>
      <description>After starting the Zombie Crusher game, you will find yourself in a city filled with the risen dead. Your task is to move around the track and push, push, push them all. At the same time, you must not collide with fences, since this will lead to an accident and the complete destruction of your car, and you can only survive here by cars. Obstacles try to go around or jump over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Road</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-road/</guid>
      <description>The gameplay of Crush Zombies, designed for boys, will definitely keep you hooked for a long time. With its help, you will be transported to a world where the uprising of the dead took place, and now they are eager to feast on the freshest brains. At your disposal is a modest machine, on which you need to try to break through the hordes of zombies to a safe place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
