<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Racing 2 on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/racing-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Racing 2 on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/racing-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3D Night City 2 Player Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/3d-night-city-2-player-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/3d-night-city-2-player-racing/</guid>
      <description>An exciting game Racing for two 2 will take you to a distant planet, where you will participate in competitions. But first, do not forget to choose a character whose car you have to drive. Local cars do not look quite familiar, they are more like spaceships that fly through the air. This makes the process of racing on 2 even more fun. Game ups and downs include a large number of levels, and on each of them you have a specific goal: you need to overtake rivals in order to reach the finish line first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATV Traffic</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/atv-traffic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/atv-traffic/</guid>
      <description>In Super Racing 2, you will get a car that looks quite simple, but you can ride it perfectly. In addition, you will have the opportunity to choose one of 2 modes: you can play alone or in the company of other players. If you stop at the second option, then on the track you will see many other cars that will also move around the game space. They are controlled by real players who decide to start the game process at the same time as you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Demolition Derby V1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-demolition-derby-v1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-demolition-derby-v1/</guid>
      <description>In the incredible game Car Racing 2 you are invited to drive a car in a special tube. It is necessary to drive the specified distance in order to proceed to the next stage. But you need to act very carefully so as not to damage the car when meeting obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impossible Stunts Cars 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/impossible-stunts-cars-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/impossible-stunts-cars-2019/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game, you will be asked to choose a car and a place for the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sportscar Grand Prix</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sportscar-grand-prix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sportscar-grand-prix/</guid>
      <description>In this wonderful game you can feel like a real racer in a fast car.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
