<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fighting 3d on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/fighting-3d/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fighting 3d on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/fighting-3d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Boxing Fighter Shadow Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/boxing-fighter-shadow-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/boxing-fighter-shadow-battle/</guid>
      <description>The action of this game takes place in a saloon, somewhere in the wild Wild West. You have to put on a cowboy costume and take part in a fight. The game is three-dimensional and very cool. In it, you can grab tables, chairs, smash them on the head of an opponent, or throw one cowboy into a crowd of others. But be careful not to let the opponents close to you from the rear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Night Zombie Street Fight</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/final-night-zombie-street-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/final-night-zombie-street-fight/</guid>
      <description>The tense silence is slightly shocking and alarming. But it is worth finding the first weapon, as the undead will show themselves not from the best side. Move around the old house and search the rooms for items that will help you destroy the monsters and save your life at any cost. It would be nice to be the first to find a pistol or shotgun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samurai Fighter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/samurai-fighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/samurai-fighter/</guid>
      <description>Today you have to test your strength in capoeira - Brazilian martial art, vaguely reminiscent of dance. The confrontation involves two players, endowed with various options for strikes and acrobatic elements. Each lunge in the arena corresponds to a certain key combination, which are described in detail in the instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sumo Party</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sumo-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sumo-party/</guid>
      <description>You will control a small robot traveling through different worlds. It is also possible to fight other players in a destructible arena. In case of defeat, you can always repair your character by collecting his spare parts from the location. At the end of each level, you will be upgraded by the main character and more powerful weapons for him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
