<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Various on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/various/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Various on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/various/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ant maniac game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ant-maniac-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ant-maniac-game/</guid>
      <description>If you like not quite ordinary characters, then you will like this game. The main character here is an armored ant with a large-caliber gun on his back. The whole process of passing is a crazy race, during which you need to collect coins, avoid collisions with obstacles and bugs. The latter can be shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Fruit Ninja 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-fruit-ninja-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-fruit-ninja-3d/</guid>
      <description>This funny toy is probably familiar to owners of tablets and smartphones. But now it is also available for PC gamers. The essence is simple: it is necessary to dissect the thrown fruits into pieces. The smaller, the more points the user gets. Management - by means of a mouse. You can use the points you earn to buy upgrades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mad Max 3D game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mad-max-3d-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mad-max-3d-game/</guid>
      <description>This game really evokes the last part of the Mad Max movie: combat vehicles, post-industrial landscape and so on. There is no plot, as such. The point is that teams must capture the enemy&amp;rsquo;s flag and protect their own. Multiplayer mode, online. In between battles, you can upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanks vs robots game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-vs-robots-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-vs-robots-game/</guid>
      <description>This game will appeal to gamers - lovers of all sorts of robots and fancy tanks. View from above. By controlling the combat vehicle using the keyboard and mouse, you need to destroy enemy robots and not be exposed to their shots. At certain points of the location, you can pick up bonuses. In the place of the blown up enemies there is money - collect them for an upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
