<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shooting games for boys on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting-games-for-boys/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shooting games for boys on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting-games-for-boys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bullet League</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bullet-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bullet-league/</guid>
      <description>In this game, instead of running around and shooting with different characters, you have to play the role of a catapultist. That is, you will fire at the enemy castle from an old gun. As it should be in games of this kind, in order to hit the target, you must choose the trajectory of the projectile and the force of the shot. In the process of passing there will be an opportunity to improve your weapon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Pixel Apocalypse</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-pixel-apocalypse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-pixel-apocalypse/</guid>
      <description>Do you think that there are no shooting games for boys aged 5? And here you are wrong! And the proof of this is easy to get: just start the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Hand Cowboy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/one-hand-cowboy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/one-hand-cowboy/</guid>
      <description>Your character is an alien sheriff, very similar to Western characters. The action takes place on his home planet. You need to kill monsters, and at the same time stay alive. With the collected money, you will be able to purchase more powerful weapons over time. If you are wondering why all the cheese is boron, see the introduction and read the text under the pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Gun: Apocalypse</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-gun-apocalypse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-gun-apocalypse/</guid>
      <description>At the very beginning of this shooting game for boys aged 9, you can choose one of three characters. Each of them has its own specialization (medic, commando, attack aircraft) and, accordingly, characteristics and weapons. Next, you can choose the mode of passage: campaign or quick match. But the essence will still be the same: kill everyone, collect cartridges and first-aid kits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shooters io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/shooters-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/shooters-io/</guid>
      <description>Shooting games for 6 years old for boys are suitable and suitable for girls too. There is a good opportunity to verify this by running one of them right now. At first, gamers will find an interesting and colorful comic-intro. After that, no less exciting and interesting process of passing will begin. You will get acquainted with the character control buttons as you progress. The game provides for boys shooters, treasure hunts and the need to overcome obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway Clash Remastered</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/subway-clash-remastered/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/subway-clash-remastered/</guid>
      <description>The developer of this shooting game for boys aged 11 is Armor Games, which in itself is a guarantee of good graphics and an interesting plot. First, choose your fighter. They differ in class, capabilities and weapons. The action takes place on an unknown space station. You will have to not only fight, but also think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wasteland Shooters</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wasteland-shooters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wasteland-shooters/</guid>
      <description>According to the terms of Blood Shooter for Boys, you have to fight against an army of zombies. Choose from three characters the one you like best, arm him and go to destroy the monsters. Pass one level after another, not forgetting to collect drop-down bonuses - they will help to strengthen the attacking or defensive abilities of your hero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-challenge/</guid>
      <description>After launching a shooting game for boys for 8 years old, a gamer may be intimidated by a rather large menu and the need to make several choices before starting the gameplay. However, in the shooting game genre, games for boys can&amp;rsquo;t be too difficult to scare away the clientele. So, it won&amp;rsquo;t be hard to figure it out. As for the passage, you will find many levels and funny characters.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
