<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Racing for survival on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/racing-for-survival/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Racing for survival on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/racing-for-survival/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Death Race</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/death-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/death-race/</guid>
      <description>Oh horror, the zombie apocalypse has happened, and the living dead are now everywhere! During the survival race game for boys, you need to get to the helicopter to get out of the danger zone as quickly as possible. To do this, you have a small car, which you, however, can improve by earning money for the distances covered. The further you drive, the more chances for survival, and finances too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deathcario</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/deathcario/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/deathcario/</guid>
      <description>The process of playing for two Survival races is very, very exciting. It is based on a rather original idea. You will drive an unusual vehicle that leaves a colored trail behind it. Three more participants will compete with you on the playing field. You need to manage your transport in such a way to Crazy Games more points. But at the same time, it is strictly forbidden to collide with the traces of other participants and with fences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race Down</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/race-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/race-down/</guid>
      <description>The most incredible adventure begins! You find yourself in a city, on the streets of which you can do a lot. The Survival Race game provides you with a powerful car equipped with a couple of “trunks”. With their help, you can destroy other cars and other objects. You will be given missions to complete while moving through the city streets. For example, the first task will be related to the destruction of taxi cars.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
