<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About animals on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/about-animals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About animals on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/about-animals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Animal rescue 3d</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/animal-rescue-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/animal-rescue-3d/</guid>
      <description>While playing Animal Pro 3D, the famous kitty Angela decided to start her own tailoring shop for designer clothes. She has rented a small space and invites you to become her partner. Together with the heroine of the game, you will have to clean all the rooms, put the scattered objects in their places, and then sew a costume for the first client, which, of course, will be Angela&amp;rsquo;s friend, the hero of many computer games - the famous Tom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Beast Beauty</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-beast-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-beast-beauty/</guid>
      <description>While playing Wash the Animals, you meet Princess Cinderella&amp;rsquo;s favorite dog. Together with her mistress, she goes to the royal ball. The little girl turned to your beauty salon for girls and their pets with a request to prepare her for the celebration. Only you can handle such a responsible task, so get to work as soon as possible. To begin with, help your ward take a bath, then put her hair in order, do her hair and, finally, pick up original accessories that will emphasize the beauty and style of the dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become A Puppy Groomer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/become-a-puppy-groomer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/become-a-puppy-groomer/</guid>
      <description>While playing Animal Hair Salon you become a leading specialist of one of the beauty salons of a magical land. Thanks to your diligence and talent, you managed to gain popularity among the inhabitants of a fairy-tale city, and they invited you to take part in a hairdressing competition. The heroes of the game for girls Hair Salon for Animals - the cat Sophia and the dog Peg, have decided to become your helpers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Pony Care</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-pony-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-pony-care/</guid>
      <description>The famous Rainbow Dash turned to your magical beauty salon. She dreams of changing her image a bit, both as a pony and as a girl. Try to come up with an original style for the beauty that will emphasize her beauty and personality, turning her into the most beautiful pony in Ponyville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horse Care And Riding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/horse-care-and-riding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/horse-care-and-riding/</guid>
      <description>Animals game introduces you to the beautiful Cinderella and her pet - a wonderful dog. Together they went on a journey on a pumpkin carriage through the fairy kingdom. At one of the turns, the carriage fell apart, and the friends fell into a huge muddy puddle. During this animal game you have to help a girl and her shaggy friend clean up. First, take care of the puppy, remove all dirt and twigs from the dog, provide first aid and tidy up the coat, then help the unfortunate princess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory Mach Jungle Animals</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/memory-mach-jungle-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/memory-mach-jungle-animals/</guid>
      <description>During the Forest Animals game, the inhabitants of the forest decided to play hide and seek and invite you to take part in this exciting game. In a limited time, try to find all the animals hiding on the playing field. Hover over the found animal with the mouse, and it will look out of its hiding place. You can play this game on your own or with your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pet Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pet-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pet-run/</guid>
      <description>Favorite reindeer of Princess Elsa - the famous heroine of the cartoon &amp;ldquo;Frozen&amp;rdquo;, fell through the ice. The brave girl managed to pull it out, but the unfortunate animal is in a terrible state. Carefully inspect the deer, determine what medical procedures he needs to do and start treatment as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tiger-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tiger-simulator/</guid>
      <description>The heroes of the game Animal Simulators 3D - funny puppies, organized a special squad, which is designed to help people and animals in trouble. In addition to 7 wonderful dogs, the Puppy Patrol includes a ten-year-old boy, Ryder. It is he who is the leader of the tailed team from this simulation game. Its members invite you to join them and feel like a real animal, able to cope with any task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild Forest Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wild-forest-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wild-forest-hunter/</guid>
      <description>During the Animal Hunt game you have to become a watchman who guards a small plot of land from wild animals. Try to destroy all the animals trying to get through the fence and save the entire crop. At each stage of this exciting game, you will be asked to use several types of weapons that will help protect the garden from intruders. Gold coins are awarded for each destroyed animal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
