<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>princesses on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/princesses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in princesses on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/princesses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bffs Day Of The Dead</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bffs-day-of-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bffs-day-of-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>The process of the unusual Disney Princess Zombies game is dedicated to the cutie Snow White. Here she looks not quite in the usual way, because the cartoon beauty has turned into a zombie. But the girl has not lost her charm, and now you have to dress her up in fashionable things, as well as add accessories and a hairstyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ella Makeup Removal</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ella-makeup-removal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ella-makeup-removal/</guid>
      <description>Cute princess Elsa suffers from facial skin imperfections. You need to help the girl, using a variety of useful cosmetics. Then you can safely proceed to applying makeup, choosing your favorite shades of lipstick, eye shadow, blush. Finally, the final step will be the choice of hairstyle and outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellie Cinema Flirting</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-cinema-flirting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-cinema-flirting/</guid>
      <description>Princess Rapunzel hides her relationship with the handsome prince, but sometimes she really wants to be alone with her lover. Help the couple in love not to catch the eye of the nasty stepmother queen, warning the heroes of the game in time about her approach. Rapunzel will be grateful for your help and will definitely invite you to her wedding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Pony Princess Twilight Sparkle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-pony-princess-twilight-sparkle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-pony-princess-twilight-sparkle/</guid>
      <description>The process of playing Princess Pony Twilight Sparkle will perfectly train your memory and attention. Cute horses have decided to have a holiday, and you need to help them decorate the place for the celebration. To do this, remember how the elements are arranged here, and then also arrange them in a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Princess Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-princess-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-princess-makeover/</guid>
      <description>During the game Princess Juliet, you will be asked to take care of horses along with a cute girl. She is going to take part in the races, so rather choose one of the heroine&amp;rsquo;s favorites and go to the stable. You need to help Princess Juliet prepare the horse for the competition, based on the advice of her mistress. First, feed the horse and water it, then you have to clean the animal and carry out other necessary procedures with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Queen Sauna Flirting</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-sauna-flirting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-sauna-flirting/</guid>
      <description>The game My Kingdom for the princess will tell you a story about the king&amp;rsquo;s daughter and her uncle, to whom the heroine came to visit. They were sitting quietly at the table, when suddenly a terrible hurricane arose. He woke up the dragon, which sleeps and sees how to feast on people. To all the misfortunes, lightning hit the father of the heroine, and now she urgently needs to get home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jenner Sisters Matching Monster High</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jenner-sisters-matching-monster-high/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jenner-sisters-matching-monster-high/</guid>
      <description>A big ball is coming up at the school of monsters. And you during the game for girls Princess Monster High have to create chic images for the main characters. Before you are Draculaura, Frankie Stein and Claudine Wolfe. It is their appearance that needs to be addressed. Choose any heroine to dress her up and choose her hairstyle. In the wardrobes you will find luxurious puffy dresses, stylish shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Princess Wardrobe</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/modern-princess-wardrobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/modern-princess-wardrobe/</guid>
      <description>While playing Create Your Own Princess, you will be able to design your own royal person. To do this, you have a huge number of elements at your disposal. To get started, take care of the face, pick up the skin color, shape and shade of the eyes, lips. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget about the hairstyle, choosing the styling and length of the hair. Jewelry for hairstyles will also not be superfluous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Make Donut</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-make-donut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-make-donut/</guid>
      <description>The game Princess invites you to take care of the appearance of a cute girl. The process consists of four stages. First you need to treat the skin with special means to eliminate all defects. Next comes the make-up time: you are invited to use a variety of decorative cosmetics, choosing the most suitable shades. The third stage is related to the creation of hairstyles for the princess. Finally, the final step will be the choice of dress, shoes and accessories for the beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Moanas Ship</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-moanas-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-moanas-ship/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to prepare a girl for an important holiday event. To do this, you need to do makeup and choose a chic dress in which she will outshine everyone. Of course, you need to choose the right shoes and jewelry for the dress, thanks to which the image will become even brighter and more spectacular.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princesses on Ibiza</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-on-ibiza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-on-ibiza/</guid>
      <description>After launching the game Disney Princess Dress Up All Princesses, you will see cartoon girls familiar to everyone. One of the princesses is getting married, and three more beauties have become her girlfriends. You are invited to come up with outfits for all the heroines, using a variety of game features for this. Click on any heroine and choose her dress, hairstyle, shoes and accessories. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to take care of the background, against which the Disney princesses will look the most attractive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Princess</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/space-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/space-princess/</guid>
      <description>Launch the Village Princess game and try to collect coins and gems in the air. Send the character up and move him in the air in such a way as to capture as many points as possible. At each level, you need to Crazy Games a specified number of points in a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waking Up Sleeping Beauty</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/waking-up-sleeping-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/waking-up-sleeping-beauty/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for the ball is a serious matter and does not contain trifles. That is why in this game you will not only have to dress up a girl for a ball, but also work on hair, makeup and even eye color. And you don&amp;rsquo;t always have to use ready-made templates. In some moments, you can show your imagination and get creative.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
