<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thief Bob on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/thief-bob/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thief Bob on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/thief-bob/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bob The Robber 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-3/</guid>
      <description>Help the thief escape from the police. All you have to do is use the mouse to drag the robber around the playing field, preventing him from colliding with the cops. The longer you survive, the more points you earn that will allow you to move on to the next level. And remember, you can&amp;rsquo;t touch the walls either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob the Robber 4 Season 1 France</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-4-season-1-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-4-season-1-france/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to help two delinquents to escape from the crime scene. Use arrow keys to move. The main task is to stun the watchman and clear the way for escape. To pick up or use an item - press X, to run - C. And remember, you only need to act together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob the Robber 4 Season 2 Russia</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-4-season-2-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-4-season-2-russia/</guid>
      <description>Today you will play on behalf of a thief who stole valuables and money from the house, and now a whole squad of police is chasing him. You need to help him escape at any cost, moving through the intricate labyrinth and trying not to fall into the field of view of the guards. Use any cover to hide from the pursuit of the police.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob the Robber 4 Season 3 Japan</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-4-season-3-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-4-season-3-japan/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will be in the role of a fugitive criminal. You will need to jump on the roofs and balconies of buildings in order to collect bags of money and banknotes. Try not to fall into the hands of the police. The task is to Crazy Games as many points as indicated at the top of the screen in order to move on to the next stage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
