<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Score on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/score/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Score on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/score/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beautys Bookshop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/beautys-bookshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/beautys-bookshop/</guid>
      <description>Work in a bookstore that certainly doesn&amp;rsquo;t suffer from a lack of customers. Find out from customers what books they are interested in, and then sell them the goods they need. The game consists of a large number of levels, and on each of them you need to earn at least the specified amount of money. Time for the task is limited!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dotted Girl Christmas Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dotted-girl-christmas-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dotted-girl-christmas-shopping/</guid>
      <description>Santa&amp;rsquo;s shop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellie Wedding Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-wedding-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-wedding-shopping/</guid>
      <description>Fascinating game Shop invites you to work as a salesman at a point of sale that sells a variety of umbrellas. Any person needs this accessory, so the store does not suffer from a lack of customers. Customers who want to buy a nice and comfortable umbrella will constantly come here. You just have to find out what kind of umbrella the visitor wants, and sell him the right product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girls Mall Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/girls-mall-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/girls-mall-shopping/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you are invited to work in a store that sells clothes, shoes and various accessories for them. Fashionistas who want to dress up for the new season will come to you. The task is to listen to the wishes of the visitors, and then sell them the right products. At each level you need to earn a certain amount.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lady Mommy Goes Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lady-mommy-goes-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lady-mommy-goes-shopping/</guid>
      <description>During the Supermarket Shopping game you have to help the fairy Stella get ready for the wedding ceremony. To do this, you need to go to the store and buy there the things that she will need for the wedding. There is a limited time allotted for this, and you should hurry up, otherwise Stella will be very upset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mommy Goes Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mommy-goes-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mommy-goes-shopping/</guid>
      <description>Starting the process of the game Store Supermarket will turn you into a seller. You will work in a store that sells a variety of sporting goods. Many people in winter want to be active and have fun. Therefore, your virtual outlet never suffers from a lack of visitors. The sports shop-supermarket will constantly be visited by customers who want to buy skates, skis or snowboards. All you have to do is find out exactly what the visitor of the store wants to buy, and then accompany him to the appropriate rack with the goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panda Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/panda-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/panda-manager/</guid>
      <description>The departments of the supermarket are a terrible mess, and the store should not be left in this state. Start a thorough cleaning to restore the normal state of things. Throw out the trash, put all the goods in their places, remove the dirt. The task is given a limited time, you can follow it on the scale at the bottom of the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Avas Flower Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-avas-flower-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-avas-flower-shop/</guid>
      <description>This wonderful game invites you to try yourself as a jeweler. You will work in a store that sells a variety of jewelry. Girls who want to get a stylish accessory come here all the time. You need to listen to their wishes and create chic jewelry for clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Christmas Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-christmas-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-christmas-shopping/</guid>
      <description>The New Year holidays are approaching, and people want to buy gifts and festive Christmas tree decorations. You will work in a store where all this is sold. Carefully follow the wishes of customers, and then bring them the appropriate goods for which you will receive money. Lots and lots of levels ahead</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Donuts Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-donuts-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-donuts-shop/</guid>
      <description>The game Create your store offers you to feel like a designer. Work on the appearance of your own shop, where various sweets will be sold. Choose the color of its walls and roof, add a sign, decide on some decorative elements. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to invite a cheerful salesperson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Handmade Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-handmade-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-handmade-shop/</guid>
      <description>Create a cute look for a cute girl. Your task is to pick up clothes, shoes, jewelry, a handbag for the heroine of the game. Also, do not forget to decide on a hairstyle that will fit perfectly into her new image. And here you can change the background, choosing one on which the girl will look most impressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Tailor Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-tailor-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-tailor-shop/</guid>
      <description>For the duration of this game, you will turn into a shop worker that sells gorgeous wedding dresses. Your task is to sell outfits to the brides who come here. They will tell you exactly what they want, after which it remains only to demonstrate the right dress and get money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Tailor Shop samename1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-tailor-shop-samename1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-tailor-shop-samename1/</guid>
      <description>The Clothes Shop game takes you to a beach town where you can have a great time. To get started, choose a girl on whose behalf you will play. She is constantly invited to all kinds of parties, which have a strict dress code. Your task is to find suitable clothes in the stores, put them on the heroine and go to events. With a lack of money, you can work in a cafe that offers ice cream and drinks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Tailor Shop samename2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-tailor-shop-samename2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-tailor-shop-samename2/</guid>
      <description>During this game you have to work in the studio. Clients who want to get exclusive things constantly come here. It is necessary to carefully listen to all the wishes and take measurements from the visitor. Next, move to the sewing machine and create a masterpiece. For ready-made clothes, you will receive a generous payment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Winter Shopping Online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-winter-shopping-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-winter-shopping-online/</guid>
      <description>During this game you have to create a cute new look for the girl. To begin with, it is proposed to make the heroine make-up, using a variety of decorative cosmetics for this. Then you can start choosing clothes, shoes and stylish accessories. The finished image will receive an assessment, which will immediately appear on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princesses Paris Shopping Spree</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-paris-shopping-spree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-paris-shopping-spree/</guid>
      <description>The girl decided to buy new shoes, and you need to help her with this. The game has a huge assortment of shoes, and you can choose any pair. And it&amp;rsquo;s not just limited to shoes! You can change the cute fashionista&amp;rsquo;s outfit and change her hairstyle by choosing the cutest option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princesses Royal Boutique</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-royal-boutique/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-royal-boutique/</guid>
      <description>During the game Shopping and buying clothes you have to help a cute girl to prepare for the wedding. Go shopping for all the stylish items you need to create a chic bridal look. Buy a dress, veil, jewelry, shoes and make a suitable hairstyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princesses Shopping Rivals</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-shopping-rivals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-shopping-rivals/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game Shoe and Clothes Shop, you will meet a charming girl who is going to go shopping. Your task is to create a great image for a fashionista to go shopping. Choose clothes, shoes, various accessories, trying to achieve the most harmonious combination of all elements. Do not forget about the hairstyle, which is quite an important component of an attractive appearance. The finished image of the girl can be saved or printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rachel Sweet Candy Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rachel-sweet-candy-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rachel-sweet-candy-shop/</guid>
      <description>During the game Shop supermarket cashier you will be asked to sell perfumes. There will always be people coming to your department who want a perfume that suits them perfectly. The challenge is to properly serve each customer by offering them exactly the product they crave. Store visitors, receiving the desired perfume, will pay the seller in the supermarket for their cost. The game consists of a large number of levels, and in each level you need to sell as many goods in order to earn a specified amount of money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soda Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/soda-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/soda-shop/</guid>
      <description>The game Supermarket Mania invites you to go grocery shopping. The task is to purchase the goods indicated in the list. Study it carefully and find the right items on the shelves. There is a limited amount of time to complete the task. If you don&amp;rsquo;t make it in time, the game will end in defeat for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/supermarket-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/supermarket-manager/</guid>
      <description>During the game Grocery Supermarket you will be asked to help the girl to make purchases. In front of you are several stores that open in sequence. Go to the open one at the moment and start buying goods. The girl will tell you what she needs, and you just have to find the thing on the shelves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/toy-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/toy-shop/</guid>
      <description>During this game, you will turn into a salesman working in a toy store. Your task is to sell incoming customers exactly what they want. Pay close attention to what customers want, and then bring them the right toys and get paid for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/valentines-day-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/valentines-day-shopping/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to work in a store that offers gifts for lovers. People who want to please their soul mates will come here. It is necessary to listen to the wishes of visitors, and then bring them the right product. Collect the specified amount of money on each level to play further.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
