<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rangers Samurai on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/rangers-samurai/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rangers Samurai on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/rangers-samurai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Power Rangers Duel Megaforce</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-power-rangers-duel-megaforce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-power-rangers-duel-megaforce/</guid>
      <description>One of the most serious criminals in the entire galaxy was about to destroy the Rangers, using the services of the monsters that he collected from the universe. You have to fight back the attacking enemies in order to prevent the capture of the Earth. If you allow yourself to be defeated, you will not only lose, but also give the enemy the entire planet to plunder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Power Rangers Megaforce 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-power-rangers-megaforce-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-power-rangers-megaforce-2/</guid>
      <description>During the game Power Rangers Megaforce 2, in addition to killing opponents, you need to collect plasma balls that will give extra points. At the end of each level, a boss will be waiting for you. After a short dialogue, it must be destroyed using the entire available arsenal of weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rangers game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rangers-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rangers-game/</guid>
      <description>The exciting game Rangers will tell you about the struggle of teenagers with magical powers against the most dangerous villains who are trying to destroy our planet. And only with your help will the young warriors be able to destroy the sinister plans of the enemies, having gone through incredibly difficult trials. The key to success is the unification of efforts and teamwork. But even alone, each such warrior poses a considerable threat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
