<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Racing for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/racing-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Racing for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/racing-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3d Monster Truck Icy Roads</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/3d-monster-truck-icy-roads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/3d-monster-truck-icy-roads/</guid>
      <description>To show off your signature driving style will give you the opportunity to play Drift Racing for two. Do you like tight turns at full speed? Then this competition is just for you. Outrun rivals on the track and come first to the finish line. Use the handbrake when passing difficult sections of the track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Mini Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cartoon-mini-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cartoon-mini-racing/</guid>
      <description>Super racing games for two attract attention with competent and thoughtful driving. Since you have to race in huge jeeps on a special training ground, you should pay attention to the correct entry into the obstacle. If you deviate a little to the side, then after the jump, the landing may not be very pleasant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly Car Stunt</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fly-car-stunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fly-car-stunt/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game Racing for two players, you will be able to take part in a high-speed competition. In total, four racers participate in it, including you. It is important to note that you can choose both single-player mode and a game for 2 players. In the second case, only two opponents will be virtual, and two cars will be controlled by real people. After you decide on the regime, you can proceed directly to the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Fast Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-fast-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-fast-racing/</guid>
      <description>Flash games Racing for two - this is the most amazing entertainment that you can find to run on your computer. Compete with your friends, race at full speed and buy new cars with the money you earn. This flash toy will appeal to all lovers of thrills and high-speed racing on powerful cars. You have to go through several tracks with many turns. The car skids a lot, so be careful with the gas pedal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow Storm</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-storm/</guid>
      <description>In the game Cool racing for two you have to participate in circular races on various tracks. Choose your car, then the track and go to the competition. This is where the ability to drift and skillfully go around obstacles at high speed comes in handy. Win races and earn money to be able to buy a new car and open access to new levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Rumble</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-rumble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-rumble/</guid>
      <description>Racing games for two tanks will show you how the competition of these bulky cars actually goes. Agree, it is difficult to imagine a tank on the steep turns of the race track. You have the opportunity to drive this combat vehicle and try to be the first to the finish line. The most important thing is to enter the turns correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
