<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pets on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/pets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pets on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/pets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Robot Dog City Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/robot-dog-city-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/robot-dog-city-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Create your own funny pet and play with it. First, choose the appearance of the character, and then decide on its color and come up with a name. Next, you will need to dress up the ward. Finally, you can start the process of caring for a cute little animal! Feed him, play with him, put him to bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Pet Shop in the Woods</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-little-pet-shop-in-the-woods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-little-pet-shop-in-the-woods/</guid>
      <description>After starting this exciting game, you have to work in a store that sells different pets. It is necessary to meet buyers and find out who they want to acquire. Then it remains only to choose a suitable pet and bring it to the client, receiving money for it. Act as quickly as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lost Pets</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-lost-pets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-lost-pets/</guid>
      <description>The game My Pet will appeal to all lovers of pets. Here you are invited to take care of a small four-legged baby. Choose who it will be: a cat or a dog. You can also choose the appearance of the pet and give it a name. Next, go to the house where your animal will live. Your task is to feed your new friend, play with him, carry out various useful procedures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toy Maker</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/toy-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/toy-maker/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game, you will be asked to prepare your pet for the exhibition. First, choose the character you want to decorate. Next, carry out all hygiene procedures, and then choose a nice outfit for him. After that, all that remains is to go on stage, getting into the lenses of cameras.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
