<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For girls on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-girls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For girls on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-girls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game For girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-girls/</guid>
      <description>The developers of the game for girls Rastishka invite you to the fairy-tale world of the famous dragon Dino. Walk along the streets of a small town together with a funny character and play all the games that a wonderful dragon will offer you. For participation in each of them you will receive gold coins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game for girls along the line</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-girls-along-the-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-girls-along-the-line/</guid>
      <description>The authors of the game for girls Along the Lines invite you to test your reaction. Try to guide the ball with the mouse cursor through the narrow tunnel. Be careful, if your circle hits the wall of the tunnel, the game will be lost and you will have to start all over again. You can play on your own, or you can invite your friends to take part in an exciting competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game For Girls Roller Coaster 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-girls-roller-coaster-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-girls-roller-coaster-2/</guid>
      <description>The process of the game for girls Rollercoaster 2 is dedicated to the attraction on which the explosion occurred. Your task is to move along the tracks, jumping over the abysses and other obstacles in time. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect money that you can use to purchase upgrades in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game For Girls Shopping in China</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-girls-shopping-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-girls-shopping-in-china/</guid>
      <description>After the launch of the shopping game for girls in China, you will be invited to go to Beijing for a shopping spree. Here it is necessary not just to mindlessly go shopping, but to perform certain tasks. They are associated with the acquisition of suitable outfits for parties. Every event you are invited to has a strict dress code. Going shopping, you will have to go shopping and choose exactly those things that meet the conditions stated in the game for girls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Spongebob Squarepants for girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-spongebob-squarepants-for-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-spongebob-squarepants-for-girls/</guid>
      <description>Game for girls SpongeBob Squarepants is quite suitable for boys too. It has a neutral plot and develops logical thinking very well. In the process, you need to quickly and carefully think through all the movements of the character. The level is considered successfully completed when SpongeBob Squarepants collects all the trash and bonuses on the table. Jellyfish scurrying back and forth only provide additional points, but no more. The sharpness is added by the limited time to complete the level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagirls Halloween Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/instagirls-halloween-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/instagirls-halloween-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>All girls, without exception, love to go shopping. So today, three girlfriends visited the shopping center and bought a lot of new things. You can not only review all their purchases, but also help with fitting things. To start playing, press &amp;ldquo;play&amp;rdquo;. Then choose any of the girls and start trying on by simply dragging and dropping clothes onto her with the mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roller coaster game for girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/roller-coaster-game-for-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/roller-coaster-game-for-girls/</guid>
      <description>Launching the roller coaster game for girls, available absolutely free of charge, will take you to a ride that is in a terrible state after the explosion. But you can still ride it, having received a considerable portion of adrenaline. The task is to navigate the rollercoaster tracks by jumping over various obstacles or passing under them while ducking. It is impossible to face obstacles - this will inevitably lead to a loss.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
