<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fishing on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/fishing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fishing on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/fishing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Fishing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-fishing/</guid>
      <description>With the help of the game Fishing for two you will be able to feel the spirit of competition, which is so typical for fishermen. Real fishing enthusiasts do not part with their hobby even at home. Of course, the game cannot be compared with the sensations of real water hunting, but just spending time at the computer with a friend is also worth a lot. So let&amp;rsquo;s get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Master</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fish-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fish-master/</guid>
      <description>Great game about fishing with a float rod. Cast your tackle and wait for the fish to take the bait. For every fish you catch, you get a lot of money. The casting force can be controlled by the indicator on the right side of the screen using the mouse. Earned coins to spend on new gear and bait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fishing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fishing/</guid>
      <description>According to the terms of the game Catch Fish, you start your way in business as an ordinary fisherman. Stock up on a fishing rod and go to the pond to catch a couple of fish for lunch. As soon as you have more prey than you need for food, you can sell it at special outlets. You have to manage your own markups to secure a suitable profit. It&amp;rsquo;s easy enough to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Fish</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/go-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/go-fish/</guid>
      <description>During the game Fishing for Catfish you have to try to catch 30 catfish in the time left before nightfall. These fish are very picky, so keep an eye on bites and change the bait in time. A frying pan is heating near you - you can immediately fry the caught fish. But the game has time limits, so don&amp;rsquo;t relax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Fishing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/great-fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/great-fishing/</guid>
      <description>The game Summer Fishing will give true lovers of fishing great pleasure. Sit on your island and hook everything that moves. In addition to various fish, you can also catch watches to extend the level time and bait for other types of fish. The casting distance is controlled by the mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Lake</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/green-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/green-lake/</guid>
      <description>The Ural fishing application to play for free will make you be patient and go to the pond in winter. The main thing is to dress warmly, because in this ice kingdom you will have to stay for a long time. The peculiarity of fishing is that it is impossible to predict where the fish is. Only experienced anglers can determine the location of a likely bite. Drill a hole and watch your fishing rod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Lake Fishing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/summer-lake-fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/summer-lake-fishing/</guid>
      <description>Tom is very fond of fresh fish, but first you still need to catch it. He had to take a fishing rod in his paws and go fishing. You need to help hungry Tom catch as many fish as possible. The game has a huge number of hints, and if you follow all the instructions, you will be able to provide the cat with food for a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
