<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My little Pony on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/my-little-pony/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My little Pony on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/my-little-pony/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fluttershy Pony Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fluttershy-pony-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fluttershy-pony-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>If you like the animated series about cute horses, then you will also like the process of playing My Little Pony for two. Her main character is Princess Twilight Sparkle, who is going to have a real pillow fight. Just click on any place on the screen, after which the pillow will strike the horse. You can fight as you like, watching the reaction of the pony and enjoying such a fun activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony Winter Fashion 1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-little-pony-winter-fashion-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-little-pony-winter-fashion-1/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you have to dress up Bon Bon. Here the pony is presented in the form of a charming girl who loves to dress up in stylish things. Your task is to create a nice image. Use for this any of the proposed elements of the virtual wardrobe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony Pet Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-pet-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-pet-salon/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game Dress Up My Little Equestria Girl Pony, you will see Sapphire Shores, a minor character in the animated series. She took on a human form and really wants to get a fashionable outfit, like a real girl. Help Sapphire change and choose the right hairstyle for her. You can change your hair color!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Fairytale Pony Grooming</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-fairytale-pony-grooming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-fairytale-pony-grooming/</guid>
      <description>Do you love dressing up? Then boldly launch this most interesting game! Here you have to come up with a new image for the cutie pony. The virtual wardrobe includes three categories of things: hats, suits and shoes. You need to combine the selected little things with each other, trying to get the most attractive result.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
