<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Restaurants on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/restaurants/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Restaurants on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/restaurants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Annie Cooking Donuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/annie-cooking-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/annie-cooking-donuts/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to become an employee of a small cafe where everyone can taste the most delicious donuts in the world, prepared according to the recipe of the famous chef Papa Louie. Carefully write down the order of each visitor and try to prepare an original donut that will amaze the guest with its appearance and taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ariels Cake Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ariels-cake-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ariels-cake-shop/</guid>
      <description>Papa Louie opens a new original cafe where everyone can try wonderful cupcakes with air cream. A famous chef invites you to become an employee of this establishment. Try to serve as many customers as possible by treating them with cupcakes prepared according to the recipe of the famous chef.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Burger Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/biggest-burger-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/biggest-burger-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Many girls will like the Burger Restaurant 1 game. The work ahead is difficult, because you need to serve a lot of customers in a day. Look at the orders of visitors and make sandwiches at a very fast pace. For a day of work, you need to earn a certain amount of money, which is indicated in the upper right corner under the inscription &amp;ldquo;Target&amp;rdquo;. Your time is also limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Truck Frenzy USA</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/burger-truck-frenzy-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/burger-truck-frenzy-usa/</guid>
      <description>The Burger Restaurant 3 game will give you a wonderful opportunity to test yourself as a manager of a small cafe, who is also a cook, a waiter, and a cashier. The game features a long counter where visitors come up to place an order and wait for it to be filled. It takes a lot of hard work to keep customers happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caf Paris</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/caf-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/caf-paris/</guid>
      <description>Your old friend Cooper and his cat Cookie got a job in a cafe opened by the famous Papa Louie. The guy is very happy that he found such a job and invites you to join the team of the best chef in the world. Help the hero of the game serve as many visitors as possible and get big tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Panic</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cafe-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cafe-panic/</guid>
      <description>The game about the restaurant business invites you to try your hand at the role of the head of one of the companies specializing in the development of a chain of small restaurants. Try to build the maximum number of cafes in a limited time as quickly as possible. Thanks to your talent and diligence, the created network will become the most popular in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking Fast Hotdogs And Burgers Craze</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cooking-fast-hotdogs-and-burgers-craze/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cooking-fast-hotdogs-and-burgers-craze/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to become an employee of one of the eateries located in the stadium. Try to fulfill the orders of all visitors to your cafe as quickly as possible. The money you earn at the establishment can be used to purchase new equipment and products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking Scene</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cooking-scene/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cooking-scene/</guid>
      <description>During the online game Restaurant Business you become one of the employees of a small cafe in the center of the capital of the fairy kingdom. Try to serve each of the visitors as quickly as possible. Thanks to your efforts, all the wishes of customers will be fulfilled and they will definitely become regular guests of your cafe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand Made Ice Cream Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hand-made-ice-cream-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hand-made-ice-cream-cooking/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you become a famous confectioner who decided to open a small cafe in the city center. Huge crowds of visitors dream of trying the unique biscuit cakes prepared by you. So try to present to each of your guests exactly the dessert that he ordered, and do it as quickly as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Sushi Roll</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-sushi-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-sushi-roll/</guid>
      <description>In this wonderful game you have to become an architect who needs to design a small town. Try to develop a unique infrastructure that will delight people who decide to settle in this nice place. Carefully monitor the behavior of the settlers and complete the town with the necessary buildings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cream Bar</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-cream-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-cream-bar/</guid>
      <description>The game Daddy&amp;rsquo;s Ice Cream Shop sends you to one of the islands in the Pacific Ocean. There you will work in a cafe where each visitor is offered the most delicious ice cream on the island. Try to fulfill the orders of all the customers of the institution, and use the money received from them to develop a cozy cafe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princesses Burger Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-burger-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-burger-cooking/</guid>
      <description>Burger Restaurant 4 games will tell you about a unique place where you can just have a bite to eat or a hearty meal. This is another project of Papa Louis, in which he invested all his earned money. You have to cook burgers. All ingredients are available immediately after the start of the level, so get started with the task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratatouille Saras Cooking Class</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ratatouille-saras-cooking-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ratatouille-saras-cooking-class/</guid>
      <description>During the restaurant game for girls you meet a cute girl who works as a waitress. Unfortunately, her partner fell ill, and now the heroine of the game has to serve all the guests on her own. Help your new girlfriend deal with the visitors of the establishment. Try to fulfill the wishes of customers as quickly as possible, because this will bring you more tips, which can then be invested in the development of the cafe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salad Bar</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/salad-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/salad-bar/</guid>
      <description>The game Dad&amp;rsquo;s Restaurant introduces you to a talented rocker who has lost all his instruments. In order to buy new ones, he got a job at a small diner. Help your buddy serve all the customers of the cafe, earn huge tips, buy instruments and hold your first solo concert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yukikos Sushi Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/yukikos-sushi-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/yukikos-sushi-shop/</guid>
      <description>The hero of this game becomes the administrator of a small hotel and asks you for help. By controlling the movements of your new friend, try to serve all the guests of the hotel. Carefully monitor their mood and try to please everyone. Satisfied customers will be happy to visit you many more times.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
