<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wedding on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/wedding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wedding on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/wedding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angela And Tom Dream Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/angela-and-tom-dream-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/angela-and-tom-dream-wedding/</guid>
      <description>During the game Angela and Tom wedding you have to help the cat couple. Cat Tom proposed to his beloved Angela, and she agreed. Now is the time to start preparing for the wedding. Your task is to put the characters in the game in order. Start with Tom. Cut off excess hair, remove parasites and do not forget to treat the paws. Next, go to Angela. The kitty also needs a haircut, and you can also give her special make-up for the wedding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cindy Wedding Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cindy-wedding-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cindy-wedding-shopping/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will meet a couple in love. The guy and the girl decided to have a wedding on New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve. They really want to kiss, but there are a lot of unnecessary witnesses around. You can&amp;rsquo;t let anyone notice the kiss. Therefore, stop it as soon as there is a risk of being seen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Princess Wedding Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-wedding-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-wedding-day/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will meet a cute girl who is about to get married. Naturally, she wants to look her best. Your task is to create a perfect bridal look using any of the presented items of the wardrobe. Choose a dress, tiara, veil, shoes, jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapunzel Wedding Party Dress</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rapunzel-wedding-party-dress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rapunzel-wedding-party-dress/</guid>
      <description>After launching the game for girls My Dream Wedding, you will turn into a real wedding ceremonies expert. You need to decorate the venue for the next holiday. To do this, you have at your disposal a huge number of decorative elements that can be installed anywhere. The size of objects can be easily changed, and it is also possible to repaint them in any color you like. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to add the bride and groom!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
