<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business simulators on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/business-simulators/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business simulators on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/business-simulators/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beach Restaurant</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/beach-restaurant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/beach-restaurant/</guid>
      <description>You are invited to work in the diner, which is located in the cinema. People going to see a movie will certainly want to buy popcorn or a drink. It remains only to fulfill the orders of visitors, receiving money for this. Try to do everything very quickly so that customers do not get angry, otherwise they may leave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idle Farm Tycoon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/idle-farm-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/idle-farm-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>Your farm is in danger, competitors want to take it over. Therefore, it is necessary to take care of the economy, developing it and expanding their possessions. In the game, you will constantly be given various tasks related to the production of products and their delivery. You should quickly achieve goals by receiving money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idle Fish</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/idle-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/idle-fish/</guid>
      <description>Become the owner of a virtual fish farm. After starting the game, a pond will appear in front of you, where you can settle a variety of fish. They will give caviar and other useful products that can be sold in the future. The process consists of a large number of levels, and on each you need to complete the given tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Broadway Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-broadway-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-broadway-shopping/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to manage a store that sells chic outfits. Girls who want to buy a beautiful dress will constantly come here. Your task is to listen to the wishes of the clients and sell them the outfit they want. At each level you need to earn the specified amount.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Business</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/real-estate-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/real-estate-business/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you have to build cities and develop them. In front of you is a territory where you can build a variety of buildings. Build them, given that each building requires an infusion of a certain amount of finance. Try to achieve good profits and the normal functioning of all objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tap For Money Restaurant</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tap-for-money-restaurant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tap-for-money-restaurant/</guid>
      <description>This exciting game is reminiscent of the board Monopoly. On the screen you will see a field marked into cells. Press the button, which acts as a cube, and move to the appropriate number of cells. Acquire firms, make bank deposits, play casinos. Your goal is to get rich and deprive your rivals of their income.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
