<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>scary on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/scary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in scary on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/scary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Bikers</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-bikers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-bikers/</guid>
      <description>While playing Horror Stories for the night, you find yourself in a small village whose inhabitants are suffering from an invasion of zombies that have suddenly appeared in an old cemetery. Help the unfortunate townspeople escape from the fate of being eaten and destroy all the monsters walking around the suburbs. Using a six-shot revolver, shoot the monsters in each of the locations of the horror story. Be careful, each of the evil dead is able to kill you, while the game will end immediately and you will have to start its passage from the beginning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoot Your Nightmare Halloween Special</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/shoot-your-nightmare-halloween-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/shoot-your-nightmare-halloween-special/</guid>
      <description>Maniac Slenderman is chasing you through the tangled corridors of an unknown building. And you need to escape from here as soon as possible in order to save your life. However, first you have to find documents, keys and other auxiliary items that will help restore health and find a way out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slenderman History: WWII Faceless Horror</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-history-wwii-faceless-horror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-history-wwii-faceless-horror/</guid>
      <description>In this game, incredible adventures await you, during which you are invited to fight against crowds of evil spirits. You have a weapon at your disposal, use it to attack enemies. Try not to let the opponents touch you, otherwise they will quickly take away health points, which will lead to a loss. As you progress through your character, you can improve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slenderman Must Die Silent Streets</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-must-die-silent-streets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-must-die-silent-streets/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will control a gravedigger. The task to be completed is to bury the corpses, which, by the way, have also come to life. Skeletons, zombies, vampires - all should be buried. You have to go to all sorts of tricks so that the escaped dead are again in the grave. Quickly click on the individuals appearing here and there, wishing to return to this world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slenderman Must Die: Abandoned Graveyard</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-must-die-abandoned-graveyard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-must-die-abandoned-graveyard/</guid>
      <description>Slenderman game will introduce you to the legendary faceless monster. His face is smooth, sickly white skin. The body is disproportionate. Slenderman is the owner of a very thin, inhuman figure, which immediately betrays a diabolical essence in him. But the worst thing about the monster is its hands. They stretch to incredible lengths and can transform into vile slendrin tentacles. According to the plot, you, along with the main character of the game, wake up in an unknown place that looks like a hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
