<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>coloring pages on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/coloring-pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in coloring pages on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/coloring-pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Butterfly Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/butterfly-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/butterfly-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Here is a bow coloring for toddlers. If suddenly they do not go to kindergarten for some reason, you can study vegetables at home using a computer. Using the example of a colored picture, it is easy to explain to the child the process of bulb ripening. Coloring is easy: move the mouse cursor to the desired color, click and go to the area in the picture. Click there again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Me Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/color-me-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/color-me-christmas/</guid>
      <description>It is immediately obvious that the game Coloring pages seasons for children is designed to develop their creative abilities and craving for drawing. And the point is not only in a large drawing with a thematic plot, but also in the fact that from the very first second the voice-over is turned on. A pleasant female voice tells the players what to do and how to do it. Coloring will be easy, but interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Me Pets 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/color-me-pets-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/color-me-pets-2/</guid>
      <description>You won&amp;rsquo;t have to work with animated characters while playing Live Coloring Pages. However, the drawing and colors of the paints are so natural that the drawing literally comes to life during processing. The plot of the picture is based on a fragment of the cartoon about Smeshariki. The result of your work can be printed on a printer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coloring Time Animals</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/coloring-time-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/coloring-time-animals/</guid>
      <description>During the game Coloring for two you will be able to show your creativity. Here you are invited to color the image of two pretty girls. At the bottom of the screen is a palette that includes a large number of colors. Choose any of them and apply as you wish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doll Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/doll-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/doll-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Online coloring Barbie invites you to work on the image of a girl and her horse. A black and white picture will appear on the screen, it must be made bright by adding a variety of colors. All available colors are located at the bottom of the screen, and there are really a lot of them. You just have to click on the color you like, and then transfer it to the desired section of the coloring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/football-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/football-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Summer coloring for kids will show you a black and white picture of funny octopuses enjoying a walk. It is proposed to color this cute picture using any of the colors offered on the screen. You will find all available colors at the bottom of it. There are really a lot of them here! Therefore, the image of summer will turn out to be bright and attractive. Click on the selected color, and then click on the area you are going to color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football Coloring Time</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/football-coloring-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/football-coloring-time/</guid>
      <description>Coloring for children The ball is not as simple as it might seem from the name. Firstly, the ball itself is a soccer ball, which allows you to paint in its parts in separate colors. Secondly, in addition to the ball, the picture also shows a football player kicking it - this is a kitten that resembles the hero of some cartoon. You also need to make it colorful.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
