<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sports on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Drunk wrestlers game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/drunk-wrestlers-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/drunk-wrestlers-game/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the international boxing tournament. You have to demonstrate your skills and excellent reaction in order to get the belt of the winner of this competition. Try to knock out all your competitors and prove that you are the main contender for the crown of the world boxing champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Sports 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-sports-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-sports-3d/</guid>
      <description>Sports games 3D invite you to plunge into the world of football champions and become a recognized star in them. Intercept the ball from the opponent, and then try to break into his half of the field or pass the ball to another player on your team. Choose the moment and hit the gate. Show your true style and protect the sporting honor of your team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Wrestling Out of Gravity</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-wrestling-out-of-gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-wrestling-out-of-gravity/</guid>
      <description>Two famous Mexican fighters decided to hold a series of unique fights. They will measure their strength on special sites without gravity. Choose one of the participants in the competition, fight several fights with different opponents and try to prove that your character is the best wrestler in the whole world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skate extreme game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/skate-extreme-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/skate-extreme-game/</guid>
      <description>Skateboarding is one of the extreme sports. In this game you have to play on behalf of a dashing skater, demonstrating all sorts of tricks while passing the track. And do not be lazy to collect bonuses, they will give you the opportunity to purchase new equipment and wheels for the board. To perform tricks, use the Z, X and C buttons. Arrow keys - move.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
