<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tanks on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/tanks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tanks on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/tanks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Armour Clash</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/armour-clash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/armour-clash/</guid>
      <description>An excellent 3D Ww3 tank game in which you will drive a very maneuverable and well-armed armored vehicle. Use mouse to aim, left click to fire. Enemy vehicles will show up on your radar. Use the number keys to switch between available weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neon Battle Tank</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/neon-battle-tank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/neon-battle-tank/</guid>
      <description>Games Tanks 6 will show you one of the rules of warfare. Never stand still when the battle is on. Stopped - consider hit. And in this game you should stick to just such a manner of conducting a shootout. There are many enemies, they have fast cars and they constantly attack. Control the tank with the arrow keys and constantly shoot at the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick Tank Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stick-tank-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stick-tank-wars/</guid>
      <description>With the help of the Steam Tanks game you will have to take part in races on modern tanks. In life, of course, a combat vehicle does not drive like that. But this is a computer game in which everything is possible. In general, his speed is decent, and unlike a car, he is not afraid of roadsides or trees. But be careful when overcoming obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Driver Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-driver-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-driver-simulator/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to become a driver of a modern tank. Try to park your combat vehicle on the territory of a military base filled with a huge amount of equipment. By controlling the movements of the tank, try to bring it to the parking place. Be careful, if you hit other vehicles during an unsuccessful maneuver, you will have to go through the level again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanko io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanko-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanko-io/</guid>
      <description>While playing Tanks with a team, you become one of the US servicemen who took part in the opening of the second front during the Second World War. At the beginning of the story, you are the driver of one of the armored vehicles participating in the battles. Gaining experience in combat operations, you gradually gain access to more powerful types of military equipment needed in the fight against the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanko.io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanko.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanko.io/</guid>
      <description>Super tank games will allow you to plunge into the world of real battles. Any tanker dreams of driving a powerful machine that can level an entire city to the ground in a matter of seconds. Today you have just such a tank at your disposal. He has a bunch of the most modern deadly weapons in his arsenal. To learn more about control keys, press Enter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanko.io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tankoio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tankoio/</guid>
      <description>Super tank games will allow you to plunge into the world of real battles. Any tanker dreams of driving a powerful machine that can level an entire city to the ground in a matter of seconds. Today you have just such a tank at your disposal. He has a bunch of the most modern deadly weapons in his arsenal. To learn more about control keys, press Enter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanks Master</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-master/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to this game, you find yourself in the unique times of the appearance of the first tanks as a new type of weapon. Then these monsters looked completely different from what they are today, they had a steam engine, weak weapons and thin armor. You have to show design skills, upgrade your combat vehicle and defeat all enemies. Thus, you will prove the viability of this type of technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanks Squad</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-squad/</guid>
      <description>The game offers you to fight hordes of crayfish on ten difficulty levels. This version features three types of arthropods: small, medium and large individuals. Each type has its own individual style of combat, and the composition and size of the enemy team depends on the tank chosen by the player and the level of difficulty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanksmith io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanksmith-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanksmith-io/</guid>
      <description>Playing World of Tanks has become much more difficult. Before you is a fairly realistic simulator for driving a huge machine, made in 3D graphics. The effects of shots, explosions and a lot of vehicles will not leave indifferent even the most sophisticated fans of tank battles. It is possible to play online, explore the area, studying the location of enemy equipment and military fortifications. These can be machine gunners, armored vehicles, artillery mounts, bunkers and ammunition depots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanque 3D: Tank Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanque-3d-tank-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanque-3d-tank-battle/</guid>
      <description>The game Tanks against crayfish has a very simple, but at the same time, fantastic plot: crayfish attack a combat vehicle. By the way, they are drawn just fine, which cannot be said about the tank. In addition, there is a top view, aiming and shooting with the mouse. It is better not to stand still, otherwise the crayfish will quickly surround you and crush you. To pass the level, you must destroy a certain number of ticks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warzone Mercenaries</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/warzone-mercenaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/warzone-mercenaries/</guid>
      <description>While playing Lego Tanks you are going to one of the entertainment centers of the constructor&amp;rsquo;s fairyland. There you have to take part in an exciting tournament, show a good reaction, ingenuity and accuracy. While driving a Lego tank, try to destroy all the bots attacking you at each stage of this exciting toy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
