<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>little sticks on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/little-sticks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in little sticks on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/little-sticks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Draw Play Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/draw-play-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/draw-play-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>You need to help Henry Stickman escape from the prison cell. In order for everything to go smoothly, you need to think carefully about the escape plan. Fortunately, friends gave the hero a cake for his birthday, inside of which there was a surprise. There are some items hidden in it that are worth using. But where and how to apply them - you have to guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light It Up Online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/light-it-up-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/light-it-up-online/</guid>
      <description>You have to get rid of all the bad guys in the new shooting game from the Stickman adventure series &amp;ldquo;Headhunter&amp;rdquo;. Upgrade your weapons, get grenades and armor in between missions, trying to defeat enemies at all levels of the game. Remember to reload regularly using the R key and take cover in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickjet Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickjet-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickjet-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Right now you can take part in a tournament where any fighting techniques are allowed, and the main goal is the same - to stay in the ring as long as possible, defeat everyone and become a champion. Moreover, no one has yet been able to hold this title for a long time, because every time more and more new fighters enter the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman 4 Archer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-4-archer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-4-archer/</guid>
      <description>During the game Stickmen at War, you have to study all the weaknesses of your enemies in order to destroy them as soon as possible. Capture the surrounding lands to be able to unlock new units. At each stage, it is necessary to destroy the statue-symbol of the enemy and repel all enemy attacks. After successfully completing the level, you will receive 2 points for upgrading your own troops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Bike Rider</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-bike-rider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-bike-rider/</guid>
      <description>The game Stickmen will give you the opportunity to control a character who will face fierce battles with many opponents. It&amp;rsquo;s good that you have many effective attacks in your arsenal. But don&amp;rsquo;t forget to keep an eye on the hero&amp;rsquo;s health bar. It is also necessary to pick up energy capsules during the battle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Vector</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-vector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-vector/</guid>
      <description>Vinnie and his team have come into conflict with a very vindictive mafia clan. The purpose of the mission is to track down the culprit of their misadventures and deal with him once and for all. But something did not go as planned, and now we have to make decisions based on the current situation. The game perfectly combines elements of sniper battles, hand-to-hand martial arts and intense chases.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
