<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cakes on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/cakes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cakes on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/cakes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cake Design Cooking Game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cake-design-cooking-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cake-design-cooking-game/</guid>
      <description>The exciting game Cakes will turn you into a pastry chef. Here you are invited to prepare a delicious and beautiful dessert that can be served on the table both on a holiday and on any other day. The kitchen has all the necessary ingredients and tools that will be useful in the cooking process. But first, all of the above should be found! Explore the kitchen cabinets to find the indicated items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Princess Cake Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/disney-princess-cake-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/disney-princess-cake-cooking/</guid>
      <description>During this game, you will be asked to work in an establishment that offers to purchase various fresh cakes. Customers will come here, you need to find out what kind of dessert they want to receive, and then cook it in the kitchen. This must be done as quickly as possible so that the buyer does not get bored and does not leave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Thanksgiving Cake Master</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-thanksgiving-cake-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-thanksgiving-cake-master/</guid>
      <description>Cake for kids game invites you to prepare a delicious dessert for your birthday. To begin with, choose the form of future baking and its decoration, after which you can safely proceed to the cooking process. Take the indicated ingredients and mix them in the correct order. It will definitely be fun to play!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Queen Royal Baker</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-royal-baker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-royal-baker/</guid>
      <description>Here you can show all your cooking skills and decorate the cake. To do this, you can use glaze of different colors, cream in a confectionery syringe and a variety of decorative figures. There are also various toppings. And you can also depict a festive inscription using colored letters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Cake Master</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/perfect-cake-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/perfect-cake-master/</guid>
      <description>Make a great cake for the holidays! To do this, you have all the necessary ingredients at your disposal. Handle them as indicated in the prompts that appear on the screen. As a result, you will definitely get an excellent dessert, which will not be difficult to prepare in real life. Shall we try?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisters Cakes Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sisters-cakes-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sisters-cakes-battle/</guid>
      <description>Cakes for Boys game invites you to create creative desserts. Choose one of the three cakes you want to work on. Next, you need to cut the cake along the indicated lines and correctly position the pieces on the dish. After that, it remains only to take care of decorating a sweet treat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Wedding Cake</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/white-wedding-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/white-wedding-cake/</guid>
      <description>During the game Make Cakes you will turn into a pastry chef. Help Princess Elsa prepare a delicious cupcake. First you will need to go to the store to purchase the necessary ingredients. When shopping is complete, move to the kitchen to start making cakes. Mix the indicated components according to the prompts, and then pour the resulting dough into the mold. When the cake is ready, it remains only to decorate with icing and berries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
