<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>naruto on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/naruto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in naruto on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/naruto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game For two Fighting Naruto</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-two-fighting-naruto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-two-fighting-naruto/</guid>
      <description>Fans of the characters of the well-known animated series in certain circles will rejoice, because this product was created specifically for them. Moreover, you can have fun with like-minded friends, because the Naruto fight game mode for two is available. True, fights, as such, will not be here. But interest, nevertheless, is guaranteed. Firstly, in addition to the number of players, you can choose the number of opponents. Secondly, you can deal with them in a very original way - by blowing up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Naruto for two all heroes</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-naruto-for-two-all-heroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-naruto-for-two-all-heroes/</guid>
      <description>Managing the characters of the game Naruto for two all the characters, as in most Chinese entertainment, is cumbersome and requires getting used to. But fans of the popular cartoon, based on which this miracle was made, are no strangers. They are already pleased with the fact that for the passage you can choose any fighter present in the mentioned series. Well, and engage in endless combat 1 on 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naruto game for two</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/naruto-game-for-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/naruto-game-for-two/</guid>
      <description>Naruto game for two is a fighting game in which you will have to fight against many different characters of the universe. First you need to choose who you will manage, then decide on the battle arena and, finally, start the battle. There are control instructions in the game, so it&amp;rsquo;s worth just talking a little about its mechanics. The battle itself in the game about Naruto for two is quite difficult, therefore it is very important to quickly memorize keyboard shortcuts that will allow you to deliver crushing blows to the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
