<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Willy on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/willy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Willy on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/willy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wheely 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-2/</guid>
      <description>The game Car Willie 2 invites you to join the famous little car in pursuit of his beloved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheely 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-3/</guid>
      <description>The character of the game Red Car Willy decided to prove that even a small subcompact car is able to compete in the royal races, and for this he went to the largest racing track in the magical world. Help the kid overcome all the obstacles, take part in the championship race and get a huge car racing champion cup. Willy will be grateful to you for the service rendered and will definitely invite you to the celebrations dedicated to his brilliant victory and the realization of the dream of every miniature car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheely 4 Time Travel</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-4-time-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-4-time-travel/</guid>
      <description>While playing Wheely&amp;rsquo;s Car 4, you meet again with a restless little car who loves adventure. This time he went on a journey through the distant past. You have to help the kid overcome all the obstacles on the way and return to his own time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheely 5 Armageddon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-5-armageddon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-5-armageddon/</guid>
      <description>Willie&amp;rsquo;s Car 5 - Armageddon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheely 6 Fairytale</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-6-fairytale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-6-fairytale/</guid>
      <description>Walking through the streets of the city, Willy saw the most beautiful car in the world. He fell in love with the beauty at first sight, and she reciprocated. Help the hero of the game to wrest his beloved from the clutches of an insidious truck, which decided to separate the lovers and take Willy&amp;rsquo;s bride to another city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheely 7 Detective</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-7-detective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-7-detective/</guid>
      <description>The head of a criminal organization nicknamed Royce seized all the fuel supplies in the city of funny cars. A huge metropolis is threatened with famine, only Willy&amp;rsquo;s little car and you can save civilians. Go in search of the insidious bandit and try to return the fuel to all gas stations in the metropolis as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheely 8 Aliens</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-8-aliens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheely-8-aliens/</guid>
      <description>The game Car Willie 1 takes you to the fantastic world of cars. It is there that you will meet its charming main character. He worked for a very long time in one of the showrooms and was terribly tired of such a pastime. In short moments of rest, baby Willy watched 1 sports channel, and he especially liked to watch car races.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
