<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>talking cat on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/talking-cat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in talking cat on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/talking-cat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angela Tom Baby Feeding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/angela-tom-baby-feeding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/angela-tom-baby-feeding/</guid>
      <description>With the advent of a baby in the family, Angela and Tom have added trouble. The child wakes up almost every night and starts crying. Today you have to help young parents feed their baby. Take the kitten and wrap it in a blanket so Angela can hold it comfortably. Then give your baby a bottle of milk. He eats and stops crying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angela Trip Accident</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/angela-trip-accident/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/angela-trip-accident/</guid>
      <description>Angelica the Cat game will turn you into a doctor. The cat was rollerblading, but suddenly lost her balance and fell. Because of the fall, she received many different injuries, and now the heroine of the game needs qualified medical care. In the game for girls, you will see a variety of tools that you need to use according to the tips to fix Angela&amp;rsquo;s health situation. Instructions are displayed at the top of the screen, and all items needed for healing are located at the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Angela Kissing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tom-angela-kissing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tom-angela-kissing/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to help Tom and Angela kiss. A cat and a cat in love really want to pay attention to each other, but no one should see their kisses. Therefore, as soon as there is a danger of being noticed, it is necessary to immediately stop the exciting process. The progress of passing the level is displayed on the scale at the top of the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
