<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Baby on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/baby/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Baby on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/baby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aqua Bubble Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/aqua-bubble-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/aqua-bubble-shooter/</guid>
      <description>If you like extreme activities, then you will appreciate the process of playing for children aged 10-12. In it you will need to take part in a rather unusual race. You can shoot at your opponents and use various explosive devices to prevent other cars from getting ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Snow Sick Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-snow-sick-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-snow-sick-day/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to play the role of a babysitter for a small child. The baby has peed himself, and he needs to be changed urgently. Do all the necessary hygiene procedures, and then choose a cute outfit, socks and hairstyle for the child. The finished result can be fixed by saving or printing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blaze Trucks</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/blaze-trucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/blaze-trucks/</guid>
      <description>The launch of the game for children Cars will show you the characters of the cartoon of the same name. In it you will need to take part in the racing championship and try to win all its stages. At the beginning of the children&amp;rsquo;s game, only Lightning McQueen is available from the heroes, but as you progress, other cars will open for you. Winding roads in different cities of the world await you ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Garden Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-garden-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-garden-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>edible planet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef Slash</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/chef-slash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/chef-slash/</guid>
      <description>Chef game for kids invites you to the culinary school of the famous Frenchman Monsieur Svin. Today he will show you how to make a chocolate cupcake. Carefully follow the chef&amp;rsquo;s tips and strictly follow them. First, prepare the air dough for cupcakes, put it in molds and send it to the oven. While they are baking, prepare the original chocolate nougat. Once the cupcakes are ready, decorate them with cream and let cool slightly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corinne The Fairy Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/corinne-the-fairy-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/corinne-the-fairy-adventure/</guid>
      <description>The children&amp;rsquo;s game will introduce you to a funny cupid who has a magic bow. But this time, you will have to shoot not at hearts, but at balls. At the top of the screen is a design of a large number of multi-colored balls. At the bottom is your &amp;ldquo;bow&amp;rdquo;, from which you can launch the same rounds up. You need to throw the ball to his fellows of the same color, after which they all fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cut My Rope</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cut-my-rope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cut-my-rope/</guid>
      <description>Simple kids games invite you to do math with Mickey Mouse. He will ask for addition examples, and you just need to choose the correct answer from the five offered. If you answer correctly, you will receive a prize star. Your task is to earn as many of these stars as possible so that Mickey gives you a high mark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dog-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dog-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Kids games about dogs offer you to help little puppy Tim. He, like any other dog, wants to have fun, although the owner of his pranks will definitely not approve. That is why it is necessary to act only when no one is in the room. But if there is a knock on the door, then drop all your activities and pretend that nothing is happening. In the allotted time, you need to have time to eat a ham, tear a pillow, drive cats and do a lot more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elsa Rainbow Donuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-rainbow-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-rainbow-donuts/</guid>
      <description>Children&amp;rsquo;s games Frozen give you the opportunity to work on the image of the cute princess Elsa. First you need to make a girl make-up, using the proposed cosmetic options for this. The second stage is the choice of hairstyle and outfit in which the heroine of the game for children will look simply stunning. Also, do not forget to use all kinds of accessories that will complement the image and make it as complete as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Easter Girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/funny-easter-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/funny-easter-girls/</guid>
      <description>Kids Games Dolls is a beautiful dress up game that invites you to work as a designer in a large toy company. The company&amp;rsquo;s management proposed to create a collection of original toys for girls. During the game for kids about how to dress stylish modern dolls, you have at your disposal a huge range of clothes, jewelry and accessories. Try to create original images that will appeal to the company&amp;rsquo;s specialists and delight little buyers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gobble Snake</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gobble-snake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gobble-snake/</guid>
      <description>The Maze game for kids invites you to have a great time in the company of Dasha the Traveler. This time you need to help her go through the corridors of the intricate labyrinth in order to find a way out of it. You only need a mouse to control it: you need to grab Dasha&amp;rsquo;s figure with the cursor and drag it to the finish line. In this case, you can not run into the walls of the corridors, so you will lose one game life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heroic Quest</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/heroic-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/heroic-quest/</guid>
      <description>Game Quest for kids introduces you to the grandson of the legendary Indiana Jones. He, like his grandfather, is engaged in archeology and loves adventure. Together with him you go in search of lost treasures in the depths of the tropical jungle. Your journey is divided into many stages, at each of which you will have to show resourcefulness and ingenuity. Carefully examine the location where the hero of the game got to, and figure out how he can get to the transition to the next stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jelly Friends</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jelly-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jelly-friends/</guid>
      <description>During the game for preschool children, the smallest fans of computer entertainment will be able to participate in an exciting competition. Try to guess which is colder. The authors offer several test questions that you must answer by choosing one of two pictures. The toy pleases with beautiful design, as well as wonderful musical effects. Each of the questions is duplicated by the announcer, which helps the baby to make the right choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jungle Hidden Animals</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jungle-hidden-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jungle-hidden-animals/</guid>
      <description>Mystical events took place in the safari park. All animals are gone. You will have to find them thanks to the magnifying glass that moves across the screen with the mouse. You will see images of animals that you need to find under the picture. There you will also find a hint that will be valid for a certain number of points Crazy Gamesd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Soldiers Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-soldiers-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-soldiers-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game, you will find puzzles on the theme of the Lego constructor so beloved by many. Choose any of the proposed pictures and start the puzzle. Arrange the pieces in the correct order to get the selected image. Parts can be turned over if necessary, if it is not possible to install them in the picture in their original position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planes Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/planes-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/planes-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>While playing Airplanes for Kids you will have to take a keyboard training course. You become the pilot of a small plane that goes on an air journey. Your flight is divided into many separate stages, each of which will have to make your way through armies of enemy airships and balloons. In order to destroy the enemy, you need to type on the keyboard the letters indicated on the balloon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant Kitty Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pregnant-kitty-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pregnant-kitty-spa/</guid>
      <description>The heroine of the game Giving birth to children in the hospital is going to become a mother any minute. Her child is already ready to be born, and you need to help him with this by performing an operation. On the screen you will see all the necessary tools that will be useful to you for medical intervention. Take the item that the arrow points to and perform the necessary actions, focusing on the prompts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock Man Jumper</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rock-man-jumper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rock-man-jumper/</guid>
      <description>Many people know the merry fellow Bart Simpson, who cannot imagine life without getting into another adventure. An interesting game for children shows that Bart has found a motorcycle somewhere and now wants to ride it. Will you ride with him? Help Bart complete the given distance and collect emoticons to get reward points. For each smiley, 100 points will be credited to the game account. Such interesting entertainment for children in the company of your favorite character will allow you to have a great time and cheer you up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa City Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/santa-city-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/santa-city-run/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is the best time of the year, because Santa comes to everyone with long-awaited gifts. And if you want to surprise the main wizard of the planet, prepare delicious cookies. But be very careful and attentive when choosing ingredients. Prepare a dessert and if Santa likes it, you will get the best present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scooby-Doo Scoobtober Trick or Treat</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/scooby-doo-scoobtober-trick-or-treat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/scooby-doo-scoobtober-trick-or-treat/</guid>
      <description>According to the plot of the game Baby Scooby Doo, famous hunters for paranormal phenomena are sent to another challenge. This time, Scooby is driving. Help the funny dog ​​get to his destination without falling into a trap and crashing his wonderful scooby car. Watch the road carefully and try to avoid obstacles on the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Flowers Hidden Objects</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/spring-flowers-hidden-objects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/spring-flowers-hidden-objects/</guid>
      <description>In this game you are waiting for a variety of flowers. A bouquet is displayed on the screen, as well as three different flowers. Try to determine which one is suitable for the bouquet. Just click on the correct flower, after which a new task will open. If you make a mistake, no problem. In this case, nothing will happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Jigsaw Puzzles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/summer-jigsaw-puzzles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/summer-jigsaw-puzzles/</guid>
      <description>Parrot Ducky and his friends fell in love with many after the release of the cartoon &amp;ldquo;Rio&amp;rdquo;. Collect puzzles with these cute birds. On the screen you will see the pieces that need to be turned over, giving them the correct position. The game consists of several levels, and on each level the number of details increases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Raccoon World</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-raccoon-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-raccoon-world/</guid>
      <description>An interesting children&amp;rsquo;s game 3 5 years old offers you to solve exciting puzzles related to determining the heaviest or, conversely, the lightest object from those offered in the conditions. Immediately after launch, the scales will appear on the screen, on the cups of which the things being compared are located. At the top of the screen, a task is displayed that needs to be completed by pointing the cursor at the correct item.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swampy game for children 4 years old</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/swampy-game-for-children-4-years-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/swampy-game-for-children-4-years-old/</guid>
      <description>Deep below the city, a cheerful alligator lives in a sewer. He wanted to take a bath, but here&amp;rsquo;s the problem - the pipe burst. You can help him make his dream come true. All that is needed is to dig a path underground from the lake to the pipe. In this case, you need to make sure that the water washes away the shampoo in the form of ducklings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Princess Dressing Room</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweet-princess-dressing-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweet-princess-dressing-room/</guid>
      <description>Kids Games Dress Up 2 offer you to come up with a new dress for a cute girl. First, choose its top, and then add a skirt and a variety of decorative elements. The color of any detail can be changed, so your flight of fancy can be unlimited. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to choose the right hairstyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Man And Red Bat</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tiny-man-and-red-bat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tiny-man-and-red-bat/</guid>
      <description>During the game for children 8 9 years old you will need to create delicious and beautiful ice cream. For this, everything you need is prepared here. You should start by choosing a waffle cup in which you want to place the ice cream chosen for children. Next comes the turn of fillers and decorative elements. There are a huge number of them here. You can use any topping, sprinkles, berries and other nice additions for a cold treat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Slides.io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/water-slides.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/water-slides.io/</guid>
      <description>Amusement park</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winx Club Magix Mayhem</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/winx-club-magix-mayhem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/winx-club-magix-mayhem/</guid>
      <description>Children&amp;rsquo;s Winx games online for free for girls is what all fans of cartoon fairies need. Here you are invited to create your own original fairy, using a huge range of different parts. You can choose a hairstyle, hair color, shape and color of eyes, lips. There are also a lot of stylish things here: blouses, skirts, dresses and other wardrobe items that will allow you to come up with a nice look.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
