<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zoo on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/zoo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zoo on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/zoo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Animals Candy Zoo</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/animals-candy-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/animals-candy-zoo/</guid>
      <description>In the animal zoo game, you become the director of one of the most popular natural parks in the world. Every day a huge number of visitors come here. Try to get them all to the enclosures of the animals they want to see as quickly as possible. Each satisfied customer will leave gold coins at the zoo, which you can use to develop your park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic Zoo</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/magic-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/magic-zoo/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you and the main character go to the zoo for an excursion. There you meet a nasty monkey who throws stones at visitors. Together with your ward on the screen, try to throw stones at the nasty monkey, correctly calculating the trajectory of the flight, the force with which you must launch the projectile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoo Panic</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zoo-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zoo-panic/</guid>
      <description>Evil hunters have caught Milton the penguin and sent him to one of the most famous zoos in the world. A funny character of the game does not want to live in captivity and invites you to escape. By controlling the movements of Milton, try to get out of the zoo, but be careful - guards are placed everywhere, and you will have to try not to catch their eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoo Pinball</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zoo-pinball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zoo-pinball/</guid>
      <description>An unknown disease has turned all the inhabitants of the zoo into bloodthirsty monsters, and now only you can save the visitors. Hurry up and go to the store where you can buy everything you need to fight monsters, and then start treating animals. Try to hit the monsters as many times as possible with a weapon that shoots the medicines they need.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
