<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>scary for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/scary-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in scary for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/scary-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Attack on the Mothership</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/attack-on-the-mothership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/attack-on-the-mothership/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to form your army of monsters by buying various warriors. When the squad is ready for battle, send it to the arena and watch how your wards fight. After each battle, warriors can be upgraded or even sold, earning some money and buying stronger fighters for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clown Nights</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/clown-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/clown-nights/</guid>
      <description>Today you have to fight with rivals in the ring. The fights are held according to the usual scheme: you need to hold out for 2 rounds, and if the Crazy Games is equal, the 3rd fight will reveal the winner. You are waiting for very noteworthy fights and a large selection of heroes and original super tricks. In general, everything is like in classic fighting games. True, before you start fighting, you need to go through the training mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama: Temple Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-temple-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-temple-escape/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you need to collect all the gems in the room and do it within a limited amount of time. As you progress through the levels, you will have to face many enemies, solve several puzzles and perform other unusual actions in order to find a way out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silent Insanity P.T.: Psychological Trauma</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/silent-insanity-p.t.-psychological-trauma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/silent-insanity-p.t.-psychological-trauma/</guid>
      <description>A strategy game in which you have to take over the world by sending zombie squads to attack. And you will have to fight with the same monsters that the computer or your friend will control if you invite him to play. Your goal is not to let the enemy into your territory and at the same time try to destroy the enemy&amp;rsquo;s forces and occupy his possessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slenderina Must Die The Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderina-must-die-the-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderina-must-die-the-forest/</guid>
      <description>This time you have to take part in the epic battles of the warriors of Ancient Greece. Control one of the fighters and take part in bloody duels against hordes of enemies and their bloodthirsty leaders. The game allows you to invite a friend to help and destroy enemies together, earning rewards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smiley Io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/smiley-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/smiley-io/</guid>
      <description>Boy Bobby, who is very fond of traveling, decided to make a halt in the forest and set up his tent there. The next morning, he saw that there were a lot of armed people around who were not very friendly. Help the boy to destroy the bandits and stay alive. To do this, you need to jump on the heads of the villains. Dexterity is required to win the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>While We Sleep Slenderina Is Here</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/while-we-sleep-slenderina-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/while-we-sleep-slenderina-is-here/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to do running, but not simple, but really dangerous. There are various obstacles to be overcome. Choose your hero from four available characters. They differ from each other both in appearance and characteristics. Then decide on the mode of passage and go to the start.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
