<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dress up for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/dress-up-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dress up for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/dress-up-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Audrey Pony Daycare</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/audrey-pony-daycare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/audrey-pony-daycare/</guid>
      <description>Help the heroes of this game to become even more stylish and attractive. You have to choose new clothes for them, decide on a hairstyle, hair color and makeup. A distinctive feature of the toy is that in it you can draw any item you like from their wardrobe, print it out on a printer, and then color it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbie And Ken Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/barbie-and-ken-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/barbie-and-ken-christmas/</guid>
      <description>This game has a wide range of possibilities. In it, you can not only dress up a boy and a girl, using a large number of various wardrobe items, but also seriously work on changing their appearance. Hairstyle, hair color, eye shape and skin tone can be corrected. In addition, a large number of accessories are available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bffs World Cup Face Paint</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bffs-world-cup-face-paint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bffs-world-cup-face-paint/</guid>
      <description>Girls dress up for two sisters</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Fashion Runaway</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/christmas-fashion-runaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/christmas-fashion-runaway/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is a holiday of pleasant surprises. In this game, you will need to prepare a couple of charming girls for the celebration by choosing elegant costumes, shoes and accessories for them. Wonderful caps, soft earmuffs and warm scarves can complete the look in a worthy way. Now the girls are fully prepared for the holiday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Couple Travel Selfie</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/couple-travel-selfie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/couple-travel-selfie/</guid>
      <description>Lorraine and Carla are invited to a friends Christmas party. The holiday is expected to be cheerful and noisy. Help the couple choose the right costumes. Combine dressy tops and trousers with warm outerwear, hats and shoes. When one of them is ready, move on to choosing an outfit for another character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Princess Mommy Real Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-mommy-real-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-mommy-real-makeover/</guid>
      <description>This game is exclusively for girls. Although, if the boys want to fantasize about their future wife and children, they may well play too. Immediately after launch, the loading screen pops up, but do not rush to press &amp;ldquo;play&amp;rdquo;, otherwise you will end up on another tab. As for the game itself, in it you have to dress up mom for a walk with a child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin And Selena Back Together</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/justin-and-selena-back-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/justin-and-selena-back-together/</guid>
      <description>During the game Dress Up for two, a boy and a girl, you will meet a couple in love. The guy and the girl decided to go on a picnic. You have to take care of their appearance, because even in nature you want to look attractive. Come up with great images for the heroes of this game!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miraculous School Kiss</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/miraculous-school-kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/miraculous-school-kiss/</guid>
      <description>You have to transform a couple of gangsters, very similar to the legendary Bonnie and Clyde. To do this, the game has everything you need: stylish elements of men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s clothing, elegant hats. Sparkling precious jewelry will add an additional charm to the girl. And, of course, you need to equip the heroes with appropriate weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Gymnastic Olympics</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-gymnastic-olympics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-gymnastic-olympics/</guid>
      <description>After launching the Dress Up 2 game, you will instantly find yourself in the underwater space where fairy-tale little mermaids live. With two of them - mother and daughter, you just have to meet. In this wonderful game for girls, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to come up with new and attractive images for the main characters. To do this, a wide range of different parts is provided here. You can change the hairstyle, choose a stylish bodice and ponytail, add a lot of matching jewelry, without which the image will be incomplete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Photo Shopping Dressup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-photo-shopping-dressup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-photo-shopping-dressup/</guid>
      <description>A dress up game for two will introduce you to an adorable couple who are about to go to a festive event. You also need to choose suitable outfits for the girl and the guy. To do this, use all the elements of the wardrobe of the game for girls presented on the screen. For the girl, do not forget to make a suitable make-up, this will be your first task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Team Blonde</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-team-blonde/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-team-blonde/</guid>
      <description>So, there are two girlfriends on the screen who adore the floral theme in everything: in hairstyles, in clothes, in the interior. Your task is to come up with new outfits for them. Do not forget that there is nothing scarier than the same or similar costumes on your best friends. Try to make each one unique. It&amp;rsquo;s not that difficult, given the rich selection of clothing and jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
