<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Runners for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/runners-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Runners for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/runners-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dino Meat Hunt New Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-meat-hunt-new-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-meat-hunt-new-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Runner game for two is a test of strength and endurance in a long-distance race. You can even invite a friend and compete with him, which of you is faster. Well, you can set your personal records in a single race. But be extremely careful - all sorts of obstacles and dangers await you along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fireboy &amp; Watergirl 3 In The Ice Temple</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fireboy--watergirl-3-in-the-ice-temple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fireboy--watergirl-3-in-the-ice-temple/</guid>
      <description>All that is required of you in this game is to overcome a certain distance with the main character in the minimum amount of time. In this case, it is desirable to collect as many coins as possible and not fall into the abyss. During the movement, do not be lazy to collect various useful things, ranging from magical shields to a talisman that turns the heroine invisible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fireboy &amp; Watergirl In The Light Temple</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fireboy--watergirl-in-the-light-temple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fireboy--watergirl-in-the-light-temple/</guid>
      <description>Controlling the character, you need to go through a little training before you boldly rush towards the test. Learn to jump, run fast and, most importantly, have time to collect glowing balls. And with the points earned and collected bonuses, you can visit the store, where it will be possible to purchase armor for the hero and replenish his health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Race 3d 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/run-race-3d-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/run-race-3d-2/</guid>
      <description>A fun, retro-styled game in which you can run both in solo mode and compete with an opponent. Your character must rush forward, overcoming obstacles and collecting coins. In addition, he can move along the ceiling, and sometimes the only way to avoid collisions or falling into the abyss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Mission 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-mission-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-mission-2/</guid>
      <description>You can’t run away from zombies if you don’t have special agility and dexterity. And you also need to be able to jump over obstacles and masterfully own a baseball bat. Using the arrow keys to control and the spacebar, take the character of the game along the road, dotted with obstacles and numerous bloodthirsty zombies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
