<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>archers on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/archers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in archers on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/archers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game archer master</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-archer-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-archer-master/</guid>
      <description>You will need the Firefox browser to run this game. But it&amp;rsquo;s worth it, because the game immerses the user in the world of Medieval Japan, where you will be in the role of an archery master. But you have to start with a simple warrior. First-person view. The bottom line is that you need to hit the target in the allotted time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Archer The Lord of the Rings</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-archer-the-lord-of-the-rings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-archer-the-lord-of-the-rings/</guid>
      <description>All fans of the film &amp;ldquo;The Hobbit&amp;rdquo; have a happy day today! Get ready to fight in a fit of joy, because you are waiting for a game based on the already mentioned film. The user will have to choose one of the heroes and start a merciless shooting of orcs. Everything is relatively simple: you choose the angle of fire, then you adjust the tension of the bowstring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween archer game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-archer-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-archer-game/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a maniac and want to go out and have some fun, then you can&amp;rsquo;t imagine a better occasion than Halloween. After all, everyone here looks unusual and ominous. But relax: you won&amp;rsquo;t kill anyone in this game. By the way, the view from the first person. So, you have to shoot from the bow at the magic lights on the night of the already mentioned holiday. It takes place in a cemetery.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
