<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Max Steel on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/max-steel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Max Steel on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/max-steel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Max Steel - city defense</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-max-steel---city-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-max-steel---city-defense/</guid>
      <description>The ability to generate energy gives a sixteen-year-old boy incredible strengths and abilities. Max will become a member of the organization that his late father created, and will fight the villains. This guy will have to go through many incredible adventures, fight opponents and free the planet from alien invaders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max Steel game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/max-steel-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/max-steel-game/</guid>
      <description>Max Steel is an exciting shooting game for boys based on the popular animated series. The protagonist is half alien, half teenager with a special turbo energy. This guy is incredibly fast, brave, strong. And he also has a special suit that protects the hero during battles with aliens. And Max has to deal with them very often. For example, it was today that the evil Dred sent his troops to attack the N-TEK base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max Steel game - N-tech invasion</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/max-steel-game---n-tech-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/max-steel-game---n-tech-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Max Steel is sent on another mission. You need to destroy the enemy detachment of robots that captured a peaceful spaceship. Before the start of the mission, you can choose the color of armor and ammunition for the guy. Max will have a powerful laser gun in his arsenal, with which he will fight enemies, overcoming dangerous traps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max Steel game - steel defense</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/max-steel-game---steel-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/max-steel-game---steel-defense/</guid>
      <description>The aliens have reached Max Steel&amp;rsquo;s secret base. It’s quite difficult for a guy to keep the defense, because the onslaught of the enemy is very serious. Move from cover to cover and shoot at the enemy at the same time. At each level, you need to eliminate a certain number of enemies in order to proceed to the next stage of the operation. Try to do it quickly, not missing the opportunity to earn a bonus for speed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
