<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Educational for children on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/educational-for-children/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Educational for children on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/educational-for-children/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Didi &amp; Friends Connect the Dots</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/didi--friends-connect-the-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/didi--friends-connect-the-dots/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will be asked to collect animals from scattered pieces. Such a fun puzzle will bring a lot of positive. Just place the elements in the right places based on the existing template and get images of cute animals like sheep, lion and more. You can repeat if you want!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Jigsaw 1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-jigsaw-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-jigsaw-1/</guid>
      <description>Children&amp;rsquo;s educational game invites you to the ski track. It is necessary to help the skier make the longest possible jump. To do this, you need to correctly solve several examples. Before starting the game, choose which mathematical operation you like best: addition, subtraction, multiplication or division.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Math</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/funny-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/funny-math/</guid>
      <description>The presented educational games for children aged 8-9 allow not only to have a great time, but also to practice mathematical skills. Here you will find yourself on a pirate island, where you need to move around the locations and collect various items. In addition, you need to solve the given example and find the numbers of the answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teddy Bear Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/teddy-bear-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/teddy-bear-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Children&amp;rsquo;s educational game is aimed at training mathematical thinking. You need to play it together, each participant controls an alien on a flying saucer. A mathematical example is displayed on the screen, and you need to fly to the answer number as quickly as possible, ahead of your opponent. Fuel is limited!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Jigsaw Time</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/winter-jigsaw-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/winter-jigsaw-time/</guid>
      <description>Educational for children</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
