<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About space on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/about-space/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About space on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/about-space/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Air Force Shooter Sky Strike</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/air-force-shooter-sky-strike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/air-force-shooter-sky-strike/</guid>
      <description>Galaxy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galactic Cop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/galactic-cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/galactic-cop/</guid>
      <description>In the game Astronauts you have to control two brothers who decided to go into space to find new planets and make the most accurate star map. Who would have thought that terrible dangers await them, and the guys will have to make a lot of joint efforts to overcome obstacles. The heroes cannot cope together, they need a coordinator. The game invites you to help the brave astronauts in their difficult journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interstellar Travel</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/interstellar-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/interstellar-travel/</guid>
      <description>On the way of your spaceship come across asteroids of different sizes. They rush towards them with great speed and strive to break through the skin of the ship. Try to fly between them without colliding. Prevent damage to the skin of your ship and its complete depressurization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Astro Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/run-astro-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/run-astro-run/</guid>
      <description>Before you is a unique puzzle game in which you have to find the path by which the rocket can get to the space station. You will have to overcome many obstacles and avoid traps. Navigate the ship through the universe, making turns at small intermediate stops. In case of an error, you will fly off the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slenderman Must Die Dead Space</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-must-die-dead-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-must-die-dead-space/</guid>
      <description>The main goal of this game is to crush the enemy by participating in intergalactic battles. At your disposal there is a high-speed space fighter equipped with different types of firearms. In addition to the enemy, there are a large number of asteroids in space, collisions with which should be avoided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Lab Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/space-lab-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/space-lab-survival/</guid>
      <description>Space Pro is an exciting 3D flying game. A robotic alien race is preparing to invade Earth. But the earthlings have an infiltrator who was landed behind enemy lines and now has information vital to preparing the defense of the planet. In an online game about space, you have to help him break through enemy forces, shooting them and dodging enemy projectiles. A dynamic space game sets you one task - to break through to the teleport and get to Earth as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
