<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unity 3d on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/unity-3d/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unity 3d on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/unity-3d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Basketball 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/basketball-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/basketball-2018/</guid>
      <description>Sports fans will definitely enjoy this wonderful game. She invites you to take part in basketball competitions. Choose the teams that will take the field. Then all that remains is to competently manage the members of your team and try to score as many goals as possible in the opponent&amp;rsquo;s basket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basketball Arcade</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/basketball-arcade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/basketball-arcade/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to control a funny character who is going to fight enemies somewhere in space. Navigate fantastic locations, attack enemies on your way and collect coins. The money will be useful to you in the future in order to purchase some kind of improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Brofors Unity 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-brofors-unity-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-brofors-unity-3d/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to complete very important missions. The task is to move around the locations and destroy enemies by shooting them from the available weapons. It is also necessary to find hostages held in cages and free them. Try not to fall into the abyss and not succumb to the attacks of enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Hungry Goliath Unity 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-hungry-goliath-unity-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-hungry-goliath-unity-3d/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will control a giant who is constantly running forward. You need to help him jump over obstacles in time or crawl under them, trying not to hurt anything. A single collision will immediately lead to a loss. Do not forget to collect valuable crystals that are scattered everywhere here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Mazinger z Unity 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-mazinger-z-unity-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-mazinger-z-unity-3d/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will go straight to the war. Allies are in dire need of help. Your task is to complete various tasks and eventually lead your army to victory. You will need to deftly move through the streets, which are shot through by enemies, attacking opponents yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama: Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-forest/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to control astronauts who travel high above the Earth. They need to go through the platforms located in space. Some of them can easily withstand the weight of a person, but some can fail, which will certainly lead to a loss. You have to go from start to finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mine Clone 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mine-clone-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mine-clone-3/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will enter a fantasy world. It is necessary to clear the possessions that you have inherited from evil enemies. Move around the locations, clearing your way and destroying enemies that come across. Try not to succumb to their blows, because otherwise you can lose all your health points and quickly lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superman Puzzle Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/superman-puzzle-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/superman-puzzle-challenge/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to play on behalf of superman. The task is to fly around the city, collecting bonus items. From time to time you will meet enemies, and you need to fight them, because Superman was created for this. The top of the screen displays all the important information that can help you in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
