<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mickey Mouse on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/mickey-mouse/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mickey Mouse on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/mickey-mouse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Goofy Sleepwalkin Shenanigans</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/goofy-sleepwalkin-shenanigans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/goofy-sleepwalkin-shenanigans/</guid>
      <description>Assemble a puzzle that depicts Disney cartoon characters - Minnie Mouse, Daisy Duck and Pluto, located near the fireplace. The game has three difficulty levels. Depending on the selected conditions, the puzzle will include 9, 25 or 49 pieces. The assembly process is quite simple, even the smallest fans of collecting colorful images can easily cope with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mickey &amp; Minnie - Parisian Park Puzzler</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mickey--minnie---parisian-park-puzzler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mickey--minnie---parisian-park-puzzler/</guid>
      <description>Mickey Mouse and his girlfriend Mini went for a walk in the woods. It is their portrait on a walk that you need to collect from separate fragments. At the bottom of the screen you can see a red button. Click on it to show one of the parts of the image. Use your mouse to place it where you want it. It will not be difficult to do this, since you will always have a translucent original image in front of you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mickey Mouse Bump In The Night</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mickey-mouse-bump-in-the-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mickey-mouse-bump-in-the-night/</guid>
      <description>During the game Mickey Mouse Adventure you have to go along with the hero of the Disney cartoon on an exciting journey. He needs to save his friends kidnapped by an evil witch. Be extremely careful and as attentive as possible, because there will be various dangers on the way. Use arrow keys to control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mickey Mouse Football Game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mickey-mouse-football-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mickey-mouse-football-game/</guid>
      <description>A simple but very interesting game in which you&amp;rsquo;ll have to help Mickey Mouse build a football team and try to win the championship. Use the mouse to control the players. Move the cursor over the character, hold down the left key and draw a path for him to move along. Crazy Games as many goals as possible for the opposing team and become the champion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
