<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cleaning on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/cleaning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cleaning on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/cleaning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Baby Doll House Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-doll-house-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-doll-house-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>There is an incredible mess in this children&amp;rsquo;s room. Your task is to put the toys in their places, put the bedding in the closet, put all the necessary items in their places, and throw out the trash. To complete the task, use the mouse and try to cope within the time allotted in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach House Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/beach-house-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/beach-house-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>The main task of this game is to perfectly clean the hotel room. Of course, you need to cope in a short time, because new guests will drop in here soon. So, getting started, you need to carefully examine the room, find special containers, lockers, shelves where to put things, and throw out the garbage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bffs College Dorm</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bffs-college-dorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bffs-college-dorm/</guid>
      <description>An emo girl lives in this room, and the room is fully consistent with the aesthetic preferences of the hostess. But the trouble is, the girl can not stand keeping order. You can help her clean up and be an example of how to keep clean. Collect all the toys, and put things in their places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirty Palace</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dirty-palace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dirty-palace/</guid>
      <description>According to the terms of the game Cleaning the house without time, you have to clean up the children&amp;rsquo;s room. This is a room that has to be cleaned more often than others. Those who have a little sister or brother understand what it is, because everyone knows how much children love to play, but do not clean up after themselves after the game. However, cleanliness still needs to be maintained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dotted Girl Family Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dotted-girl-family-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dotted-girl-family-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is coming soon, and in order to properly welcome Santa, the house must be sparkling clean. Help the two sisters get ready for the holiday. It will be necessary to arrange beautifully wrapped gifts under the tree, and throw everything unnecessary into the wastebasket. Next up is the bedroom and kitchen. There&amp;rsquo;s plenty of work to do here, so get to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellie New Year Room Deco</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-new-year-room-deco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-new-year-room-deco/</guid>
      <description>Today the beauty Barbie is going to clean up her room. But can&amp;rsquo;t decide where to start. The top of the screen will show the items that need to be found and placed in their places first. Try to find them in the picture within the time allotted in the game. Use your mouse for this and be careful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fairy House Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fairy-house-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fairy-house-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Game Cleaning is extremely simple. The task is to put things in order in the brother&amp;rsquo;s room, where he made a real mayhem. He wanted to play, and now you need to clean it all up. Put toys and clothes in their places, hang pictures and throw out the garbage. To successfully cope with the task, you will have to rely only on your own strength. But cleaning cannot last forever, so the game has a time limit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Decoration</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/garden-decoration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/garden-decoration/</guid>
      <description>With the help of the game Cleaner you will be able to get acquainted with the difficult work of a maid in a huge house, in which it is simply impossible to do without a good housekeeper. Your duties will include cleaning the premises, caring for flowers, folding the bed, cleaning the furniture and much more. Here you can not be distracted for a minute, there is a lot of work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girls Fix It: Audrey Spring Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/girls-fix-it-audrey-spring-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/girls-fix-it-audrey-spring-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>During the Barbie Cleaning game you have to take care of the appearance of the beauty. She loves fun parties and just invited guests today. Choose a beautiful outfit for the girl using items from the existing wardrobe, and then help her clean up the house. Put everything in its place, set the table and get ready to meet friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girly House Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/girly-house-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/girly-house-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>The game House Cleaning puts you in front of a rather difficult task. We urgently need to put things in order in the room after gatherings with girlfriends. For many girls, these games will be a great simulator, with which it is easy to learn how to quickly and efficiently clean up. Agree, every girl should have household chores. After all, in the future no one will tell you, you will have to do everything yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goldie Princess Laundry Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldie-princess-laundry-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldie-princess-laundry-day/</guid>
      <description>In this game you can clean up the laundry room. It is necessary to make sure that there is perfect cleanliness here by the time visitors arrive. Start cleaning from the floor, see how many objects are lying around. Collect everything and put it in its place: hangers - on the shelf, bottles of cleaning products - in the closet, send the garbage to the trash can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goldie Princess Wardrobe Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldie-princess-wardrobe-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldie-princess-wardrobe-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Today you will participate in the ironing championship. Get down to business quickly, because the more things you iron, the more money you will earn. You can use them to buy new devices to make your work more efficient. Act quickly and do not get distracted, because the time in the game is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highschool Girls House Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/highschool-girls-house-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/highschool-girls-house-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Sophia&amp;rsquo;s House Cleaning game invites you to clean up the room after the Halloween celebration. Garbage must be thrown into the bin, and the lying objects should be put back where they were before. The top right corner shows you how many things still need to be removed. You can use the hint, but hurry, time is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Castle Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-castle-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-castle-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Your task in this game is to help three girls clean their apartment before the New Year holidays. It will be quite difficult for them to do this alone, and constant monitoring is needed. Collect the trash together, then take care of the scattered things and mop the floor. Agree, to celebrate the New Year in a clean apartment is doubly pleasant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids House Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kids-house-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kids-house-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Before the New Year holidays, even such an unpleasant thing as cleaning can cheer you up. It is best to start from the living room, where the beautiful Christmas tree stands, and prepare it for receiving guests. A little later, you will also have to decorate all the gifts beautifully. It will not be superfluous to remove unnecessary things from the room that only interfere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marie Kondo Clean Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/marie-kondo-clean-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/marie-kondo-clean-up/</guid>
      <description>Every home needs to be cleaned from time to time. It&amp;rsquo;s time to clean up this kitchen. It takes a little bit of effort and patience. You need to collect all the garbage: bottles, bags, scraps and throw them away. Wash the dishes and put all the items in their places. And hurry up, time is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/restaurant-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/restaurant-makeover/</guid>
      <description>We all like to spend time in an ice cream parlor because it is both fun and delicious. But few people know that after the closure of the institution, its staff is left with a huge amount of work: they need to remove the garbage, and wipe the tables, and put the chairs in their places. This is exactly what you have to do today in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riley Bathroom Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/riley-bathroom-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/riley-bathroom-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>The room is a terrible mess, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to start cleaning. Your task in this game is to restore order as quickly and efficiently as possible. Look at what things do not lie in their places, put them on the shelves, throw out all the garbage, vacuum, wipe the dust. Make sure that this room is clean, comfortable and beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
