<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeeps on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/jeeps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jeeps on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/jeeps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3D Monster Truck SkyRoads</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/3d-monster-truck-skyroads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/3d-monster-truck-skyroads/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to drive a monster truck. This machine is capable of destroying everything in its path. There are 16 tracks in total. They are divided into four levels of difficulty: from easy to extreme. Between races, you can pump your &amp;ldquo;monster&amp;rdquo;. Replace wheels, engine, suspension and nitro boost system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4x4 Off Roading</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/4x4-off-roading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/4x4-off-roading/</guid>
      <description>Parking is a dangerous business, let alone a huge jeep capable of smashing a nearby car to smithereens. However, it is you who needs to find a parking place for him, carefully park the car and try to keep your and other people&amp;rsquo;s cars safe and sound. Take your time - the game does not limit you in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4x4 Offroader</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/4x4-offroader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/4x4-offroader/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will have to drive through the desert. On the road there are continuous steep hills, ravines and huge boulders blocking the path. Your jeep is capable of overcoming all of these obstacles, but you will need precise and accurate driving. Try to mega carefully climb up the hill and go down without turning over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Army Cargo Truck Drive</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/army-cargo-truck-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/army-cargo-truck-drive/</guid>
      <description>A very exciting type of racing on a car with big wheels. As you know, this type of technology makes it possible not to worry too much about the quality of the roadway. The passability of the jeep is so great that it allows you to easily overcome almost any obstacles, and do not pay attention to small potholes in the road at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bus Simulator: City Driving</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bus-simulator-city-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bus-simulator-city-driving/</guid>
      <description>This bus has huge wheels. They are able to overcome any obstacles. You will have to drive through a car dump, cross a ravine and climb a high mountain. But you have to move carefully. Use arrow keys to control. Try to get to the finish line without crashing the bus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirt Car Race Offroad</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dirt-car-race-offroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dirt-car-race-offroad/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the world of rally crosses! These competitions are held in the most remote and harsh corners of our planet. Mud, desert sands and snowy roads are ideal for such races. Before each stage, you need to decide on the class of the car. You can drive all-wheel drive cars, SUVs and even trucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Offroad Cars 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-offroad-cars-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-offroad-cars-2/</guid>
      <description>You have to drive an SUV that moves along quite dangerous jungle roads. It so happened that a whole army of enemy soldiers is operating on them, and you need to deal with them. Huge spiked wheels and a saw on the bumper of your car will allow you to easily complete the task. The main thing is not to slow down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster 4x4</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-4x4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-4x4/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to drive a jeep over various obstacles until your gas tank runs out of fuel. Perform tricks in the air and collect bonuses that will help you earn even more coins. Use the money you receive to buy upgrades for your jeep. The main thing - try not to roll over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offroad Dirt Racing 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/offroad-dirt-racing-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/offroad-dirt-racing-3d/</guid>
      <description>Once Ben-10 decided to conquer the off-road in his huge jeep. He chose difficult routes, with many steep climbs and dangerous descents. In some areas, you will have to use a useful feature of any good SUV - downshifting. In the case of a difficult ascent to the slope, you should press the spacebar, and the jeep will be able to climb to the very top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Kamaz Truck Driver</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-kamaz-truck-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-kamaz-truck-driver/</guid>
      <description>There are pros and cons to owning a Jeep. It looks so cool on the road - just a feast for the eyes. But the dimensions of the car cause some kind of problem. Parking can be a real challenge for you, especially when there are almost no places left around. Finding a free spot in the parking lot is not an easy task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sahara Racer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sahara-racer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sahara-racer/</guid>
      <description>A unique and very interesting game that combines racing and logic quiz. When driving along the highway, you are offered questions, the answers to which can be found on the traffic signs located along the road. If you turn the right way, you earn points, and if you make a mistake, anything can happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Stunts 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ultimate-stunts-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ultimate-stunts-3d/</guid>
      <description>An excellent arcade game for those who like to park using various types of cars to drive. This time you will be able to show your skills in driving a jeep with a trailer. Pay attention to the inscriptions that are present on the signs indicating the parking place. It is on the place indicated by the arrow that you need to put the car.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
