<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mineblocks on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/mineblocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mineblocks on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/mineblocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build Craft</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/build-craft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/build-craft/</guid>
      <description>The boundless world, familiar to millions of users from classic Minecraft, is waiting for you this time as well. The texture rendering is amazing. As well as the smoothness of the movement of the character (although there is still the same view from the first person) and even the voice acting. The biggest problem is to deal with the control keys. And it is also desirable to increase the game window to full screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merge Jewels</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/merge-jewels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/merge-jewels/</guid>
      <description>The next version of Minecraft awaits gamers after downloading. View, as always, from the first person. The character appears in the world already with a certain set of items. Management is standard. It is better to immediately switch to full screen mode (right mouse button and click on full screen). You can&amp;rsquo;t get killed here. You need to complete the tasks that the game itself throws up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecaves 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecaves-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecaves-2/</guid>
      <description>Do you love Minecraft, but the computer can&amp;rsquo;t handle 3D graphics? No problem! You can do what you love while playing Mine Blocks 2d. Except for the fact that the action takes place in two-dimensional space, there are few differences. The bottom line is the same extraction of materials, the manufacture of tools, and so on. You can now see mineral deposits immediately, as well as your character, by the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Craft</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mini-craft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mini-craft/</guid>
      <description>Before you start playing, pay attention to the text under the &amp;ldquo;Play&amp;rdquo; button. It contains operating instructions. There are quite a few buttons involved. The game itself is 2D. The character is a little man who went on a dangerous journey. On the way he meets monsters from the classic Minecraft. You can either lure them into a trap or kill them with arrows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Craft 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/world-craft-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/world-craft-2/</guid>
      <description>Mainblocks 2 is based on the Minecraft sandbox, which is popular among gamers all over the world. That&amp;rsquo;s just to build and extract resources in it will have very little. As many as you need to protect your own base from the penetration of all sorts of malicious characters: bugs, spiders, skeletons and other creatures known to you from the original Minecraft. First you need to pave the way. This is where the enemies will go, so make more turns to somehow slow down their progress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
