<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Battle for Manhattan for boys</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-battle-for-manhattan-for-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-battle-for-manhattan-for-boys/</guid>
      <description>The game is ideal for fans of dynamic adventures and Lego constructor. Brave mutant turtles are depicted here as figurines from a well-known designer. Your task is to control each of the heroes and fight the forces of evil. Use various combat tricks and collect bonuses, they will help you win any battle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage mutant ninja turtles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles/</guid>
      <description>Teenage mutant ninja turtles game invites you to help Michelangelo in the fight against monster robots. They are always trying to escape from their &amp;ldquo;pen&amp;rdquo;, but you need to act as quickly as possible and stop them. You will need the arrow keys for this. Press them in the correct order and then the escaped characters of the arcade game will be stopped. Be careful, because those mutant monsters that break free will certainly attack Michelangelo and try to bite him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - all on the boards</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles---all-on-the-boards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles---all-on-the-boards/</guid>
      <description>The turtle brothers decided to have some fun and went to the skateboarding area. But even here they were not allowed to rest in peace: mutant teenagers were attacked by warriors from the Nogi clan. While driving a skateboard, help one of the heroes of the game repulse the attacks of the attackers, and don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect all the prize points for performing tricks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - collect and win</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles---collect-and-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles---collect-and-win/</guid>
      <description>Nightmare Krang managed to steal a mutagen from a secret laboratory, which they plan to use to create an army of mutants. According to their insidious plan, it should capture the entire planet. Help one of the game&amp;rsquo;s characters defeat the guards, consisting of android robots, collect all the containers with a dangerous chemical and break the evil plans of the aliens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Skaters for Boys</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles---skaters-for-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles---skaters-for-boys/</guid>
      <description>Talented ninja turtles are trying to demonstrate their excellent physical shape. This time their choice fell on skateboards. Click on one of the famous four mutants and start an exciting competition on a skateboard. And you don’t need to limit yourself, on the contrary, any, the most incredible tricks, are encouraged in every possible way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-2/</guid>
      <description>Excellent game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2 invites you to go on a journey in the company of your favorite cartoon characters. Choose any mutant superhero from the famous four. It could be Donatello, Raphael, Leonardo or Michelangelo. Each of the ninja turtles has special characteristics, which you can get acquainted with by hovering over the selected hero. After the most interesting begins - the passage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-3d/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 3D, you can have a great time in the company of characters from the well-known animated series about mutant superheroes. Turtles have remarkable strength and are excellent at martial arts. You have to take part in an exciting battle with them! Think about who you will play: Donatello, Raphael, Michelangelo or Leonardo. Choose the hero you like and start the battle. Your ninja turtle needs to deal with opponents using different types of attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-adventure/</guid>
      <description>After starting the Ninja Turtles adventure game, you will control Raphael, who is forced to face a huge number of enemies. Move around the location using the arrow buttons and use the spacebar to attack. You have only two minutes to complete the walker, and during this time you need to try to destroy as many opponents as possible. If you suddenly see a piece of pizza somewhere, feel free to grab it, because it will give you one game life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Super Fight 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-super-fight-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-super-fight-3/</guid>
      <description>During the game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Super Brawl 3, the famous crime fighter and friend of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, Casey Jones, is sent to patrol the streets of New York. In one of the districts of the metropolis, he meets with a ninja from the Nogi clan. Help Casey deal with a gang of criminals and protect the city&amp;rsquo;s residents from insidious villains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Fight in 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-fight-in-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-fight-in-3d/</guid>
      <description>The young Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles have become skilled enough to take the final exam before being initiated into a ninjutsu master. Choose one of the four green warriors and go with him to the first stage of the test. Help your character win all the battles of the exam and get the title of a true master.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Fights and Dark Horizon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-fights-and-dark-horizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-fights-and-dark-horizon/</guid>
      <description>The Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles fell into an unknown sewer tunnel that led them to old pipes that distill streams of a very strange liquid. This poisonous essence turned animals into terrible monsters. Together with four brave men, go to the deep catacombs and find out where this mutagen stream flows from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Robot Fights</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-robot-fights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-robot-fights/</guid>
      <description>Carefree Michelangelo made his way to the laboratory of his brother Raphael and found an apparatus with a large red button and the inscription &amp;ldquo;Do not press&amp;rdquo;. Naturally, Mikey pressed the button first and was instantly transported to the training ground created by his brother. Help the curious ninja pass all the tests and get back to the turtles&amp;rsquo; house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ninja Turtle Racing Game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ninja-turtle-racing-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ninja-turtle-racing-game/</guid>
      <description>After starting the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle Racing game, you will understand that mutant superheroes are not only perfect in martial arts, but also skateboard very well. Choose the character you will play as. It can be any of the turtles: Michelangelo, Raphael, Donatello, Leonardo. Control the hero moving along the race track and hitting jumps on the way. This will allow you to do some cool tricks, but you will need to quickly press exactly the buttons that appear on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skateboarding Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/skateboarding-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/skateboarding-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles/</guid>
      <description>The fascinating plot of the game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles on a skateboard will appeal to all fans of these funny cartoon characters. In order to quickly deal with all the villains of the Nogi clan, they decided to race around the city on skateboards and punish the bandits. You should help the heroes to destroy the enemy, and during the chase, do not forget to perform tricks by pressing certain keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Threat game on the streets of Manhattan</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/threat-game-on-the-streets-of-manhattan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/threat-game-on-the-streets-of-manhattan/</guid>
      <description>The Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles discovered Shredder&amp;rsquo;s secret base, where the villain tried to create an army of robotic warriors and, with their help, first capture New York, and then the entire planet. Help the heroes of this wonderful toy to destroy as many Purple Dragon gang warriors as possible and fight Shredder himself in a deadly battle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
