<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About World War II on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/about-world-war-ii/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About World War II on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/about-world-war-ii/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alien Infestation FPS</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/alien-infestation-fps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/alien-infestation-fps/</guid>
      <description>During the game about World War 3, you will control one of the special forces soldiers participating in the global confrontation between the armies of the planet. Cities on all continents are to be liberated. At the first level, you are thrown into one of the Arab countries. The city was captured by terrorists, and the task to be completed is to destroy the bandits and save the hostages. A game about World War 3 gives you the opportunity to choose different types of weapons and even use equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sniper Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sniper-reloaded/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sniper-reloaded/</guid>
      <description>The World War II Sniper game gives you the opportunity to feel like an elusive shooter, who is fluent in the art of accurately hitting targets. You will perform various tasks on enemy territory in the midst of World War II. You have to destroy objects at long distances with a sniper rifle with a telescopic sight. Almost all games about World War II snipers involve not only the elimination of the enemy, but also the ability to choose cover and disguise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Battle: War Commander</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-battle-war-commander/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-battle-war-commander/</guid>
      <description>Your task in this game is to protect the territory from enemies by all available means. Arrange your units so as not to let the enemy break through the defense. As you accumulate points awarded for each successful operation, you can purchase additional weapons and use them to strengthen your positions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Off</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-off/</guid>
      <description>All you have to do in this game is to control a recruit who finds himself in a war zone. Using the mouse and keyboard, you can move to any side of the screen, jump onto the platforms and go down. The E button performs all active actions: repairing items, opening gates, searching in the bushes, collecting things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank War Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-war-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-war-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Quite a dynamic game in which you have to destroy enemy tanks, aircraft and infantry units. You control an armored vehicle, and in a particularly difficult situation, you have the opportunity to call for air support. To accomplish the task, you can use various weapons, up to the atomic bomb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanks Battlefield</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-battlefield/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-battlefield/</guid>
      <description>The presence of tanks on the battlefield is of great importance, and you can see for yourself by driving one of these armored vehicles. Constantly move ahead of the infantry, clearing the way for it, which will allow you to avoid unnecessary losses and capture a large territory. Improving your material part, you will be able to destroy the most fortified points of the enemy defense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tankwars io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tankwars-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tankwars-io/</guid>
      <description>You have to fight with a large Nazi army, having only one tank at your disposal. So that you can fight on equal terms with the enemy, after each battle there is an opportunity to improve the combat characteristics of your combat vehicle. First of all, destroy grenade launchers - they pose the most serious danger to tank armor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WarBrokers.io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/warbrokers.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/warbrokers.io/</guid>
      <description>Game action takes place during the German occupation. Your task is to liberate the territories captured by the Nazis. By driving a tank and completing various combat and tactical tasks during the game, you will receive rewards. In a special workshop, you can upgrade your tank, increasing its power, rate of fire, and ammo capacity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
