<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For children 7 years old on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-7-years-old/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For children 7 years old on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-7-years-old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blocks Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/blocks-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/blocks-battle/</guid>
      <description>Developing for children from 7 years old</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Burst</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-burst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-burst/</guid>
      <description>One of the simplest, and at the same time the best ball games. Multi-colored clusters hang from the &amp;ldquo;ceiling&amp;rdquo; of the game, and you have to knock out groups of balls of the same color from this mass. Each ball knocked out brings you 10 points, and the more points you Crazy Games, the higher your position in the ranking of players will be. No timer, no levels - play as much as you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gun Masters</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gun-masters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gun-masters/</guid>
      <description>Kids games for boys 7 years old will make you feel like a real toy picker. This game consists of several levels, and on each of them you will see the assembly scheme, as well as various parts from which the toy should eventually turn out. Please note that there may be extra parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Car Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-car-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-car-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Interesting and useful logic games for children 7 years old will allow you to have a great time solving puzzles. In them, you need to continue a series of several items, choosing one suitable from four options. The game has two modes: easy and hard. On a simple one, you can make an infinite number of mistakes, but on a complex one, you can only make a mistake twice in all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line Puzzle Artist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/line-puzzle-artist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/line-puzzle-artist/</guid>
      <description>Mind games for children 7 years old will make you rack your brains over puzzles, the conditions of which are laid out against the background of the starry sky. Here you will need to unravel the shape so that none of its lines intersect the others. With each figure, the task will become more difficult, more and more lines will be used in the composition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Matador</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/math-matador/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/math-matador/</guid>
      <description>The game allows you to solve 26 tasks on 6 different maps. But to do this will not be easy at all, you will need knowledge of the basics of mathematics and the ability to think logically. The sum of the numbers appears on the screen, for example, 3+9. From the numbers scattered around the playing field, you must choose the one that corresponds to the final amount by clicking on the squares with the desired values ​​one by one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Casual Life Dressup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-casual-life-dressup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-casual-life-dressup/</guid>
      <description>During an incredibly exciting game for children 7 years old for girls, you will need to create original sand pictures. First, choose an image template and create its outline. Then it remains only to use the glue and pour the sand of the desired color on the greased place. Insert the finished picture into the frame!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
