<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terraria on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/terraria/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Terraria on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/terraria/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Terraria online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-terraria-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-terraria-online/</guid>
      <description>The authors of this game send you on an exciting journey through the underground labyrinths of the magical land of Terraria. Try to search the location where you find yourself and find hidden treasures. But be careful, in addition to nightmarish computer-controlled monsters, there will be other players acting online and seeking to destroy you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraria 3D game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/terraria-3d-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/terraria-3d-game/</guid>
      <description>Terraria 3D game invites you to take part in an exciting adventure on a deserted island. Try to organize your life and protect yourself from the bloodthirsty natives using your knowledge and ingenuity. Try to explore the entire island as quickly as possible and find items that will help you survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraria game on a desert island</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/terraria-game-on-a-desert-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/terraria-game-on-a-desert-island/</guid>
      <description>The old pirate decided to go on an honorable vacation, but on his last voyage he was shipwrecked near the famous treasure island. Help the sea wolf to search a piece of land and find all the chests of gold that were hidden by his bloodthirsty comrades. Try to do everything as quickly as possible, and then the pirate will give you one of the found gold coins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timed Terraria game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/timed-terraria-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/timed-terraria-game/</guid>
      <description>The hero of this game accidentally discovered an old map showing the place where an old pirate buried a huge treasure. He asks you to go on a journey with him. Help the treasure hunter get to the chest with gold bars as quickly as possible. By controlling the movements of your partner, try to dig an underground passage to the pirate&amp;rsquo;s huge treasure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
