<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Educational on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/educational/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Educational on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/educational/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Guess What</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</guid>
      <description>Educational games for schoolchildren of the 2nd grade will allow you to train your mathematical and logical skills. The challenge is to correctly complete the sequences. On the screen you will see shells with numbers, and you need to put another shell at the end of the chain, which will fit perfectly here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Egg Search</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-egg-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-egg-search/</guid>
      <description>This wonderful game perfectly develops memory and ingenuity. On the screen are reversed cards hiding images of cute animals. You need to sequentially open the pictures, trying to find pairs that match each other in meaning. If you choose the wrong card, the cards will return to their original position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Tracing Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/english-tracing-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/english-tracing-book/</guid>
      <description>This game will allow you to quickly learn the alphabet. All 33 letters are displayed on the screen, and you can click on any of them. After that, you will see a capital letter and the word that begins with it. In addition, an image corresponding to the word will also appear. Check all the letters and learn the Russian alphabet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Coloring Time</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kids-coloring-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kids-coloring-time/</guid>
      <description>Do you like to draw and color? Then you will definitely like this game. Here it is proposed to work on a black-and-white image dedicated to the fairy tale &amp;ldquo;Ryaba the Hen&amp;rdquo;. At the bottom of the screen are all available colors, click on them with a brush to be able to use the selected color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Test Challenge 1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/math-test-challenge-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/math-test-challenge-1/</guid>
      <description>Educational math games for grade 1 offer you to practice your counting skills. The screen displays two rows of cards. At the top of the screen are images of objects, and at the bottom - numbers. You need to count the items and match each card with the correct number. Correct pairs will immediately disappear from the screen. An educational game for the first grade takes place in several stages, and the task gradually becomes more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peppa Pig Pop And Spell</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/peppa-pig-pop-and-spell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/peppa-pig-pop-and-spell/</guid>
      <description>Educational game will turn you into a real artist who knows a lot about a variety of colors. Several painted Easter eggs are displayed on the screen. Half of each is painted, while the other half is still in black and white. You need to arm yourself with a brush, dip in a suitable paint, and then apply it to the correct area. Very fun and educational activity! Color all the halves of the eggs, and then click on the &amp;ldquo;Check&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Food Court</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-food-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-food-court/</guid>
      <description>Turn into a real artist and paint a dull black and white image. You need to use a variety of paints located at the bottom of the screen. Choose any shades and apply them to the picture to make it bright and attractive in the end. Fantasy has no limits!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smurfberries Drop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/smurfberries-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/smurfberries-drop/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to start harvesting! Five baskets of different colors will appear on the screen, and you need to place the corresponding vegetables and fruits in them. Grab the fruit with the mouse, and then transfer it to a basket of the same shade. If you make a mistake, the element will return to its place. Act carefully to make mistakes as little as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swan Puzzle Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/swan-puzzle-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/swan-puzzle-challenge/</guid>
      <description>All jigsaw puzzle lovers will love this simple but interesting game. It is necessary to assemble a full-fledged image from a large number of pieces. To do this, move the elements to the appropriate places and connect them in the correct order. As a result, you will get a bright and pretty picture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
