<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Operation on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/operation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Operation on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/operation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Anna Scoliosis Surgery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/anna-scoliosis-surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/anna-scoliosis-surgery/</guid>
      <description>Little Lisa turned to you, as one of the best surgeons in the country. She developed a back problem called scoliosis. The child constantly feels pain, and she urgently needs to undergo a complex operation. Thanks to special implants inserted during the surgery, her back will straighten and the pain will gradually stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goldie Princess Mommy Birth</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldie-princess-mommy-birth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldie-princess-mommy-birth/</guid>
      <description>During the game Operation Birth, you go to one of the best maternity hospitals in the city, where you become a doctor who helps babies to be born. At the beginning of the game you need to choose the level of training. If you choose an intern, then the whole process of childbirth will be accompanied by tips, thanks to which you can easily perform the necessary manipulations. If, during the game for girls, you dare to click on the level of a specialist, then you will have to take birth without any help and completely on your own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Princess Twins Birth</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-twins-birth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-twins-birth/</guid>
      <description>A married couple who are expecting a child turned to one of the city&amp;rsquo;s maternity hospitals. Pregnant Lisa complains of strange pains and you have to accept her premature birth. To protect the future mother and her child, a complex operation is to be performed. Try to give Lisa a C-section as carefully as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Queen Brain Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-brain-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-brain-doctor/</guid>
      <description>A nice girl came to the hospital where you work as a surgeon. She complains of severe headaches and dizziness. You have to examine the beauty, conduct medical research and, if necessary, perform a complex brain operation that will save the patient from terrible pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessies Hospital Recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessies-hospital-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessies-hospital-recovery/</guid>
      <description>During the game Do Operations you meet with an alien whose ship was defeated near the Earth. The beauty was injured during the fall of her flying saucer, and now you have to give her first aid. Carefully examine the amazing patient, determine what injuries she received, perform the necessary operations and try to cure the baby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mommy Twins Birth</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mommy-twins-birth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mommy-twins-birth/</guid>
      <description>The famous model and TV star Barbie is expecting a baby. She came to see her doctor, and you have to become his assistant. Guided by the prompts, conduct a medical examination of the expectant mother, prepare her for childbirth and take part in them. Barbie and her cute baby will be grateful for your help.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
