<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cold heart on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/cold-heart/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cold heart on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/cold-heart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elsa Adventure game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-adventure-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-adventure-game/</guid>
      <description>The Elsa Adventure game introduces you to the brave Kristoff Bjorgman. Together with him you have to go to a distant snowy desert. There you must find the Ice Palace, where the elder sister of his beloved Princess Anna lives. Elsa, the princess of the fairy kingdom, left her father&amp;rsquo;s house a long time ago, but now it&amp;rsquo;s time to return. Help the young man safely reach his destination and deliver the beauty home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen game for boys</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/frozen-game-for-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/frozen-game-for-boys/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game Frozen for boys, you will see the snowman Olaf, who has lost all his body parts. And you need to quickly help him collect everything! To do this, jump on the snow platforms, avoiding the snowballs flying from above. And the deer will help you jump even higher, playing the role of a kind of springboard!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Action Frozen</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-action-frozen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-action-frozen/</guid>
      <description>The action game Frozen sends you along with Anna and her friends in search of the girl&amp;rsquo;s older sister. Elsa, that&amp;rsquo;s the name of Anna&amp;rsquo;s sister, received a unique gift at birth. She could control the cold, turning everything around her into ice. Having matured, the beauty realized that her ability is dangerous for others, and retired far, far away, to the land of snow. While playing an adventure game about Elsa and Anna, you have to help the main characters overcome a huge number of dangers and obstacles, avoid meeting with wild animals and terrible monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Adventure at Olaf&#39;s Falls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-adventure-at-olafs-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-adventure-at-olafs-falls/</guid>
      <description>Snowman Olaf decided to go to visit his beloved princess Elsa. On the way, he managed to fall into a deep abyss and lose parts of his snowy body. Help the unlucky traveler to get out of the trap, and at the same time collect all your spare parts. Climbing up, use the help of Sven&amp;rsquo;s reindeer, who will gladly throw the snowman high up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Adventure in the Kingdom of Arendelle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-adventure-in-the-kingdom-of-arendelle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-adventure-in-the-kingdom-of-arendelle/</guid>
      <description>Princess Anna and her friend Christophe go in search of the eldest daughter of the ruler of the kingdom of Arendelle. Help the couple go through all the trials and get to the ice castle, where Princess Elsa took refuge. On the way you will find a huge number of exciting adventures, traps and dangers. Thanks to your help, Anna and Christoph will be able to bring the princess back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Frozen 2 rpg</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-frozen-2-rpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-frozen-2-rpg/</guid>
      <description>While playing Frozen 2, you meet Olaf, a funny and very inattentive snowman. Walking in the mountains, he managed to lose parts of his body, and now it is necessary to find all the lost pieces. Help Olaf complete this difficult task by jumping from one mountain ledge to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Frozen and Double Bad</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-frozen-and-double-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-frozen-and-double-bad/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to play as both Christoph and Anna. They want to find Elsa, but for this they need to go through several intricate levels, trying not to catch the eyes of enemies. Use the arrow buttons to move through the levels and overcome obstacles. And don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect bonus items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Frozen Elsa Escape from the Castle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-frozen-elsa-escape-from-the-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-frozen-elsa-escape-from-the-castle/</guid>
      <description>The game Frozen Elsa Escapes from the Castle is an exciting quest, over the passage of which you will have to rack your brains. Explore the snowy forest area in order to find a variety of items (set in the game conditions) and place them in your inventory. Then it remains only to figure out how these items need to be applied.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
