<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For children 3-4 years old on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-3-4-years-old/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For children 3-4 years old on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-3-4-years-old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse &amp; Friends Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/arty-mouse--friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/arty-mouse--friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>In the English city of Birmingham, where the engine Thomas and his friends live and work, a holiday will take place in a few days. The mayor of the city asked his friends to help him prepare for the upcoming celebration. Help Thomas, Bert and Harold complete important tasks as quickly as possible, because the inhabitants of the city are looking forward to this wonderful event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Elsa Homemade Cookies Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-elsa-homemade-cookies-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-elsa-homemade-cookies-cooking/</guid>
      <description>An interesting game for children aged 3-4 will introduce you to a firefighter puppy who is ready to put out all the fires. But you need to help him with this. The screen will display a fire area with a certain number, and you need to set the same number on the pump, and then give a command to the rescue dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Day Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-day-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-day-coloring/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you will have the opportunity not only to show your creative talents, but also to learn the letters of the English alphabet. Choose one of the letters and color it with a magic brush and paints. Then complete the picture with her image with drawings of objects that begin with this letter. Color all the pictures and save on your computer a wonderful handmade alphabet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Puzzle Time</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweet-puzzle-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweet-puzzle-time/</guid>
      <description>Chica the hen and her friends had a big celebration on the occasion of Mr. C&amp;rsquo;s birthday. During the celebration, the guests managed to break all the paintings in the house. Help the hostess fold the pieces correctly and glue the pictures together. Chika will be grateful for your help and will return all the images to their places with great pleasure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom And Jerry Mouse Maze</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tom-and-jerry-mouse-maze/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tom-and-jerry-mouse-maze/</guid>
      <description>The heroine of the game went to the far side of the field, but accidentally scattered gardening supplies all over the garden. Help the muddler: get on your bike and go searching, find all the scattered things in the labyrinths of the homestead and deliver them to the girl. The baby will be very grateful to you for your help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trolls: Käferflug</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/trolls-k%C3%A4ferflug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/trolls-k%C3%A4ferflug/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s an air show in a small town and you&amp;rsquo;ve been invited to take part in an airplane race. Choose one of the characters in the game and go to the runway. You need to win three championship races and thanks to this, get the title of king of the sky before the next competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Under The Sea</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/under-the-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/under-the-sea/</guid>
      <description>This toy will help develop your mindfulness and memory. She offers to find pairs of identical cards in a deck laid out on the playing field. Turning over the cards with pictures in pairs, memorize their location and try to open the same ones. The game ends only when all pairs have been found.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
