<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ambulance on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/ambulance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ambulance on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/ambulance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exotic Princess Mission Accident ER</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/exotic-princess-mission-accident-er/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/exotic-princess-mission-accident-er/</guid>
      <description>The life of the patient may depend on how quickly and successfully the ambulance reaches the place of the call, picks up the patient and parks near the hospital. Therefore, quickly and accurately move through the streets, collecting first-aid kits. Don&amp;rsquo;t collide with other cars on the road and don&amp;rsquo;t crash into buildings. Use the arrow keys to control your car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Queen Resurrection Emergency</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-resurrection-emergency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-resurrection-emergency/</guid>
      <description>You have received a girl who is preparing to become a mother. Soon she should give birth to a child, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to conduct a thorough examination. Connect the oxygen mask, measure the patient&amp;rsquo;s temperature and listen to the baby&amp;rsquo;s heartbeat. If everything is normal, the pregnant woman can be transferred to the ward. There you can take her blood pressure and do an ultrasound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Rescue</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/traffic-rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/traffic-rescue/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will drive an ambulance. An urgent challenge awaits you, and you need to deftly overcome obstacles to get to the patient as soon as possible. Then turn around and take him to the hospital, carefully moving over bumps and potholes. Calls come from all over the city, but your goal is to deliver all the victims to the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
