<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dress up for a wedding on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/dress-up-for-a-wedding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dress up for a wedding on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/dress-up-for-a-wedding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Annie Wedding Shopping</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/annie-wedding-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/annie-wedding-shopping/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to come up with a cool wedding look for the heroine of the game! Choose for her hairstyle, dress, stockings, shoes, veil, bouquet, jewelry. If you want, you can use the random selection of outfits. Click on the button with two arrows and watch the change of ready-made stylish options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audreys Dream Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/audreys-dream-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/audreys-dream-wedding/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game, you will find yourself in an eastern country, where you are invited to work on the images of men and women. The character to be dressed up will be displayed on the screen. Rewards points are awarded for this. Try to collect as many of them as possible, choosing the most suitable items for each!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbies Tropical Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/barbies-tropical-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/barbies-tropical-wedding/</guid>
      <description>A wedding dress can be not only white, and this game clearly demonstrates this fact. In it, you are invited to create a chic outfit for the bride in pink shades. If you are not sure about your design talents, use the hint button and look at ready-made options for holiday looks. They will inspire you to create your own great outfit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blonde Princess Wedding Fashion</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/blonde-princess-wedding-fashion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/blonde-princess-wedding-fashion/</guid>
      <description>Here you have to work on the wedding images of the newlyweds. On the screen you will see the bride and groom, as well as an impressive range of wedding items. Click on them and choose a suit, dress, hairstyles, accessories, shoes, trying to achieve the most harmonious combination of all the details. Let this couple be the most beautiful!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonnies Surprise Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnies-surprise-proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnies-surprise-proposal/</guid>
      <description>The heroine of the game decided to hold a unique wedding in retro style. Your task is to create the most suitable wedding look for the girl. You can choose a hairstyle, outfit, various cute accessories to complete the picture perfectly. The finished result can be saved or printed directly from the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridal Dress Designer Competition</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bridal-dress-designer-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bridal-dress-designer-competition/</guid>
      <description>The heroine of the game is getting ready for her wedding and you are invited to help her. Almost everything is ready, it remains only to decide on the outfit. Choose the most luxurious dress for the bride and complete it with all the necessary wedding accessories: veil, gloves, jewelry. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget about the hair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridal Shower Party for Moana</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bridal-shower-party-for-moana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bridal-shower-party-for-moana/</guid>
      <description>No wedding is complete without a bridesmaid. Naturally, this participant of the holiday should also look attractive. The game asks you to come up with a cool outfit for the bridesmaid by choosing a great dress for her and complementing it with cute accessories. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget about the right hairstyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bride Wedding Dresses</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bride-wedding-dresses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bride-wedding-dresses/</guid>
      <description>In this game you can feel like a real royal stylist. Here you can choose outfits and hairstyles for Prince William and his wife Kate. Press the buttons and dress up the royal couple whenever you want. In addition to clothes, you can change hairstyles and skin color. And the finished image can even be printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dove Wedding Dolly Dress Up H</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dove-wedding-dolly-dress-up-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dove-wedding-dolly-dress-up-h/</guid>
      <description>The heroine of the game is preparing for the wedding, and you need to work as her stylist and come up with a cool wedding outfit. In the game assortment you will find puffy dresses, veils, jewelry, bouquets. From all this, you will definitely get the best wedding look that will appeal to the bride herself, and the groom, and all the guests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exotic Wedding Looks</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/exotic-wedding-looks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/exotic-wedding-looks/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will see a girl who is getting ready for her wedding. You need to come up with a suitable wedding outfit for her, using any of the suggested wardrobe items. The menu contains not only luxurious dresses, but also all kinds of additions: jewelry, gloves, bouquets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Queen Wedding Kiss</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-wedding-kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-wedding-kiss/</guid>
      <description>In this wonderful game you will meet a girl who needs to choose a wedding dress. You can also press special buttons to change her hairstyle, lipstick and skin color. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget about cute accessories that will perfectly match your newly created wedding look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Queen Wedding Tailor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-wedding-tailor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-wedding-tailor/</guid>
      <description>A sweet girl wants her wedding to be held at the highest level. Your task is to create a suitable outfit for the heroine of the game. Here you can choose a chic dress, add a veil, tiara, handbag and other accessories, without which it is difficult to imagine a modern bride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katies Wedding Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/katies-wedding-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/katies-wedding-day/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you are invited to create a wedding look in spring style. On the screen you will see green, yellow, pink clothes that look very chic. You can decorate the chosen dress with all sorts of cute jewelry that will perfectly complement the image and make it as complete as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant Princesses Fashion Dressing Roo</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pregnant-princesses-fashion-dressing-roo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pregnant-princesses-fashion-dressing-roo/</guid>
      <description>Immediately after loading, a fitting room appears on the screen with the main character in the center. The girl is already dressed up in a wedding dress, but you can make your own adjustments: add a touch or two and even completely change clothes, shoes and accessories. By the way, there is a hint button, when you click on it, you will see three ready-made options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Annie Summer Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-annie-summer-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-annie-summer-wedding/</guid>
      <description>A young couple is going on a honeymoon trip, and the guy is already fully prepared, but the girl still needs to get dressed. You will have to help the heroine of the game by choosing comfortable and cute clothes for her. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget about accessories that will perfectly complement your holiday outfit. The finished result can be saved for memory or even printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Black Wedding Dress</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-black-wedding-dress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-black-wedding-dress/</guid>
      <description>Not all girls are attracted to the classic wedding style, and in this game you will meet a bride who decided to celebrate her wedding differently from others. She wants to get an informal outfit, and you have to help her with this. In the game you will find a large number of dresses and accessories for an informal wedding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Ellie Dream Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-ellie-dream-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-ellie-dream-wedding/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will see a girl who is getting ready for a wedding. You are invited to help her choose a great outfit using the available assortment. Here is a large number of modern dresses, as well as a variety of additions to it. There is an opportunity to see ready-made versions of images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Snow Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-snow-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-snow-wedding/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you have to work on your wedding look. The girl is waiting for one of the most important events in her life, and she wants to look perfect on it. The menu has a large number of corsets, skirts, shoes, tiaras and other items that are great for a wedding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess The Day Before My Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-the-day-before-my-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-the-day-before-my-wedding/</guid>
      <description>During the wedding dress up and makeup game for girls you will have to create a look for the girl who is going to get married. Choose for her a suitable hairstyle, dress, shoes, veil, cute jewelry. If you wish, you can use the tips and admire the finished options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Wedding Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-wedding-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-wedding-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>A sweet girl is preparing for the wedding ceremony and wants to get the best outfit. Let&amp;rsquo;s help the bride! It is necessary to choose the most beautiful things and accessories from among those offered and simply drag them onto the girl. The creation of an outfit is not limited to anything, you can fully show your imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapunzel Wedding Hair Design</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rapunzel-wedding-hair-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rapunzel-wedding-hair-design/</guid>
      <description>During the game for girls Dress up wedding dresses you will meet a girl who is going to an important event - her marriage. Naturally, she wants to look as chic as possible. You have to come up with a great outfit for the heroine, using a virtual assortment of clothes for this. It has a variety of dresses, as well as all kinds of accessories: bouquets, earrings, pendants, hair ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sery Wedding Dolly Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sery-wedding-dolly-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sery-wedding-dolly-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Any girl dreams of a luxurious wedding, and the heroine of this game is no exception. You are invited to dress her up for the wedding ceremony, using all sorts of elements of a festive wardrobe. Try on a chic dress for the bride, add a veil, bouquet, jewelry. You can change the wedding dress as many times as you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Day Before Elsa Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-day-before-elsa-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-day-before-elsa-wedding/</guid>
      <description>The lovers are going to the wedding ceremony, and you need to think over the most suitable outfits for them. Pick up a suit for the groom and a dress for the bride, not forgetting about various little things. The finished image of happy newlyweds can be saved to a computer or printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiana Spring Green Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tiana-spring-green-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tiana-spring-green-wedding/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will see on the screen a girl who is going to marry her beloved prince. Your task is to design a wedding dress for her. Grab any items with the cursor and drag them to the heroine. The game menu contains only the most stylish dresses and accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding Perfect Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wedding-perfect-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wedding-perfect-makeup/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you are invited to prepare a girl for marriage. First you need to choose a hairstyle for the bride, and then do makeup using all kinds of decorative cosmetics. Please note that here you can choose the intensity of application of cosmetics. And the final stage is the choice of dress and accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding Planner</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wedding-planner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wedding-planner/</guid>
      <description>The girl is about to get married, which means that you need to come up with a great outfit for her. By launching this game, you will see a large number of chic dresses, as well as all those little things, without which the wedding image will be incomplete. And when you click on the “Hint” button, ready-made options for holiday sets will open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding Spring</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wedding-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wedding-spring/</guid>
      <description>A charming girl is preparing for the wedding ceremony, and, of course, dreams of the most luxurious outfit for this event. Help the bride to achieve an excellent result by choosing a dress, gloves, veil and other elements of the wedding wardrobe. You can also choose the format of the wedding photo!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
