<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>car parking on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/car-parking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in car parking on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/car-parking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>18 Wheeler Academy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/18-wheeler-academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/18-wheeler-academy/</guid>
      <description>You are incredibly lucky - you can try your hand at a tow truck. It is necessary to drive up to a standing car, hook it and drag it to the penalty area. However, not everything is as simple as it seems. You will have to be careful not to crash not only the client&amp;rsquo;s car, but also your own. In addition, you need to park cars on the site so that there is room for others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bus Master Parking 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bus-master-parking-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bus-master-parking-3d/</guid>
      <description>This game can be played by several people, competing in scoring and speed through the level. The bottom line is that you need to rearrange the pickup in the parking lot from one place to another, trying not to break it and spend a minimum of time on it. Where exactly you need to go, the arrow indicates. The machine has a fairly large inertia, so it is not recommended to gas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bus Parking 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bus-parking-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bus-parking-3d/</guid>
      <description>To play Bus Cars you will need patience, a good eye and spatial thinking. For a successful passage, it will be necessary, while driving the bus, to lead it along a tricky path to the end point. In this case, you need to collect coins and manage to not crash into anything. The levels are constantly becoming more difficult, so you won&amp;rsquo;t be bored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Parking 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/car-parking-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/car-parking-2/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to become a parking champion? Try your hand at this game! Park the clunker given to you by the developers in such a way as to meet the specified time and not crash the car. By the way, other parked cars are also crushed, which looks fun, but not for long, because your safety margin quickly dries up and the game ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-parking/</guid>
      <description>The fact that this is an international airport is only indicated by aircraft that are visible at the edges of the screen. It does not affect the gameplay in any way. You will have to park your car at any time of the day. The game has 12 levels, which provide different options for the location of the parking lot. You can compete with your friends by playing the game in turns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross Road Exit</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cross-road-exit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cross-road-exit/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to help the SpongeBob characters to park their boat. On the first level you will do it with hints. That is, along the designated trajectory. However, you will have to sweat on your own. There is a limited time to complete the task, so hurry up. If you don&amp;rsquo;t, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to start all over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dockyard Car Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dockyard-car-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dockyard-car-parking/</guid>
      <description>Finally, in front of you is such a game that parents cannot call fooling around, and they will even be very happy that you play it. After all, this is not just about parking a toy car, but also about mathematics. An example appears at the top left. The correct answer is the parking space. Well, you also need to drive in the right way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Bus Parking 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-bus-parking-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-bus-parking-3d/</guid>
      <description>A very interesting toy designed for two players. Management is carried out from one keyboard, but different sets of keys. You will have to act simultaneously, but not competing, but helping each other. At the same time, it is worth considering the fact that the death of one machine leads to the need for a general restart. So, be careful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Car Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-car-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-car-parking/</guid>
      <description>If you were looking for a relatively simple, calm game about cars, then this option is perfect. During the game it is necessary to park the car in the indicated places. Parked - moved to another level, which will start from the previous parking lot. If you do not fit into the turn at least a millimeter, you have to start all over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frolic Car Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/frolic-car-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/frolic-car-parking/</guid>
      <description>A game with weird graphics and car rendering. Otherwise, there is almost nothing original in it. Just drive your car along the arrows, collect bonuses and look for a parking spot. There is not so much fantastic here, but there is. For example, transitions between parking levels. The game has a time limit, so there is no time to stare at the sights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garage Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/garage-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/garage-parking/</guid>
      <description>During the game Car Parking, you will start each new stage with a new car. The task is always the same: to drive the car to the parking lot and park it. Along the way, it is recommended to collect coins and not crash into anything. The number of allowed collisions is limited. Each level can be completed as many times as you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Truck Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/heavy-truck-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/heavy-truck-parking/</guid>
      <description>If you don&amp;rsquo;t like school, don&amp;rsquo;t know a craft, or just don&amp;rsquo;t like luck, get ready to work as a parking attendant. In this game, cartoon characters come to Mickey Mouse&amp;rsquo;s studio on business. You need to park their car, hang the keys in the closet, and then serve the car. The game is not very convenient control: you need to hold down the character with the mouse and drag across the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Park It 11</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/just-park-it-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/just-park-it-11/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to not just park an 18-wheel truck in a specified place, but also fulfill a number of additional conditions. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the fact that this is not a truck, but a fire truck and, accordingly, they are waiting for it at the fire. You need to put the car clearly so that the firefighters start extinguishing. You will also have to drive for water, monitor fuel levels, save people, put out fires and watch the timer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Parking Multiplication</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/math-parking-multiplication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/math-parking-multiplication/</guid>
      <description>Even if you are a driver of a powerful heavy truck, this does not mean that you are allowed to park any way and anywhere. You, too, can have your tires slashed and water tanked for bad parking. So you will train to drive through the whole city, hitch a trailer, carry loads, and then properly park your car neatly and like a normal person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monoa City Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monoa-city-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monoa-city-parking/</guid>
      <description>It is unlikely that the Mustang is any different from the Lada in terms of parking. Is it just the power of the motor, which should be taken into account when you press the gas pedal. To successfully complete each level of the toy, you must not only park at the indicated place, but also not beat the car while you drive up to it. And you still need to meet the allotted time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Park Your Car</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/park-your-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/park-your-car/</guid>
      <description>Once again, gamers are encouraged to practice putting toy cars in the parking lot. View in the game from above, control is standard. For something, a steering wheel is drawn in the lower right corner. There are two serious limitations in the game: a timer in the form of a bar in the upper right and the number of collisions. You can only collide once: the first and the last.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking/</guid>
      <description>During the game Parking cars with a steering wheel and pedals, it will not be possible to get rid of the usual four buttons with arrows. Here you will come across an imitation of driving a car. You can switch the view: from the third person and from the first, that is, from the cockpit. Many levels are waiting for you. The task for each of them is the same - to drive the car into the parking space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking Fury</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-fury/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-fury/</guid>
      <description>It is unlikely that the game Car Parking will teach you how to properly park your car in the parking lot. You can learn this only in a driving school, or on your own, but in any case through a long and hard training. And in this case, parking cars is just fun. So, you need to put the car in the specified place. In this case, you need to park correctly, that is, according to the inscriptions &amp;ldquo;back&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;front&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking Fury 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-fury-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-fury-3/</guid>
      <description>So, in this game you will learn how to work as a parking attendant again (and what if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to learn anything else?). The task is as follows: in the allotted time, it is necessary to overtake the cars parked at the curb to the parking lot. First you have to get into one of the cars, and then start driving it. Do it carefully, because after three collisions comes a game over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking Fury 3D Bounty Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-fury-3d-bounty-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-fury-3d-bounty-hunter/</guid>
      <description>The splash screen in the game is promising. True, it does not really reflect the gaming reality. And it is such that for a start you can choose a police car (only elite options here). Next, you have to put the car in place in the shortest time and not break it at the same time. If you are not satisfied with the results of the completed stage, you can restart it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking Fury 3D Night Thief</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-fury-3d-night-thief/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-fury-3d-night-thief/</guid>
      <description>The developers of the game offer you to try to park vintage cars. The game has enough levels to kill your free time and see plenty of vintage cars from above. As you progress in the game, the levels will become more difficult. In addition, there is a timer and you need to invest in a certain time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking Panic</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-panic/</guid>
      <description>The process of the game for girls Car Parking, if it differs from the boyish options, is only cartoonish. The game can&amp;rsquo;t be called easy. In addition to the difficult driving, there is also a timer. That is, the task must be completed within the allotted time. The task itself is to overtake the Scooby Doo minibus from point A to point B and park. At the same time, even a slight collision with the curb leads to damage to the machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/police-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/police-parking/</guid>
      <description>An ordinary toy in which you have to put the car in the parking lot and keep within thirty seconds. The main feature is that retro cars will have to be parked. Although, given the view from above, you will not see anything special. Another curious feature: while you are parking, some bastard is trying to take your place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Port Car Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/port-car-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/port-car-parking/</guid>
      <description>If you hope that parking your car will be easier in the future, then this game will shatter all your dreams. That&amp;rsquo;s what she likes, so it&amp;rsquo;s graphics. As for the process itself, it is not bad either. The goal is to park the car. The physics here is almost the same as in reality. That is, you will have to taxi carefully, taking into account inertia and other factors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Car Parking 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/real-car-parking-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/real-car-parking-3d/</guid>
      <description>If you do not want to get a normal education and you decide to link your future life with parking, then know that there is a lot of competition among parking attendants. In this regard, to weed out the unsuitable and the worst, parking competitions are arranged. You need to put the car in the indicated place as quickly as possible and without collisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Semi Driver 3d Trailer Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/semi-driver-3d-trailer-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/semi-driver-3d-trailer-parking/</guid>
      <description>If there are lego cars, then there should be lego parking for them. Is it logical? Absolutely! And this toy clearly demonstrates everything. You have to park a passenger car in accordance with the instructions, where should be the back and where should be the front. Do everything carefully, without too much haste. There are no time limits, but you will be shocked by how many traffic cops rush along the road!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skill 3D Parking Thunder Trucks</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/skill-3d-parking-thunder-trucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/skill-3d-parking-thunder-trucks/</guid>
      <description>The name of the game suggests certain difficulties with the passage. And they start from the second stage. At each level, the tasks are different and more complicated. The margin of safety of your car is very limited. But the margin of time should be enough for a careful check into the parking space without damage. If you fail, you will have to start from the first level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sport Car Parking Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sport-car-parking-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sport-car-parking-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Everything starts small. In this case, toys. You need to find a place to park the toy car. It is not enough to find a free stall (many are busy with other cars, cubes, some kind of trash). It is necessary not to crash the car on the way to the parking lot yet, because there are a lot of other toys scattered on the floor. Also, the game has a time limit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Police Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-police-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-police-parking/</guid>
      <description>The game has miniature cars and a top view. Perhaps for some it will only add bonuses. The goal is to put the car in the specified place and spend the minimum amount of time on it. It&amp;rsquo;s not easy to fulfill the conditions: as expected, there are a lot of cars in front of the supermarket, and someone in addition parked like an asshole. One collision is a game over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supercar Police Parking 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/supercar-police-parking-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/supercar-police-parking-2/</guid>
      <description>What could be more fun than parking your car on a slippery winter road? That&amp;rsquo;s right, only the option when you have summer tires. It looks like the developers of the game thought the same way, and you are given a unique chance to try to park a truck with gifts in such conditions. All sorts of cars drive around you, which is very disturbing. Also time is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUV Parking Simulator 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/suv-parking-simulator-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/suv-parking-simulator-3d/</guid>
      <description>The toy has a top view, so don&amp;rsquo;t expect any special beauty from the image of the car. They look like toy cars. The goal is to move along the arrows, drive the car to the parking lot and park it. You need to park correctly, observing where the back should be, and where in front of the car. Collisions damage your car. If there are too many, the game will end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tap Tap Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tap-tap-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tap-tap-parking/</guid>
      <description>It is not often that you get a chance to be the captain of a comfortable yacht for at least a short time. This game will give you that opportunity. The task is to park the ship in the allotted place. This must be done with all caution so as not to drown the boat. To control, use the arrow keys and carefully look around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truck Driver Crazy Road 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/truck-driver-crazy-road-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/truck-driver-crazy-road-2/</guid>
      <description>Even if you&amp;rsquo;re in a patrol car, don&amp;rsquo;t think that you can do everything: crash into other cars, park like an asshole, and so on. The game will clearly demonstrate this. Your task is extremely simple: put the police car in the parking lot in the indicated place. The route is marked with arrows, follow them. A few minor hitting obstacles - the game is over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valet Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/valet-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/valet-parking/</guid>
      <description>Although you drive a limousine, this does not mean that you can automatically park anywhere and any way you like - there are cars and cooler ones. So, don&amp;rsquo;t ooh, don&amp;rsquo;t ah, but turn the steering wheel and put this monster in its place. At the next levels, you will have to park other cars, and each time in a different way. Each stage can be replayed, bringing to perfection.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
