<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>McDonald&#39;s Simulator on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/mcdonalds-simulator/</link>
    <description>Recent content in McDonald&#39;s Simulator on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/mcdonalds-simulator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Burger Bar</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/burger-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/burger-bar/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been hired at a fast food restaurant. Now you need to quickly learn how to cook the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s signature dish. An experienced chef will help you with this, but you have to be very careful. Within a few seconds, he will show you the entire composition of the burger. Your task is to repeat the dish exactly using the ingredients available in the kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Chef</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/burger-chef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/burger-chef/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game, you will have a unique chance to become the owner of the McDonald&amp;rsquo;s network for a while. The task is to establish the work of all links, the interaction of which will ultimately allow you to get delicious burgers and earn money. Make sure everything runs like clockwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Chef Restaurant</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/burger-chef-restaurant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/burger-chef-restaurant/</guid>
      <description>In the game, you are invited to compete with the chef, who cleverly creates the most incredibly appetizing and juicy sandwiches. You can start the first round with a professional master who smiles slyly from under his mustache with any burger. But before you start cooking, you need to carefully remember what and in what sequence to put on bread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Club Sandwich</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/club-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/club-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to take on the management of a restaurant. The faster and better the service in it, the greater the chances of getting an award in the competition and thereby attracting more customers. It is required to overtake competitors and prove that your institution is the best in the city. To do this, you need to seat each client at a free table, write down the order, bring it, and then remove it from the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dner Kebab Salade Tomates Oignons</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dner-kebab-salade-tomates-oignons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dner-kebab-salade-tomates-oignons/</guid>
      <description>Try to make the most delicious and unusual hamburgers in the world! Buy groceries with all the money you have and start cooking. Learn new recipes and try to surprise your customers with new, original burger recipes. Use the money you earn to purchase additional appetizing ingredients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Burger</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fast-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fast-burger/</guid>
      <description>The McDonald&amp;rsquo;s Simulator game invites you to play the role of a fast food restaurant manager. So you can see for yourself how difficult the process is. Starting to play, you have to control all stages of the production of hamburgers. You, as a leader, must see everything, hear everything and imagine step by step how to quickly and efficiently perform this or that work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Burger Biz</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-burger-biz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-burger-biz/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to figure out the technological process of making hamburgers and serve visitors to an ordinary small cafe. The client will be satisfied when he receives his order on time. To do this, you need to quickly prepare the dish and hand it to the buyer. Manage all processes with the mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Burger</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/top-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/top-burger/</guid>
      <description>This game is a step-by-step instruction for cooking two delicious cheeseburgers. Recipes will vary from one to another. All that is required of you is to follow the yellow-green arrows in the pictures and follow the chef&amp;rsquo;s instructions exactly. If everything works out, you will earn a record number of points.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
