<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fights 2 on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/fights-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fights 2 on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/fights-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Street Fight King Of The Gang</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/street-fight-king-of-the-gang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/street-fight-king-of-the-gang/</guid>
      <description>The game gives the opportunity to participate in the battle as one or a pair of players. In it, 8 characters are waiting for you, ready to fight for victory in the ring of the prestigious championship, using super blows and their various combinations. Fight in different modes - quick, practice and challenge, against the clock, or a certain number of rounds. Two players can play on the same keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Fighter Madness</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/street-fighter-madness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/street-fighter-madness/</guid>
      <description>An exciting game for real fighters in which you will be able to demonstrate all your dexterity by delivering accurate and crushing blows to your opponent. Control your character with the mouse, trying to dodge your opponent&amp;rsquo;s attacks in time. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to use the block, as any accurate hit from the opponent takes away points from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streets Rage Fight</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/streets-rage-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/streets-rage-fight/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to take part in a unique fight, where instead of professional boxers, celebrities, music and movie stars will fight in the ring. This time, your opponent will be a fragile girl. But, despite her appearance, she is fluent in boxing technique and has a well-placed strike. So don&amp;rsquo;t relax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superhero Fight</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-fight/</guid>
      <description>Here is a 2D fighting game in which you can control different characters, including Superman, Batman, Aquaman, Joker and Green Lantern, meeting in battles with no less famous supervillains. As you progress through the game, its main characters gain experience, and you get access to new warriors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Apocalypse: Survival Warz</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-apocalypse-survival-warz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-apocalypse-survival-warz/</guid>
      <description>Crazed zombies have filled the whole city and are hunting for the survivors. A brave girl from the Avengers team decides to destroy the monsters. You have to support her in an unequal battle. You need to constantly improve the weapons and skills of the main character in order to withstand zombie attacks. Use the bonuses that come across her on the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Mission</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-mission/</guid>
      <description>An excellent fighting game where all the superheroes of Marvel comics are present, from which you can choose anyone, taking into account the individual characteristics and abilities of each character. Several game modes are available - arcade, survival, demonstration, training and others. Try to win in each of them and become a champion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
