<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Similar to minecraft on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/similar-to-minecraft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Similar to minecraft on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/similar-to-minecraft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blocky Combat Swat Killing Zombie</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/blocky-combat-swat-killing-zombie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/blocky-combat-swat-killing-zombie/</guid>
      <description>Roam the dark forest and collect notes left by Slender. Who it is is not so easy to answer, but those who were not lucky enough to meet him were very frightened. Your task is as follows: you need to find all the leaves with the text and take them with you. But try not to catch the eye of Slender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blocky Runner</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/blocky-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/blocky-runner/</guid>
      <description>An interesting game that develops dexterity and reaction speed. Your native island has become completely different. It is crawling with monsters, pitted with lava ditches and deep rivers in which you can easily drown. It&amp;rsquo;s time to leave this inhospitable place. Run, overcome obstacles and collect coins to buy upgrades. Management: W - attack, A, S, D - movement, SPACE - jump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gunhop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gunhop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gunhop/</guid>
      <description>Complete the parkour map in Minecraft style, overcoming all available obstacles with the help of jumps. Explore the area both outside and inside buildings. In this game you will find places where you will need to climb the mountain, which is very difficult to do. Some parts of the route pass through abysses filled with boiling lava. Falling into them is clearly not worth it, because the consequences are irreversible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legocraft</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/legocraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/legocraft/</guid>
      <description>Minecraft 200000000000</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets Kill Jeff The Killer Jeffs Revenge 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lets-kill-jeff-the-killer-jeffs-revenge-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lets-kill-jeff-the-killer-jeffs-revenge-2020/</guid>
      <description>Your friend is asking for help, and you need to hurry, otherwise he will be killed. Navigate through game locations to find the items you need to save. It is worth exploring the most mysterious corners of the gaming space, but be very careful, because scary monsters can attack you at any moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mazecraft</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mazecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mazecraft/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will have to try to get out of an old castle full of zombies. Your enemies are unusual: they consist of many squares, which crumble when hit by bullets. But, if parts of the corpse are highlighted in green, this means that it is self-healing, so keep shooting until it stops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mine Clone</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mine-clone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mine-clone/</guid>
      <description>An updated version of Minecraft 0 is waiting for you with new maps, weapons, and a more stable server. Prove that you are the best shooter in the world. Pick up a crowbar, pistol, shotgun, sniper rifle or machine gun and destroy as many enemies as possible. Fight in Minecraft style team battles and destroy the entire enemy squad. There are a lot of firearms of various types in your arsenal, however, the number of cartridges for them is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mineblock</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mineblock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mineblock/</guid>
      <description>While playing Minecraft Story Blocks you find yourself in a primeval unknown world, your main goal in it is just to survive. Playing is quite simple, especially since you can use the hints. In addition, the first proposed tasks will be training and will help you familiarize yourself with the rules of the game. In the first of them you will learn how to move around and explore the surroundings, in the second - to create the necessary items from the materials found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Lego Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecraft-lego-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecraft-lego-edition/</guid>
      <description>The Minecraft universe is endless and diverse. Can you build your home among the endless ice, snow, somewhere in the Alps, under the endless starry sky? It is quite difficult to get the necessary elements for your cherished housing; you will have to use both a pick and a shovel. A garden, farm or courtyard can be attached to the main building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecraft-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecraft-online/</guid>
      <description>Flash game Minecraft offers you to protect your house from encroachment of enemies. But first you need to get to the dwelling, paving the way through the grass. Enemies will then move along the same path, so it makes sense to make it longer and more winding. Another reason for this decision is that for every step you take when creating a road, you will receive blocks. It is they who in the flash game about Minecraft serve as a bargaining chip for acquiring weapons that will help to cope with enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Super Mario Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecraft-super-mario-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecraft-super-mario-edition/</guid>
      <description>Scary underground monsters have stolen a rare artifact from a famous museum. With the help of the game Minecraft Mario try to return the treasure. A difficult but full of excitement battle with monsters is ahead, but our hero has never been in such alterations. Thanks to special weapons and the ability to jump high, he will go through all the mazes of the Minecraft world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Rally 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-rally-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-rally-3d/</guid>
      <description>Many drivers are capable of driving at full speed on the highway, but only the best of them know how to drift. The Car Racing Minecraft game has a limited time to complete each level, and you need to try to go through many tight turns using the handbrake at speeds of over 100 miles per hour, leaving your opponent far behind. Get behind the wheel of a sports car and go for fame and money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Stories 1: Young Blood</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-stories-1-young-blood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-stories-1-young-blood/</guid>
      <description>In the peculiar world of the Minecraft GTA 5 game, you play the role of a thief who was able to rob a bank. Now he is waiting for a dynamic action that requires the manifestation of ingenuity and dexterity. You&amp;rsquo;ve done half the work, the money&amp;rsquo;s in your car. Now the main thing is to safely get away from the police chase. Try to escape from pursuit as quickly as possible without crashing into obstacles on the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Stories 2: Night of Payoff</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-stories-2-night-of-payoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-stories-2-night-of-payoff/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to try to escape from the police after a successful bank robbery. Your car is controlled by just two keys - &amp;ldquo;left&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo;. Survive the mini chase as long as you can, you might even be able to set a time record. The main thing is not to crash into anything in the excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
