<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A crisis on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/a-crisis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in A crisis on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/a-crisis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crisis shooter game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crisis-shooter-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crisis-shooter-game/</guid>
      <description>Another online shooter is ready to take couch commandos and offer them death matches. You can choose a team mode with the number of members from 4 to 8. Or you can play a war for singles. In the first case, by the way, you can &amp;ldquo;blame&amp;rdquo; your comrades, as well as yourself. A good arsenal is provided for the destruction of targets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Crisis</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-crisis/</guid>
      <description>The Crisis game only works in those browsers that support Unity. In addition, it is quite “heavy”, and loading can take a long time. However, the wait will be rewarded with a vengeance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Crisis - ghost team</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-crisis---ghost-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-crisis---ghost-team/</guid>
      <description>Ghost Team is a first person shooting simulator. After downloading, the user finds himself among some ancient ruins. He needs to fight off opponents rolling in waves. At the first level there is only a pistol. The second level is passed with &amp;ldquo;Kalash&amp;rdquo;, but the enemies are stronger. You can&amp;rsquo;t stand still. You need to run, jump, squat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Crisis 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-crisis-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-crisis-2/</guid>
      <description>Fans of contra-like toys are invited to try their hand at another online shooter. View, of course, from the first person. Already at the start, there is a bunch of weapons available: a dessert needle pistol, a Kalash gun, a shotgun, and something else. You can choose a team game, or you can run for yourself. Shooting takes place on difficult landscape locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Crisis online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-crisis-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-crisis-online/</guid>
      <description>Here is a good fantasy multiplayer shooting game. One single principle works in it: man is a wolf to man. That is, every man for himself. Each character is controlled by real people. Cunning and resourceful. Fortunately, everyone has the same weapons within the same location. It can be a grenade launcher, a blaster, a sniper and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
