<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Driving simulators on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/driving-simulators/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Driving simulators on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/driving-simulators/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>18 Wheeler Cargo Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/18-wheeler-cargo-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/18-wheeler-cargo-simulator/</guid>
      <description>While playing Truck Driving Simulators, you will have a unique opportunity to get a truck driver&amp;rsquo;s license. To do this, you must pass an exam in one of the licensed companies and obtain permission to drive a truck. Try to complete all the levels in this exciting truck simulator game. Pay close attention to the hints that appear on the playing field and try to complete the maneuvers on the heavy truck within a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Parking Real 3D Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/car-parking-real-3d-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/car-parking-real-3d-simulator/</guid>
      <description>A sweet grandmother asked her grandson to park her old car. Help the guy park the car. Do it like a real professional parking attendant and surprise your new friend with your skills. Try to park Granny&amp;rsquo;s old car in record time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checkpoint Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/checkpoint-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/checkpoint-run/</guid>
      <description>Racing games and driving simulators invite you to take part in exciting sports car competitions of one of the most famous car manufacturers in the world - Bugatti. On the tracks of the tournament you have to demonstrate good reaction and talent of a real racer. Try to overtake three of your competitors and get the cup of the legendary Italian stable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Car Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-car-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-car-parking/</guid>
      <description>While playing 3d driving simulator you have to take part in an exam, after passing which you can get a taxi driver&amp;rsquo;s license. The process is divided into 16 separate steps. Each of them will require you to confidently drive a car, know the rules of the road and be a talented driver. Be careful not to get into an accident on the streets of a big city filled with just a huge number of cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Car Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-car-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-car-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Here you are invited to test drive a fast Audi car. Move around the proposed location, gaining speed and avoiding obstacles. Please note that a collision may damage the car, but this will not prevent you from continuing to move. At the bottom of the screen is the speedometer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dubai Police Parking 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dubai-police-parking-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dubai-police-parking-2/</guid>
      <description>As a rule, in simulation games there is no clearly defined task. You just have to drive around the city blocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Truck Simulator 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/indian-truck-simulator-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/indian-truck-simulator-3d/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you become a truck driver who has to go on a long journey. By controlling the movements of your heavy truck using the arrow keys, try to deliver the goods to customers within a limited time. Be careful, follow the rules of the road and don&amp;rsquo;t get into an accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off Road Cargo Drive Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/off-road-cargo-drive-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/off-road-cargo-drive-simulator/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game, you become a student of truck driving courses. Carefully follow the prompts that appear on the game screen and follow them unquestioningly. Try to put the truck in the parking space within the limited time in each of the stages of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking Fury 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-fury-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/parking-fury-3d/</guid>
      <description>The game Car Driving Simulator 3D Instructor was developed by leading specialists of the famous training center in Moscow. Thanks to it, you will be able to quickly navigate the implementation of the &amp;ldquo;Check in Boxing&amp;rdquo; exercise on the training ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Car`18 Simulator 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/real-car18-simulator-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/real-car18-simulator-3d/</guid>
      <description>Driving Simulator 3 turns you into a professional racer who takes part in street racing competitions. Demonstrate your skills and talent as a driver and go through all the stages of this exciting toy. You can play a cool race on your own, or you can invite one of your friends and arrange competitions. In any case, you will have a great time at the computer screen with this excellent simulator, driving a unique racing car specially prepared for competitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian UAZ 4x4 Driving Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-uaz-4x4-driving-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-uaz-4x4-driving-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Driving in Russian city</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stunt Simulator Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stunt-simulator-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stunt-simulator-multiplayer/</guid>
      <description>The Driving Simulator game invites you to become a student of a driving school. In it, you will learn how to properly maneuver in a dense stream of cars and park your car in a limited space. Each lesson at the school of professional drivers takes the form of a practical test, the time of which is limited. Try to complete the task of each stage as quickly as possible and get the maximum number of points.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
