<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For boys on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-boys/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For boys on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-boys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game For boys Freddy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-boys-freddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-boys-freddy/</guid>
      <description>At the very beginning of the game for boys Freddy, you get a job as a security guard at Freddy Fazbear&amp;rsquo;s Pizza. Funny animatronic robots serve visitors here. They create an incredibly positive atmosphere. But only during the day. At night, things begin to happen, from which the blood runs cold. Robots roam freely around the pizzeria, and it is better not to run into them at this time of day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game For boys Makvin racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-boys-makvin-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-boys-makvin-racing/</guid>
      <description>The essence of the game for boys Makvin racing is participation in speed competitions. There are no people here, and machines that can talk to each other live their own lives. And what do you think is the most common hobby these cars have? Of course, racing. And today you will drive one of the most powerful and fastest local cars, which dreams of winning the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game For boys motorcycle racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-boys-motorcycle-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-boys-motorcycle-racing/</guid>
      <description>During the online game for boys Motorcycle Racing you have to demonstrate your talents and ability to drive sports bikes. Starting to play for free driving an ultra-modern motorcycle, try not to get into an accident and collect the maximum number of gold badges, which can be used to buy new, more powerful bikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck game for boys</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-game-for-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-game-for-boys/</guid>
      <description>While playing Monster Truck for Boys, you will be the pilot of one of the huge Bigfoots participating in the world championship. You have to go through an incredible number of stages, each of which will have to demonstrate the talent of the driver and Crazy Games the maximum number of bonus points needed to buy new cars. In addition, you will have to collect additional badges that will help improve your iron monster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slenderman game for boys</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-game-for-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-game-for-boys/</guid>
      <description>While playing Slenderman for kids, you find yourself in a fantasy world, the ruler of which loves to feast on the fears of people. Carefully move across the territory of a small abandoned town, search broken houses and warehouses. Try to find a firearm as quickly as possible that can save you from a nightmarish monster.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
