<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Football 3d on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/football-3d/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Football 3d on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/football-3d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kix Dream Soccer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kix-dream-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kix-dream-soccer/</guid>
      <description>You have the opportunity to fully control the gameplay by managing the players of one of the teams. The most active player is highlighted with a yellow circle. The red crosshair indicates the place where you need to pass. The situation on the field is easily controlled, and the outcome of the match depends only on you. The opponent also does not stand still and tries to counterattack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Soccer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/smart-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/smart-soccer/</guid>
      <description>You have to play real 3D football in the stadiums of many countries. Choose your favorite team and compete against other players in the world tournament. Play a full game in two half-times, ending with a control of the players&amp;rsquo; statistics. When you Crazy Games a goal, you can even review your actions in slow motion replay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer Mob</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/soccer-mob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/soccer-mob/</guid>
      <description>Football euphoria swept the whole world. Millions of fans clung to the TV screens. At the stadium, the crowd of thousands bursts into applause. The match of the century begins. And you have the opportunity to participate in this football celebration. Choose your team and go to win victories, prizes and recognition from the audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer Stars Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/soccer-stars-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/soccer-stars-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>In this game, everything is like in real football. There are subtle passes, powerful shots, unique combinations and the highest class - when the goalkeeper Crazy Gamess a goal from his own penalty area to the opponent. To win, you need endurance, an accurate eye and a steady hand. And it does not matter that the players all the time stand still and cannot move - this does not make the game less interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
