<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beauty saloon on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/beauty-saloon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Beauty saloon on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/beauty-saloon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blonde Princess Spa Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/blonde-princess-spa-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/blonde-princess-spa-day/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to work in a beauty salon. A pretty client has already come here, who wants to receive a full set of procedures. Your task is to follow the hints of the game and use different means to improve the appearance of the heroine. Turn her into a real beauty!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candyland Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/candyland-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/candyland-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Today, the girl will have a prom, but something strange is happening to her face! You need to quickly deal with all the problems, and then make up and, of course, choose a chic ball gown. As a result, the heroine of the game will be the most beautiful at the gala event, and it&amp;rsquo;s all thanks to you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crystals Spring Spa Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crystals-spring-spa-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crystals-spring-spa-day/</guid>
      <description>While playing Spa Beauty Salon, you are invited to work on the images of cute princesses. Choose any girl you decide to make even more beautiful. Next, you will need to carry out various cosmetic procedures using the issued useful products. Process the body, face, hair of the heroine, following the prompts. The final touch will be the choice of hairstyle and outfit. At your disposal is a lot of different chic dresses, skirts, corsets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fairys Tiny Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fairys-tiny-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fairys-tiny-spa/</guid>
      <description>Work on the look of a cute girl. The game consists of several stages. First you need to carry out various cosmetic procedures for her. Next, move on to choosing a hairstyle and applying makeup. The final step will be the choice of outfit. Here at your disposal is a huge wardrobe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Queen Mountain Resort Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-mountain-resort-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-mountain-resort-spa/</guid>
      <description>The girl decided to put her legs in order. Help her in this important matter, because in the end the heroine of the game wants to get really smooth skin. Your task is to follow the prompts on the screen, choosing the right tools and cosmetics. It will be quite interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pure Princess Real Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pure-princess-real-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pure-princess-real-makeover/</guid>
      <description>After starting this exciting game, you will turn into a beautician. The task is to work on the girl&amp;rsquo;s skin problems. To do this, at your disposal is a huge number of useful cosmetics. Follow the game prompts and use the drugs as directed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping Princess Spa Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sleeping-princess-spa-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sleeping-princess-spa-day/</guid>
      <description>The girl had a hard day and now she needs a relaxing massage. Your task is to carry out this wonderful procedure. The game consists of several stages, first prepare everything you need, and then start the massage itself. Hints will help you figure it all out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Witch To Princess Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/witch-to-princess-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/witch-to-princess-makeover/</guid>
      <description>During this game you have to act as a beautician. In front of you is a client who has some skin problems. It is necessary to use useful means that will help her cope with shortcomings. Detailed tips will help you understand what to do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
