<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For boys 5 years on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-boys-5-years/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For boys 5 years on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-boys-5-years/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Paw Patrol for boys for 5 years</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-paw-patrol-for-boys-for-5-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-paw-patrol-for-boys-for-5-years/</guid>
      <description>Dogs from the Paw Patrol always try to complete their missions perfectly. In this game, you are invited to help cartoon characters cope with new tasks. Choose any of the characters to start an exciting process. You will be asked, for example, to drive a car and save ducklings or put out a fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game School defender for boys for 5 years</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-school-defender-for-boys-for-5-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-school-defender-for-boys-for-5-years/</guid>
      <description>In this interesting game you have to control a brave boy who is constantly moving forward. Along the way, it is proposed to collect coins that bring bonus points and fight enemies. A collision with an enemy will result in the loss of a game life, and you have three of them in total. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on various bonus items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles for boys 5 years old</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-for-boys-5-years-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-for-boys-5-years-old/</guid>
      <description>After launching Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles for Boys 5 years old, exciting adventures await you along with your favorite heroes. Choose any of the characters - Donatello, Leonardo, Raphael or Michelangelo, and go save the world. Here you are invited to fight with enemies, using your combat skills to the maximum.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
