<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boys dress up on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/boys-dress-up/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Boys dress up on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/boys-dress-up/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Icy Beard Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/icy-beard-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/icy-beard-makeover/</guid>
      <description>While playing Boys Dress Up, you can feel like a real dresser invited to participate in the preparation of actors for the shooting of a new youth series. Choose an original memorable image for your ward, which will be noticed by the audience who came to the premiere of the film. By dressing up the male actors, you will be able to show all your skills and talent. Create the perfect image of the hero of the series, which will become the standard of style for all his future fans for a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pocket Anime Maker</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pocket-anime-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pocket-anime-maker/</guid>
      <description>Dressing up a superhero from some famous movie or TV series has already happened. But to come up with your own superman - such an opportunity in games is extremely rare. But you&amp;rsquo;re in luck. Create your character, dress him up in a super suit, come up with a name, then save or print the picture. And then invite your friends to make the hero cooler than yours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prince Romper Squad</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/prince-romper-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/prince-romper-squad/</guid>
      <description>While playing Dress Up for Boys you have to come up with a cool look for a guy. Here you can change his appearance, choose the shape and color of his eyes, lips, skin tone and other elements. Then you can start choosing stylish clothes. A distinctive feature of the game is that it has the ability to independently choose the color of things and even decorate them with original ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rick And Morty</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rick-and-morty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rick-and-morty/</guid>
      <description>The hero of dress up game for boys and girls is going to a cool Halloween party. The only thing left is to come up with a suitable costume. You just have to do it. You can use all sorts of outfits and masks to come up with a cool look that looks cute and scary at the same time. Do not forget about suitable accessories, for example, you can give the kid a scythe or a rod of Satan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zayn Malik World Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zayn-malik-world-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zayn-malik-world-tour/</guid>
      <description>After launching the game Dress Up for Boys, you will meet a guy who wants to get a cool outfit for walking the streets. Here you will find a variety of cool things that such a badass character will definitely like. The virtual dress-up wardrobe contains t-shirts, shorts, sneakers, caps and accessories. And if you do not want to come up with an image yourself, then you can always use the random selection function.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
