<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>monster truck on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/monster-truck/</link>
    <description>Recent content in monster truck on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/monster-truck/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eggy Car</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/eggy-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/eggy-car/</guid>
      <description>An interesting game in which you have to drive an unusual car with huge wheels and a powerful engine. It is necessary to win in street races, deftly managing this maneuverable monster. Competitions take place on the most ordinary city streets. Focus on the map so as not to get lost in the intricacies of streets and roads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Spooky Roads</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-spooky-roads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-spooky-roads/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the epic off-road race, which will feature the most experienced racers in the world! On their powerful jeeps, they will have to conquer five different tracks, each of which consists of many sharp turns, climbs, descents and potholes. Your task is to be the first to the finish line, no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Spooky Roads 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-spooky-roads-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-spooky-roads-2/</guid>
      <description>Monster truck game will not allow you to relax while passing the tracks, because the higher the levels, the more difficult they are. There are a total of nine locations in the game, however, they cannot be completed if you simply hold down the acceleration button. Your goal is to get to the finish line without crashing your car. Drive your car with the arrow keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hill Riders Offroad</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hill-riders-offroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hill-riders-offroad/</guid>
      <description>After a desperate race, your monster car needs maintenance and upgrades. But before you start improving its appearance and functionality, the car should be washed. What exactly to do in a given situation will become clear from the prompts that appear at the bottom of the screen. True, the less time you spend on washing, the more will be left for a full-fledged tuning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Flip Jumps</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-flip-jumps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-flip-jumps/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you will have at your disposal not just a car, but a very heavy and fast monster truck. On it you need to overcome a rather difficult track, collect the maximum of bonuses on the way, and also spend a minimum of time on it. The good news is that the car has a very decent dynamics, which contributes to super fast acceleration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Soccer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-soccer/</guid>
      <description>monster truck</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck: Beginning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-beginning/</guid>
      <description>The Monster Truck game offers you, for starters, to choose one of three amazingly large cars. Now you can hit the road through colorful, picturesque locations, where suspension bridges, sharp ascents and descents, various kinds of landscapes and even rivers await you. Along the way, do not forget to collect all kinds of bonuses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OffRoad Extreme Car Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/offroad-extreme-car-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/offroad-extreme-car-racing/</guid>
      <description>The Monster Truck game will give you the opportunity to drive a powerful jeep with huge wheels and destroy everything that is possible on your way. Run it soon and start earning points. To do this, you will have to destroy obstacles and blow up other people&amp;rsquo;s cars. To jump on hydraulics, use the &amp;ldquo;space&amp;rdquo; key on your keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offroad Monster Trucks</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/offroad-monster-trucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/offroad-monster-trucks/</guid>
      <description>monster truck</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ride The Bus Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ride-the-bus-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ride-the-bus-simulator/</guid>
      <description>The school bus from this game has big wheels and a powerful engine. Thanks to this, he easily overcomes any obstacles. Today you have to drive this powerful car along a rather difficult track winding through the forest. Overcoming numerous obstacles, do not forget to collect stars that will allow you to move to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Extreme Offroad</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-extreme-offroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-extreme-offroad/</guid>
      <description>Immediately after launch, an excellent track for racing big cars will appear on the screen. You will have the opportunity to drive one of these monsters and take part in competitions. The main task is to overtake rivals, collecting bonuses and coins along the way. They give you the opportunity to earn some extra points.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
