<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Subway surf on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/subway-surf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Subway surf on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/subway-surf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Similar to Subway Surf</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-similar-to-subway-surf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-similar-to-subway-surf/</guid>
      <description>The hero of the game Similar to Subway Surf is professionally engaged in one of the most unique sports - parkour. Extreme occupation requires the athlete to be in excellent physical shape and reaction. Test your abilities and feel like a real parkour player. At each stage of the game, you have to go through a section of the track passing on the roofs of skyscrapers in a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Subway surfers run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-subway-surfers-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-subway-surfers-run/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to control a character who is trying to run through the underground catacombs, collecting gold coins. But the road is full of dangers and unexpected obstacles. Some of them you need to jump over, and under the rest you need to slip. Use the arrow keys to control and take the hero to the end of the level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway surf game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/subway-surf-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/subway-surf-game/</guid>
      <description>Today you have to manage a cheerful boy named Jake. Early in the morning he left the house and went for a run. But, as luck would have it, his road is teeming with all sorts of obstacles. To avoid collisions, you need to quickly press the keys with the letters that will appear on the screen. Help the young athlete overcome the distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway Surf Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/subway-surf-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/subway-surf-halloween/</guid>
      <description>While playing Subway Surf, the boy lost his beloved puppy, is terribly worried about the fate of his little pet and goes in search of him. You have to help the kid run through the streets of the town where he lives and try to find the dog. You need to play carefully, because a huge number of obstacles and dangers await him on the road, pedestrians, builders, open sewer manholes and open hydrants block your path.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
