<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Makeup on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/makeup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Makeup on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/makeup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Candy Girl Makeup Fun</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-girl-makeup-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-girl-makeup-fun/</guid>
      <description>In this interesting game you are invited to pay attention to a pretty Japanese girl. Choose her hairstyle, outfit and accessories. You can change your facial expression. And, of course, don&amp;rsquo;t forget about makeup. There is a large variety of decorative cosmetics, use any of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>College Princess Spa Makeup H</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/college-princess-spa-makeup-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/college-princess-spa-makeup-h/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game Makeup and Facial you will see Ashlyn Ella - the heroine of the animated series &amp;ldquo;Ever After High&amp;rdquo;. She always tries to look attractive, but this time something happened to the skin of her face. The situation urgently needs to be corrected! The game consists of three stages. To begin with, it is just to eliminate all problems using useful tools. Next, it is proposed to remember about makeup and apply it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Rich Asian Princesses</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-rich-asian-princesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-rich-asian-princesses/</guid>
      <description>This time you have to work on the appearance of the stewardess. At work, she should look as attractive as possible. Try to put the girl&amp;rsquo;s face in order by applying various useful tools. After that, it remains only to do makeup and choose the right suit. Change your hair too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dolly Princess Vs Villain Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dolly-princess-vs-villain-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dolly-princess-vs-villain-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will meet a cheerleader girl. She is going to the next performance, but she needs to prepare well. Take care of the appearance of the heroine of the game, using a variety of cosmetics. And, of course, after you do your makeup, choose your hairstyle and outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dotted Girl New Year Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dotted-girl-new-year-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dotted-girl-new-year-makeup/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to create stylish outfits for two charming girls at once. This is done sequentially: first work on the appearance of one girlfriend, and then move on to another. Here you can apply a variety of cosmetics, choose fashionable clothes, shoes, accessories, hairstyles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dove Trendy Dolly Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dove-trendy-dolly-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dove-trendy-dolly-makeup/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to take care of the appearance of the heroine of the game! Now she does not look her best, and your task is to eliminate all the problems that have arisen in her. Use the proposed cosmetics for this, following the game prompts. And then apply makeup and choose a hairstyle. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget about the outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellie Beauty Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-beauty-tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-beauty-tutorials/</guid>
      <description>While playing Makeup by Order, you will need to create a fashionable look for a girl who is going for a walk. Use a variety of cosmetics to apply makeup, and then start choosing an outfit. If you wish, you can use the tips and look at ready-made options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellie Coachella Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-coachella-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-coachella-makeup/</guid>
      <description>During the game for girls Face Paint, you are invited to work on the appearance of the cute princess Rapunzel. To be more precise, the girl needs to do a fashionable make-up, using all the prepared cosmetics for this. In the process of applying makeup on the face, you will be helped by detailed graphic tips pointing to the desired item. Take it and use it exactly as intended. For control, only the mouse is used, so you definitely will not have any difficulties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fairy Make Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fairy-make-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fairy-make-up/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will meet a charming fairy who decided to change her usual image a little. Choose her hair and make-up, choosing any shades of decorative cosmetics from the proposed assortment. You can use eye shadow, blush, lipstick, nail polish. The resulting image can be printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Barboskins Fashion Makeup Roses 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-barboskins-fashion-makeup-roses-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-barboskins-fashion-makeup-roses-2/</guid>
      <description>While playing Barboskiny Rose Fashion Makeover 2 you are invited to help the heroine of the famous animated series. Rosa was invited on a date by Timokha, and the girl wants to look as attractive as possible. You need to create a new cute image for her as quickly as possible, using a variety of tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goldie Emo Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldie-emo-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldie-emo-makeup/</guid>
      <description>The girl wants to attend an unusual party, and you have to help her get ready. The game consists of two stages. First you need to do makeup, and then take care of the outfit. There is an extensive wardrobe, where you will find a variety of stylish things. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget the accessories to complete your look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highschool Love Story</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/highschool-love-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/highschool-love-story/</guid>
      <description>During the game for girls Makeup you have to turn into a real make-up artist. A pretty girl will appear on the screen, and it is her image that will need to be dealt with. Choose a hairstyle for the heroine, and then start applying makeup using a variety of decorative cosmetics. Here you will find shadows, and blush, and lipstick, and many other means. Also in the game it is proposed to choose an outfit for the girl and stylish accessories suitable for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Princess Make Up Academy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-make-up-academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-make-up-academy/</guid>
      <description>Work on the appearance of the cartoon princess Elsa! This game has three stages. First you need to treat the girl&amp;rsquo;s face with useful means, then the turn of applying makeup will come. And the final stage will be the choice of hairstyles, dresses and accessories. You can print or save the finished image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty Beach Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kitty-beach-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kitty-beach-makeup/</guid>
      <description>Work on the appearance of a pretty girl. To begin with, you need to use useful products to restore beauty and health to your skin. After cosmetic procedures, it will be possible to start choosing a hairstyle, outfit, accessories, as well as applying makeup. Create an original look!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Makeup For A Star</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/makeup-for-a-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/makeup-for-a-star/</guid>
      <description>The process of the game Celebrity Makeup is dedicated to the well-known film &amp;ldquo;Twilight&amp;rdquo;. In it you will be able to change the appearance of three characters of the saga at once - Bella, Edward and Jacob. Choose any of them and immediately proceed to the transformation. You have three options for hairstyles for each hero. In addition, in the game for girls, you can change their hair color. And after that, apply makeup for the stars and choose an outfit, the color of which, by the way, can also be chosen by yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Halloween Parties</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-halloween-parties/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-halloween-parties/</guid>
      <description>Cute little mermaid Ariel, like any other girl, tries to take care of her appearance. You need to help this fabulous heroine. At your disposal is a huge variety of cosmetics, and you can use any of them. Follow the hints of the game and make Ariel a real beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Princess New Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-princess-new-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-princess-new-makeup/</guid>
      <description>Make up for girls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Zodiac Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-zodiac-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-zodiac-makeup/</guid>
      <description>Work on the appearance of a pretty girl who wants to become even more beautiful. To do this, at your disposal is a large number of various cosmetics and chic outfits. You can also change the hairstyle, which allows you to create the most harmonious options. Experiment more boldly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Mermaid Makeup Style</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-mermaid-makeup-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-mermaid-makeup-style/</guid>
      <description>Anna decided to make Elsa a pretty makeover, and you need to help the girls. Use a variety of cosmetics that are presented on the screen. Hints will help you in the gameplay. Follow them closely to make sure you get it right. So Elsa will become a real beauty!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisters Fashionista Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sisters-fashionista-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sisters-fashionista-makeup/</guid>
      <description>Face makeup for girls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stylish Makeup Look</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stylish-makeup-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stylish-makeup-look/</guid>
      <description>Take care of the appearance of the heroine of this wonderful game by creating an attractive makeover for her. Your task is to use the proposed decorative elements, trying to end up with a harmonious look. The game has not only cool cosmetics, but also a variety of decorations. Try them on!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tris Vip Dolly Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tris-vip-dolly-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tris-vip-dolly-makeup/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you have to create images for two charming girls. It is proposed to put them on make-up, as well as choose clothes, shoes and accessories. Pay attention to the hairstyle, because you have the opportunity to choose the cutest options. Work on the image of girls and admire the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Underwater Make Up Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/underwater-make-up-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/underwater-make-up-salon/</guid>
      <description>After starting this exciting game, you will turn into a beauty salon worker. A visitor came to you who wants to get rid of problems with her skin. Follow the game prompts, use the suggested tools and return the girl to her former beauty. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to apply makeup to make the heroine even prettier.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
