<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>To treat teeth on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/to-treat-teeth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in To treat teeth on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/to-treat-teeth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Audrey Real Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/audrey-real-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/audrey-real-dentist/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will see a cute girl who has a toothache. The task is to act as a dentist and eliminate all problems. Use the given tools for their intended purpose, based on the prompts. The result will be a radiant snow-white smile of the heroine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blonde Princess Real Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/blonde-princess-real-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/blonde-princess-real-dentist/</guid>
      <description>While playing Treat Barbie&amp;rsquo;s Teeth you have to help a cute girl. She has problems with her teeth, and they urgently need to be fixed in order to save the heroine of the game from discomfort. And when everything is ready, you will be asked to take care of the outfit and hairstyle. The finished image can be saved or printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Animals Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-animals-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-animals-dentist/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game Dentist Dentist for Boys, you have to become a vampire dentist. Start playing and treating your teeth by choosing the right tools and using them for their intended purpose. Tips that constantly appear on the screen when you click on the selected item will help you not get confused in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-dentist/</guid>
      <description>During the game Treat children&amp;rsquo;s teeth you have to meet a little girl. The baby has eaten too many sweets, and now her teeth are suffering. Your task is to use the proposed tools and eliminate problems with a smile. Tips will help in the treatment process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kid Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kid-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kid-dentist/</guid>
      <description>A small child suffers from unbearable toothache. Use the suggested tools to heal his cavities and pull out his rotten teeth. Do not forget to insert new teeth after removal. And you can also recolor your smile in any color you choose and apply cute drawings. The finished image can be saved or printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty Real Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kitty-real-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kitty-real-dentist/</guid>
      <description>Something terrible is happening to Angela&amp;rsquo;s cute kitty&amp;rsquo;s teeth, and it can&amp;rsquo;t go on like this. Rather, arm yourself with dental instruments to correct the situation. After you pick up one or another item, a detailed hint on its use will be displayed on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miraculous Hero Real Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/miraculous-hero-real-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/miraculous-hero-real-dentist/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to brush your teeth, removing plaque and food debris from them. The process consists of several levels, and at each one you need to correct problems with a smile in a limited time. The faster you complete the process, the more reward points you get. You can get to the next stage only after passing the previous one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noelle Real Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/noelle-real-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/noelle-real-dentist/</guid>
      <description>Gemma Atkinson needs medical attention. The fact is that her teeth hurt a lot, and only you can act as a dentist. The task is to use the proposed tools for their intended purpose. Tips on the screen will definitely help you in this exciting process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
