<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fish on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/fish/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fish on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/fish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dolphin fish game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dolphin-fish-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dolphin-fish-game/</guid>
      <description>Put on a real show with dolphins! Here you will find this smartest creature, which is able to show a variety of tricks. Your task is only to control the dolphin, directing it in the right direction. Try to attract as many people as possible to the show, otherwise you may lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fat Shark</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fat-shark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fat-shark/</guid>
      <description>Control an incredible shark that is ready to devour everyone who gets in its way. Your task is to deal with ships, planes and other objects, getting reward points for it. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to destroy people and fish as well. If you grab a plane, you will have to work hard to pull it under the water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fish-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fish-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to help a fisherman catch fish for making sushi. Dip the bait with pre-prepared bait under the water so that the fish can swallow it and get hooked. Note that different fish respond to different baits. Choose the most suitable for a big catch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Tank My Aquarium Games</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fish-tank-my-aquarium-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fish-tank-my-aquarium-games/</guid>
      <description>Fish eat fish and grow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fishing Game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fishing-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fishing-game/</guid>
      <description>Aquarium Fish game invites you to show your creativity. Here you can create your own pretty aquarium by choosing the right decorative details. The game presents an assortment of houses for fish, algae, pebbles, and decorations. Do not forget to put a fish in the aquarium and, for example, a crab or a starfish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ill Billy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ill-billy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ill-billy/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game Fish eat people, you will be asked to control a toothy shark. She is able not only to devour a fish or a person, but even to drag an airplane or helicopter under water. Your task is to Crazy Games as many reward points as possible. Move in water and air, eat everything you see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King Of Fishing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/king-of-fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/king-of-fishing/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you will control a powerful shark that sows destruction and death around. Move underwater to devour all oncoming fish and scuba divers. Jump into the air to grab a helicopter or other object that can bring you more reward points. Destroy as many vehicles as possible and eat people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Fish Factory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tiny-fish-factory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tiny-fish-factory/</guid>
      <description>The exciting Pisces game will take you to the underwater space, where you will be offered to control a small fish, which is not averse to feasting on its own kind. But you can only eat those fish that are smaller than yours. If the sea creature is larger than you, there is a danger of being eaten yourself. And this should not be allowed, so as not to lose.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
