<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Balloons on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/balloons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Balloons on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/balloons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bubbles game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubbles-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubbles-game/</guid>
      <description>An interesting combination of puzzle and adventure comics is the Bubbles game. The plot is based on the search for treasures in ancient Mayan tombs. Keys are needed to get to the gold and gems. Here they are offered to be mined by users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frogtastic</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/frogtastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/frogtastic/</guid>
      <description>While playing Zuma Deluxe 2, you will have to take part in an exciting competition, where you will have to show maximum attention and good reaction. Try not to miss a single ball from the multi-colored Zuma chains into the central hole. Knock them out online for free using a cannon with colored charges. Complete all levels of the game and prove that you are one of the best Zuma players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Balls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-balls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-balls/</guid>
      <description>Balls game invites you to a wonderful town, one of the little inhabitants of which calmly played with her favorite dolls. Suddenly, several hooligans attacked her, they showered the heroine of the game with water bombs. You have to become a hero who defended the unfortunate girl and punish the nasty boys. Stock up on water balloons, refill your water pistol and go on a hunt for hooligans who dared to offend a cute little girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Red balloon 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-red-balloon-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-red-balloon-3/</guid>
      <description>With Red Balloon 3 you have to help a funny balloonist. You need to overcome many obstacles, flying over the city, and have time to collect all the bonuses you meet on the way. Control the character with the mouse, constantly clicking the left button to climb or releasing it to lower the hero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match balls by color game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/match-balls-by-color-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/match-balls-by-color-game/</guid>
      <description>The exciting game Match Balls by Color invites you to have a great time. The screen will display a huge number of balloons that must be rotated in such a way as to eventually build combinations of four or more elements of the same color. At each level, you will be given tasks regarding how many and which balls you need to burst. Collect these balls and move on to another stage, where the rules become more complicated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
