<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Counter Strike on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/counter-strike/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Counter Strike on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/counter-strike/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Strike</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cartoon-strike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cartoon-strike/</guid>
      <description>The Contra City game is a classic representative of the “shooter” genre, in which everything depends, first of all, not on the completed tasks, but on your marksmanship. Here you will not be able to run around the map in a relaxed way, find unique items and kill everyone you meet. Everything is simpler and at the same time more difficult: you move quietly, calculate the location of the enemy and get closer by dashes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contra game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/contra-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/contra-game/</guid>
      <description>You have to participate in a secret operation on enemy territory. Carefully make your way through the forest, trying to get close to the enemy from the rear. The main task is to eliminate the terrorist camp. Your machine gun is equipped with a silencer and a scope, which will allow you to silently take out the base guards. You can aim and shoot with the mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contra Strike game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/contra-strike-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/contra-strike-game/</guid>
      <description>You have to complete the task of the commander - to destroy a large terrorist group that has occupied the abandoned territory of the military base. As part of a special forces group, try to clear the area from all enemies and not get under fire yourself. The weapon reloads automatically, so you just have to make well-aimed shots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>counter strike game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/counter-strike-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/counter-strike-game/</guid>
      <description>Those who like to shoot and run along the intricate corridors are familiar with the Counter-Strike game and, as before, is a first-person team shooter. Today, there are a huge number of versions of this magnificent and realistic shooting game. In ours, you have the opportunity to fight both against bots in a single company, and as part of a team, by downloading the level from the server. Before the start of the battle, the Counter Strike game gives you the opportunity to decide which side you will play on: terrorists or special forces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game counter strike against counters and zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-counter-strike-against-counters-and-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-counter-strike-against-counters-and-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Terrible, evil mutants surround you from all sides. Help is nowhere to be found. Here you are on your own. Lucky that there is a gun and an almost endless supply of ammunition. But you have to run, because the monsters appear unexpectedly, and sometimes there is not enough time to destroy them all at once. After each level, you have the opportunity to replenish ammo in the store.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
