<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dragons on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/dragons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dragons on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/dragons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dragon game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dragon-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dragon-game/</guid>
      <description>The game Dragon will be of interest, first of all, to small gamers. The main character himself is drawn in a very funny way, in the style of children&amp;rsquo;s cartoons, and the surroundings match him well. The rules are simple: run forward, jump over gaps, collect coins. Enemies can either be burned with fire (so as not to injure the child&amp;rsquo;s psyche, the fire looks like a sound wave, and the enemies simply disappear), or jump on their heads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game How to Train Your Dragon 2 - Card Match</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-how-to-train-your-dragon-2---card-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-how-to-train-your-dragon-2---card-match/</guid>
      <description>In front of you on the screen will be located twelve cards face down. Behind each of them is an image of a dragon or one of Berk&amp;rsquo;s riders. During the game, you must open the cards one by one and find pairs of identical pictures. When all of them are collected, a hidden image with a frame from the cartoon &amp;ldquo;How to Train Your Dragon&amp;rdquo; will appear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game How to train your dragon 2 - dangerous flights</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-how-to-train-your-dragon-2---dangerous-flights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-how-to-train-your-dragon-2---dangerous-flights/</guid>
      <description>A colorful and addictive game invites you to choose one of 4 dragons and go flying. To do this is not at all easy, you need to be able to dodge obstacles in the form of thunderclouds and stones flying from the sky. It is also necessary to collect sheep to restore energy and, preferably, not to catch on a rock and not crash into an iceberg.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
