<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mario 3 on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/mario-3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mario 3 on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/mario-3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1985</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/1985/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/1985/</guid>
      <description>It is not clear to whom and for what Mario is going to take revenge. Although it seems that they are taking revenge on him for all the turtles killed during the campaigns. So, you control a mustachioed Italian who runs around a closed room, and two large turtles fire at him with balls. Sooner or later the character will die. But you must have time to score more points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario FPS</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mario-fps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mario-fps/</guid>
      <description>Mario turned out to be not only a tourist, but also a fly agaric lover. Apparently, for this reason, he is worn like mad. Your task is to help the brave plumber collect mushrooms and get to the end of the level. It will not be very easy, but all because of the speed of movement of the character. So you have to get used to the controls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Invaders</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mario-invaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mario-invaders/</guid>
      <description>Calmly! There will be no need to drop nuclear bombs on anyone. You need to fight only with the monsters in the labyrinth, and even then, as a last resort. In general, your goal is to free the princess. The game has a mode for two players at the same time. At the same time, you can control the characters from one keyboard without interfering with each other. Before starting the game, it is better to familiarize yourself with the controls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/new-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/new-platform/</guid>
      <description>The main feature of the game can be considered, perhaps, the mode for two players at the same time. In this case, someone will control Mario himself, and someone - his girlfriend. The task is simple, as in all Mario games - you need to reach the end of the level, collecting as many bonuses as possible and not sticking flippers together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Alfonso</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-alfonso/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-alfonso/</guid>
      <description>Manage Mario this time will not have to. This rogue dug up an ownerless piece of gold somewhere and is now dragging it to a pawnshop. But the path is full of traps. Your task is to provide him with a safe path to the pawnshop using the correct placement of blocks. It is not always possible to do this the first time, but if you try, Mario will reach the collection point of precious metals alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Mario Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-mario-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-mario-rush/</guid>
      <description>The jungle is full of dangers. Killer turtles, cannibal bunches, brain-biting woodpeckers scurry about everywhere, and there are enough predatory plants. But Mario is not afraid of this. Especially if you manage it. Collect bananas and various tropical fruits. Monsters can be jumped over or trampled. To go to the next level, you need a portal to appear. It will appear when you collect the required amount of fruit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Mario Rush 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-mario-rush-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-mario-rush-2/</guid>
      <description>The Mario 3 game, with all its simplicity, can provide you with many pleasant minutes. The gameplay is simple: the main character goes forward through the location, collects money and stomps the monsters. And so from level to level. At the beginning of each level, a task is given. For example, collect a certain number of coins or kill a monster. Only when this condition is met, you can go to the next stage, reaching the blue flag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super World Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-world-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-world-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Unusual game, but interesting. To go to the next level, you need to get the key and climb to the very top. And initially, Mario is on the bottom log. Hatches move along the log, through which you can fall through or rise to the floor above, if you manage to jump into the hatch. Everything would be fine if it weren&amp;rsquo;t for the bird that knocks out Mario in any, even an accidental, collision.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
