<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Geometry Dash on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/geometry-dash/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Geometry Dash on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/geometry-dash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Frenzied Cube</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/frenzied-cube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/frenzied-cube/</guid>
      <description>At any time of the day, you can play for free (until you get bored) the fantastically popular online project Geometry Dash 4 in the world. A typical platformer awaits on the screen. The bottom line is that the cube slides from left to right, to the transition to the next level (by the way, the coolest one is 4), and you must prevent it from colliding with obstacles and traps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geo Dash</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/geo-dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/geo-dash/</guid>
      <description>Gambling online platformer &amp;ldquo;Geometry Dash: Cube Adventures&amp;rdquo; consists of 21 levels of varying difficulty. At the start of the game, they all open for free and immediately. But, if you have never played Geometry Dash up to this point, it is better to start the passage from the beginning, gradually moving towards the end. The main character is a cartoon cube, running through a location full of all sorts of obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geometry Dash Horror</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-dash-horror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-dash-horror/</guid>
      <description>The locations of the online game &amp;ldquo;Geometry Dash: Dungeon Escape&amp;rdquo; are a gloomy, confusing labyrinth. Its numerous corridors are littered with traps, like a hedgehog with needles. It&amp;rsquo;s worth hitting even one when the game is over. The task of the gamer is to help the main character, the cube, escape from the gloomy place to freedom. To do this, you need to find the yellow door - the transition to the next stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geometry Dash Jump</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-dash-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-dash-jump/</guid>
      <description>The protagonist of the gambling online arcade - a black ball, goes in search of treasures. You can keep him company for free. The game location looks like an ancient Indonesian temple with a lot of artifacts. The task of the character is to collect as many of them as possible. The difficulty is that the ancient monks, leaving their native monastery, set up many traps inside it. It is necessary to please one, and the game will immediately end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geometry Jump</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-jump/</guid>
      <description>He prepared the biggest difficulties for users when passing the online project &amp;ldquo;Geometry Dash&amp;rdquo; level 5. If you&amp;rsquo;re a weakling, it will make your eyes bleed. Only users with steel ropes instead of nerves and ultra-modern mice are able to overcome everything that the game will present them. By the way, access to it is provided for free. When you start playing, you will understand that it&amp;rsquo;s not about geometry, but about your reaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geometry Neon Dash Subzero</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-neon-dash-subzero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-neon-dash-subzero/</guid>
      <description>The online project &amp;ldquo;Geometry dash subzero&amp;rdquo; quickly became popular. Schoolchildren around the world are fighting for the right to play it, but only you can do it for free. Be proud and download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geometry Neon Dash World 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-neon-dash-world-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-neon-dash-world-2/</guid>
      <description>Geometry Dash: Neon Jump is a new addition to the Geometry Dash series of gambling platform games. To go through it to the end, you will need attentiveness. Use the mouse to control. Press her left button every time the main character - a cartoon cube, there will be some kind of obstacle. It will be difficult to play because the terrain of locations is changing all the time. Just get used to the horizontal passage, as it will be replaced by a vertical movement from the bottom up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geometry Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/geometry-rush/</guid>
      <description>The gameplay of the online game &amp;ldquo;Geometry Dash for Girls&amp;rdquo; is no different from the same arcade games for boys. Unless the design of the location is brighter. You have to play in exactly the same way: by clicking the mouse in time, help the cartoon cube to overcome obstacles for free. Passage includes two dozen levels. First, the main character moves on the ground, and then soars into the air on a small painted rocket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am The Ninja 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/i-am-the-ninja-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/i-am-the-ninja-2/</guid>
      <description>The main character is a tiny ninja. The enemies caught him and locked him in an abandoned monastery on a high mountain. The player&amp;rsquo;s task is to help the hero escape from prison for free. The difficulty is that only one narrow path leads to the valley from the monastery. The villains set deadly traps and barriers on her. You need to play so as not to get into any of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impossible Lite Dash</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/impossible-lite-dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/impossible-lite-dash/</guid>
      <description>The online game &amp;ldquo;Geometry Dash: Light&amp;rdquo; differs from other arcade games in the series by the unusual vertical structure of the location. The main character - a square with eyes, moves across the screen not from left to right, as usual, but from bottom to top. The player&amp;rsquo;s task is to direct the character&amp;rsquo;s movements so that he can quickly get out of the deep mine. Use the mouse to control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scratch Geometry Dash</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/scratch-geometry-dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/scratch-geometry-dash/</guid>
      <description>The online project &amp;ldquo;Geometry dash world&amp;rdquo; has enslaved the minds of millions of schoolchildren. Do you want to test your reaction and stress resistance for free? Start playing. In fact, &amp;ldquo;Geometry dash full version&amp;rdquo; is a typical platform game. Easy to perform, but very difficult to pass the first time. You have to control the cube, which slides from left to right. Your task during the game is to click the mouse in time and make the hero jump over obstacles and traps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sliding Box</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sliding-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sliding-box/</guid>
      <description>The online game &amp;ldquo;Geometry Dash: Cubes&amp;rdquo; offers, together with a small square, to jump over obstacles from platform to platform. The goal is survival. On all sides of the protagonist, obstacles lie in wait: spikes, abysses, hungry monsters, etc. There are no bonuses and free spare lives for the cube in Geometry Dash. You have to play on your own strength. To stay in the game longer, the cube will have to move on the ground, soar in the air and even run along the ceiling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Square Jump</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/square-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/square-jump/</guid>
      <description>Here is a new arcade survival platformer from the Geometry Dash series. It is so captivating and passionate that it is impossible to tear yourself away. But get ready for the fact that the game will be difficult. Especially if you don&amp;rsquo;t have much of a reaction. The protagonist is a big-eyed cube, moving along a picturesque rocky location dotted with abysses, steep ascents and descents. It is worth even once to stumble, as the character will fall down and break into a cake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Square Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/square-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/square-run/</guid>
      <description>About the online project &amp;ldquo;Geometry dash 2 2&amp;rdquo; it&amp;rsquo;s hard to say that this is a simulator of something. Before you is a typical platformer with a very simple goal, but not an easy passage. To play, the user will need a lot of patience and strong nerves. And also the Internet. The character is a cube with a cheerful face, sliding from left to right. The gamer&amp;rsquo;s task is to help him perform the jump in time, avoiding collisions with obstacles and traps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Impossible Dash</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-impossible-dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-impossible-dash/</guid>
      <description>The popular online platformer &amp;ldquo;Incredible Geometry Dash&amp;rdquo; is available to play for free. But do you have enough patience and enough direct hands? Start playing and test yourself. The character you control looks like a cube with a mouth and eyes. He slides from one part of the screen to another, and you have to save this mindless creature from collisions with various obstacles. Just click the left mouse button to make the hero jump at the right moment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
