<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Action games for boys on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/action-games-for-boys/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Action games for boys on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/action-games-for-boys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bear Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bear-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bear-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Controlling a cyborg soldier, you have to find the enemy&amp;rsquo;s lair and destroy everyone who is there. To do this, you can use a whole arsenal of the most modern weapons and various tricks. For defeating the enemy, some cash is required. They can be spent on buying more powerful weapons and other improvements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowy Kitty Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/snowy-kitty-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/snowy-kitty-adventure/</guid>
      <description>The essence of the Adventure Adventure game for boys is to destroy all the enemy soldiers on the level. Controlling a brave commando, run, jump, collect ammunition and ruthlessly kill enemies. But the enemy is also firing, so during the passage of missions, do not be lazy to collect first-aid kits that restore health. You have to go through 6 challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vex 4</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/vex-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/vex-4/</guid>
      <description>Terrorists have captured a desert island with a military laboratory, and you need to quickly neutralize the bandits. By helicopter you are delivered to the thick of things. Pick up a laser gun and get ready for a brutal fight. But try not to reveal your presence on the island for a longer time. If an enemy sees you, eliminate him immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warrior And Coins</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/warrior-and-coins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/warrior-and-coins/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will become a participant in a bloody battle with terrible zombies. We have to defend a small tower, which has two exits and a machine-gun nest on the roof, but there are no cartridges. They are to be dropped by parachute shortly. In the meantime, shoot back with a shotgun and try not to let the monsters close to the tower.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
