<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kill zombies on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/kill-zombies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kill zombies on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/kill-zombies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angry Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/angry-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/angry-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Grandfather Nikifor lived quietly in his farm and did not know grief until he accidentally met a terrible zombie in the forest. Grandfather was not a timid ten, but still decided to leave on a tractor from his farm to a distant city. Unfortunately, the iron horse has long been broken. Help the brave old man fight off the attacks of the bloodthirsty dead and collect the parts needed to fix the tractor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apocalypse World</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/apocalypse-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/apocalypse-world/</guid>
      <description>One of the hot dog vendors ordered a new portion of ketchup, but instead, suspicious people handed him some strange substance. The hero of the game had no choice but to use it as a gas station. Having tasted hot dogs, customers turned into zombies, eager to gobble up as much of this delicacy as possible. Help the character fight off the attacks of nightmarish monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cowboy Shoot Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cowboy-shoot-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cowboy-shoot-zombies/</guid>
      <description>The owner of one of the salons in a small Texas town has offered you a dangerous task. You must destroy the zombie horde that has taken over part of the city. Go to fight monsters and try to eliminate as many dead people as possible. For the head of each of them, you will receive gold coins from the employer, for which you can buy new weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realistic Zombie Survival Warfare</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/realistic-zombie-survival-warfare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/realistic-zombie-survival-warfare/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to clean up the city cemetery, which has a huge number of zombies. On each of the locations you have to destroy all the monsters using a limited amount of ammo. Calculate the flight path of each of the bullets so that it causes maximum damage to the monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Legendary zombie hunter Shotgun embarks on a dangerous mission to test a new type of shotgun. Help the hero of the game complete the assigned mission. Try to destroy all the monsters on the locations. After each successful battle, you will have the opportunity to improve the characteristics of the Shotgun rifle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
