<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Minecraft 2d on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/minecraft-2d/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Minecraft 2d on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/minecraft-2d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Block Ninja HD</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/block-ninja-hd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/block-ninja-hd/</guid>
      <description>Go through the levels that make up the exciting game Minecraft 2d. On your way objects from squares will appear, with which you can do whatever you want - destroy, build and explore new lands. There are no restrictions on the passage of the Minecraft game. You can become a creator, a fisherman, a carpenter and even a musician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecraft-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecraft-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>A real find for all adventure lovers. Help the boy who, according to the terms of the Minecraft 2D game, fell asleep at the lesson and ended up in an unknown world. He will have to fight with strange cubic creatures of pink color with heads that look like hammers. And even if this 2d-world is only a dream, it is undesirable to expose yourself to the blows of monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Memory Match</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecraft-memory-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/minecraft-memory-match/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will be a wizard. But do not expect that everything will be easy and simple. The Minecraft 2D game with mods is a lot of tests, during which you will have to destroy a large number of enemies on your way. At your disposal are various magic wands, potions, swords and much more. But the main goal is to defeat the evil magician.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
