<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aircraft on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/aircraft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aircraft on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/aircraft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>After Burner</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/after-burner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/after-burner/</guid>
      <description>Airplanes for kids game will make you feel like a pilot performing a responsible combat mission. It is necessary not only to destroy enemy planes and equipment, but also to collect all the bonuses in flight. In addition, you need to overcome several difficult obstacles in the form of air corridors, flying through them without hitting a single wall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airplane Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/airplane-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/airplane-battle/</guid>
      <description>In the game Airplanes you have to become an English fighter pilot who takes part in fierce battles with the German air force. Enemy aircraft can be seen on the locator screen in the upper right corner before they enter the field of view. And you will complete tasks together with brave pilots who will help you win this battle for Britain. Use all your skills to destroy enemy aircraft and prevent the enemy from breaking through deep into the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airplane Fight</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/airplane-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/airplane-fight/</guid>
      <description>The Airplane Simulator game consists of three separate levels in which you will have to sit at the controls of different models of cars. The first mission is to control a small sports monoplane. Your task is to land the car in the right place. Starting to play the second mission, you will find yourself in the cockpit of a modern passenger liner, which is quite difficult to manage. In the process of playing about aircraft simulators, the most important thing is not to lose control of a huge machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airplane Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/airplane-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/airplane-memory/</guid>
      <description>According to the rules of the Airplane Control game, you have to become a carrier-based fighter pilot. Take off from an aircraft carrier and try to destroy all enemy targets indicated on the radar. But you must not only effectively attack the enemy, but also be able to masterfully dodge enemy missiles, otherwise you will not be able to fulfill the order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airplanes Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/airplanes-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/airplanes-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Airplane 94 game will give you the opportunity to fly a paper model of an airplane. But you need to try to make it so that it flies as far as possible. At the first levels, you will have to earn money to further improve the glider. Then you can purchase wind turbines that will increase its flight range by 94 percent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airwingsio</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/airwingsio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/airwingsio/</guid>
      <description>During the Aircraft War game, you need to complete a responsible combat mission. You have to fight alone with the best fighters of the enemy army. Complete a short training course and go into battle. Don&amp;rsquo;t let the enemy get behind you, in this case he can easily knock out your car. Upgrade the plane by purchasing all kinds of equipment in the workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Def Island</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/def-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/def-island/</guid>
      <description>While playing Planes Tu 95 you have to learn how to fly a Soviet strategic bomber. With the help of an instructor, you must take off at one airfield and land at another. But at the same time, the Aircraft Tu 95 game gives you the opportunity to exercise full control over the state of the aircraft in flight. These are altitude, speed, flap position, and so on. The game is primarily aimed at boys and challenges them to complete several challenging missions including mid-air refueling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fighter Aircraft</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fighter-aircraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fighter-aircraft/</guid>
      <description>While playing Airport and Planes you will get an idea of ​​how a small airport works. You will have to make decisions on the order of landing of aircraft. There are many aircraft in the air, and there are only two runways. It is necessary to calculate everything in such a way that the cars do not interfere with each other when landing and do not collide in the air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panda Commander</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/panda-commander/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/panda-commander/</guid>
      <description>In the course of the game for boys Airplanes you have to become a pilot of an ultra-modern fighter. These machines are the first to defend the air spaces at the slightest danger to the state. In modern warfare, a high-speed and well-armed aircraft plays a big role. Pilots are the first to take on enemy attacks and become a shield for the enemy army. In this game for kids, your task is not to let the invader into your territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panda Commander Air Combat</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/panda-commander-air-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/panda-commander-air-combat/</guid>
      <description>Airplanes game is a very realistic and exciting shooter. You have to control a military fighter, and your task is to destroy enemy military equipment. First you need to choose a pilot, then decide on a suitable aircraft model, equip it with the necessary weapons and ammunition. After that, you can start the mission. If you have already raised your winged machine into the sky, then get down to business - destroy enemy objects, adjust artillery fire, intercept enemy bombers and engage in heated battles with enemy pilots.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
