<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3d for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/3d-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3d for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/3d-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Basketball Stars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/basketball-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/basketball-stars/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will not have the opportunity to relax. You need to often, often throw the ball into the basket, if, of course, you want to become a better basketball player. Choose your player and join the battle. The computer will pick up an opponent and load the location for the battle. You only have three minutes to show that there is only one real basketball player on this court.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game sushi battle for two 3d</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-sushi-battle-for-two-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-sushi-battle-for-two-3d/</guid>
      <description>Quite an interesting game where you have to meet in a duel with your best friend or a computer. Controlling your character, try to cut the rope on which a huge ball dangles. But you need to do this so that the ball falls on the opponent&amp;rsquo;s head. And then you will win. Use the A and D keys to control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krunker.io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/krunker.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/krunker.io/</guid>
      <description>An interesting game that will require players to be smart and precise. You and your opponent will find yourself on a white square, gradually breaking up into smaller parts. The task is to jump on the remaining pieces of the platform and hold out as long as possible. Use the arrow keys to control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Checkers Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/master-checkers-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/master-checkers-multiplayer/</guid>
      <description>Play good old checkers according to simple, &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo; rules. The blue ones go first, a simple checker moves only forward one cell. You can hit an opponent both forward and backward. If it is possible to remove more than one enemy piece, they beat the entire chain. The winner is the one who removed from the field or blocked all the opponent&amp;rsquo;s chips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raging Punch 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/raging-punch-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/raging-punch-3d/</guid>
      <description>In this game you can fight in the final boxing match with the computer or the second player. Use the arrow keys to control the fighter. The game has several locations and a wide variety of boxing techniques. To defeat an opponent, you need to accurately strike and be able to quickly restore strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed Brazil</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/speed-brazil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/speed-brazil/</guid>
      <description>Take part in a racing tournament, fighting against the computer or competing with friends. Choose your favorite car, track for the race and go to the start. To go to the next level, you need to be the first to the finish line. But keep in mind, each subsequent race is more difficult than the previous one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
