<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Optimus Prime on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/optimus-prime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Optimus Prime on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/optimus-prime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Energon Rally Game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/energon-rally-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/energon-rally-game/</guid>
      <description>The Autobots, along with Opitmus Prime, decided to have some fun and staged a racing competition outside the city. As you know, each of them can take the form of a cool and fast car. Choose one of the transformers to drive and start the race. There are only 10 levels in the game, start from the first and go through them all, reaching the finish line first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Titans Return</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/titans-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/titans-return/</guid>
      <description>Today you have to show your abilities as a strategist and tactician. The Decepticons approach the Autobot stronghold. Your task is to place combat robots at posts in such a way as to prevent the capture of the citadel. At the beginning of the game, you can only use four transformers. Then you can buy warriors for points received for killed enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformers: Dinobot Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/transformers-dinobot-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/transformers-dinobot-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Transformers are amazing creatures. They can become something useful in an instant, such as a truck, an airplane, and so on. But robots not only fight wars and help people, sometimes they also have fun. Although in this turbulent time, it is unlikely that it will be possible to simply have fun. There will always be someone worth killing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformers: Protect Crown City</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/transformers-protect-crown-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/transformers-protect-crown-city/</guid>
      <description>The Decepticons attacked the Earth and now the Autobots need to protect people. In this game you will defend the city. Arrange cyborgs on the roofs of buildings, organizing an ambush for enemy units. Each robot has its own fire parameters, which can be further upgraded. Use your knowledge of military tactics to effectively repel any enemy attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
