<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zombies 2 on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/zombies-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zombies 2 on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/zombies-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eg Zombies City</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-zombies-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-zombies-city/</guid>
      <description>During the game for two Zombie 2 you will be asked to fight against hordes of evil spirits. First you need to choose one of the two characters that you will control, or a couple at once if you plan to play for two. Then you can safely proceed to clean up game locations from zombies. Move around the screen and shoot zombies and other monsters that are coming from all sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel SWAT Zombie Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-swat-zombie-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-swat-zombie-survival/</guid>
      <description>The game takes you to a terrible dimension that has been taken over by zombies. In order to escape from this nightmare, you need to get to the science center. The quarter created in it is able to bring you back. Along the way, you need to destroy entire hordes of bloodthirsty dead, who dream of feasting on your flesh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuk Tuk Crazy Driver</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tuk-tuk-crazy-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tuk-tuk-crazy-driver/</guid>
      <description>An explosion occurred at a chemical plant somewhere in the interior of Canada, and most of the population of this area turned into zombies. Help three brave friends escape from this nightmare. Control the actions of the team and the car on which they move. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to take breaks and explore the abandoned buildings. There you can find food, weapons and fuel for your car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Crowd</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-crowd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-crowd/</guid>
      <description>Zombie Death Part 2 invites you to play as a kid who needs to protect his motorcycle from the undead attacking him. Use the available weapons to deal with the zombies and move on to the next level. As you progress, you will open a new weapon, more powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Drive</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-drive/</guid>
      <description>A terrible period has come for the city: zombies crawl out of the ground and attack people. But you will be saved by a powerful jeep, which will be provided by the game Crush Zombie 2. You need to move around the game locations on it and destroy the resurrected dead that come across on the way. You should also destroy cars, boxes and other objects on the road, for which you can get even more reward points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Trigger</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-trigger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-trigger/</guid>
      <description>During the game for two Zombie Crypt 2 you will get into a dangerous dungeon together with your friend. You need to move around the location, collecting coins and running away from enemies in order to eventually get to the exit. Often there will be obstacles, which you can get rid of with the help of levers or buttons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
