<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arcade on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/arcade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arcade on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/arcade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Helix Piano Tiles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/helix-piano-tiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/helix-piano-tiles/</guid>
      <description>The Arcade game offers you to help the guy collect all the notes in order to make a melody out of them. There are several levels, and on each of them you will find an intricate labyrinth. Move around it, collecting notes and avoiding the skull-and-bones enemy. If he suddenly overtakes you, you will lose. There is a limited time to complete any level, and you need to act as quickly as possible in order to Crazy Games the required number of points and move on to the next stage of an exciting arcade game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Dubstep</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mr.-dubstep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mr.-dubstep/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to go to the virtual world and get a lot of vivid impressions? Then feel free to run this wonderful game. A lot of interesting things await you in it: various levels, unusual characters, dangerous enemies that you need to defeat. It will definitely be unforgettable, and you will not be able to tear yourself away from the gameplay for a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Orc</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rolling-orc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rolling-orc/</guid>
      <description>While playing Arcade for Boys, you will need to fight enemies. The process consists of a large number of levels, on each of which you need to destroy the evil monster. As you progress, you will earn gold coins, which you can then spend on a variety of improvements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Ultimate Street Fighter 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-ultimate-street-fighter-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-ultimate-street-fighter-3d/</guid>
      <description>Fight your enemies by choosing a funny boy character. Also indicate the location where you will fight with rivals. Next, you need to strike opponents, taking away their health points. From time to time, boxes with useful items will appear on the location, try to pick them up immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
