<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mini Minecraft on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/mini-minecraft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mini Minecraft on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/mini-minecraft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Block Craft 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/block-craft-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/block-craft-3d/</guid>
      <description>Great arcade games Sonic Minecraft will introduce you to a funny cartoon character who cannot stand in one place for a second and is constantly moving somewhere. Keep him company and start either passing the round, destroying the enemies you meet and collecting coins, or fight with the enemy in the arena, trying to throw him into the abyss. The main task is to help Sonic rise as high as possible in the standings of the Minecraft world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coloring Bloxy Boy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/coloring-bloxy-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/coloring-bloxy-boy/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you can practice creating a character for the popular Minecraft game. There are a lot of settings at your disposal. You can start creating a character from scratch or download one of the ready-made characters. In the image simulation mode, you can customize every detail. At an additional level, you can change clothes, accessories, and even body parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyborg Slayer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cyborg-slayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cyborg-slayer/</guid>
      <description>You got into a hostile world, in order to survive here, you need to fight. Minecraft robot games offer a boxing ring as an arena for battle, where giant iron cars are waiting for you. Powerful blows that you will inflict on the enemy should knock him down. Don&amp;rsquo;t let up for a second. To protect against enemy attacks, try to block more often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Soccer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Football with gloomy zombies is more of a battle than a competition. First, in the process of playing Minecraft football, you need to destroy all the defenders and the goalkeeper, and then Crazy Games a goal into an empty net. Your partner will serve the ball, and your task is to strike as accurately as possible. And remember, if the goalkeeper gets to you, the game can be considered lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-survival/</guid>
      <description>According to the plot of the Minecraft 15 game, you need to help a funny creature get out of the underground labyrinths. Dangerous adventures, clever traps and terrible monsters await you on your way to freedom. Destroy the monsters with the weapons provided in the game and do not forget to collect the treasures located in the depths of the labyrinths.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
