<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beat Dropper</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/beat-dropper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/beat-dropper/</guid>
      <description>DJ music</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Piano Tiles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-piano-tiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-piano-tiles/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to enter the dance competition! But first, choose the character you want to control. Then it remains only to correctly press the arrow buttons, the symbols of which appear on the screen. This should be done only at the moment when the symbol falls exactly into the marked area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DJ Shaq</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dj-shaq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dj-shaq/</guid>
      <description>Game Create your own music DJ invites you to create a variety of melodies. In front of you is a DJ set with two turntables. You need to rotate them in such a way as to catch the notes. Caught should be exactly those elements that are indicated at the top of the screen. If you make a mistake, the game will end. But if you do everything right, the next level, more difficult, will open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elsa Rock Vs Hip Hop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-rock-vs-hip-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-rock-vs-hip-hop/</guid>
      <description>The girls decided to create their own musical group, and you need to help them become famous. The game consists of several levels, and on each of them the heroines must demonstrate their talents. Click on the buttons, the symbols of which are displayed above the head of each girl, to get reward points. Progress is displayed on the scale in the form of a disk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic Easter Tiles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/magic-easter-tiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/magic-easter-tiles/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to help a little bird. The screen displays moving notes, which sequentially fall into the screen frame. You need to quickly tap on the corresponding note at the bottom of the screen to lock the symbol. If you make mistakes too often, trouble will happen to the bird.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic Piano Tiles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/magic-piano-tiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/magic-piano-tiles/</guid>
      <description>After starting the Musical Instruments game, you will see the well-known traveler Dasha. She offers to create great melodies using different instruments for this. So, on the screen you will see a guitar, maracas, a flute and other objects that make pleasant sounds. You just need to click on the instrument you like to start playing. Do not forget to choose the speed of the melody, the buttons under the singing objects are designed for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Board</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/music-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/music-board/</guid>
      <description>When you play Make Music, you will turn into a DJ. Before you will be a special installation, and you can use all its features. Click on the available buttons and watch the result. The process is not limited to anyone and nothing, just experiment and enjoy a variety of compositions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Line Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/music-line-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/music-line-christmas/</guid>
      <description>The Music game will introduce you to Santa Claus, who loves rock. Play one of the songs with the brutal grandfather! To do this, you have a powerful guitar at your disposal. Colored elements move across the screen, and you just have to press the corresponding buttons. Note that sometimes you need to hold down a key to get the desired effect. The difficulty level is selected before the process starts, and you can also specify the melody you are going to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Piano Online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/piano-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/piano-online/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game Music on the piano, you will see Disney princesses. They invite you to come up with your own melodies. Click on the microphone button and start recording. Just play the already familiar compositions on the virtual piano or try to compose your own. When you finish this process, the finished music can be listened to. A total of three slots are available for recording melodies. Of course, if you suddenly don&amp;rsquo;t like an option, you can always delete it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talking Tom Piano Time</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/talking-tom-piano-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/talking-tom-piano-time/</guid>
      <description>The process of making music will turn you into a real composer. In it, you can invent your own melodies, which will be immediately performed by a team of professional musicians. On the screen you will see a trinity of great guys who know a lot about quality music. Two guitarists and a drummer will help you deal with the creation of compositions. Above the group there is a special field where you need to drive in digital values ​​that will tell the game characters what exactly needs to be done at the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tayler Schwift Vs Khanye East Parody Bat</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tayler-schwift-vs-khanye-east-parody-bat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tayler-schwift-vs-khanye-east-parody-bat/</guid>
      <description>Help the stars of the music world perform new compositions. To do this, simply click on the indicated arrow buttons. You should not make a mistake, because three mistakes will definitely lead to a loss. Gradually, the game becomes more difficult, and you need to react as quickly as possible to what is happening on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheels On The Bus</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheels-on-the-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheels-on-the-bus/</guid>
      <description>Deer, bear, penguin and other animals decided to record their own melody. You need to help them in this exciting business. Start recording and click on any character whose voice you want to add. After you finish creating a composition, you can listen to it. Create different options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xmas Magic Tiles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/xmas-magic-tiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/xmas-magic-tiles/</guid>
      <description>Tom and Angela decided to have a great disco. Help them record cool musical compositions. To do this, press any button on the DJ setup controlled by the cat Tom. To record a melody, you must click on the microphone icon. Three musical options are available for saving.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
