<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Puzzles on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/puzzles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Puzzles on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/puzzles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Block Riddle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/block-riddle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/block-riddle/</guid>
      <description>While playing Riddles Magic Story you have to help a funny dwarf get a precious stone. At each level you will see a room full of different obstacles. It is necessary to cut the ropes on which the stone is suspended so that it rolls to the gnome. Avoid evil enemies and collect coins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Puppies Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-puppies-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-puppies-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>While playing Barboskin&amp;rsquo;s puzzles, you get to know the smallest member of the family of amazing dogs. Playing with a family photo album, the Kid accidentally cut a photo with scissors, which depicts all the children in the family. During the game for girls you have to help a little puppy to put together a photo from a huge number of individual pieces. Carefully inspect the playing field and find a place for each piece of the puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dino Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>While playing Jigsaw Dinosaurs, you become one of the participants in a unique program to recreate ancient dinosaurs. You need to assemble an image of a Tyrannosaurus Rex from separate pieces. While moving the puzzles around the playing field, try to choose the right place for each of them and show your friend a photo of this terrible monster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fishing Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fishing-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fishing-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>This puzzle game invites you to sink to the bottom of the world&amp;rsquo;s oceans and admire the picturesque scenery of one of the coral reefs. Try to assemble the whole puzzle as quickly as possible from a huge number of separate pieces, because there is a competition among the participants of this game, and the best results will be posted on the developers&amp;rsquo; website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2018 Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-2018-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-2018-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to assemble a picture of an autumn road from separate pieces. Carefully inspect each of the puzzle pieces and try to place it correctly on the electronic easel. By combining all the elements, you can fully enjoy the picturesque landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw Puzzle Flowers</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jigsaw-puzzle-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jigsaw-puzzle-flowers/</guid>
      <description>The Flower puzzle game will require you to be attentive and have excellent logical thinking. You have to collect wonderful photos depicting beautiful flowers from separate pieces. The authors of the game offer players two modes: in one of them you have to collect puzzles for a while, and in the second, enjoy the unhurried collection of magnificent pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masha And The Bear Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/masha-and-the-bear-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/masha-and-the-bear-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>The heroes of Jigsaw puzzles for girls Masha and the Bear decided to create an album with frames from the animated series with their participation. A huge photo book was bought, and inseparable friends sat down at a large table to examine their photos and organize them in an album. Opening the box, Masha found that all the photos were cut into small pieces. Help the heroes of the puzzle about Masha and the Bear glue together the photos and arrange them in the album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sherlock Gnomes</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sherlock-gnomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sherlock-gnomes/</guid>
      <description>While playing Circle Puzzles, you need to collect images of funny creatures dressed as cartoon characters from the famous Walt Disney Studios. It is not so easy to complete the task, because all the images in it are round in shape. Try to correctly arrange all the pieces of the picture and guess which character&amp;rsquo;s costume the hero of the game will appear before you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>The famous cartoon donutsaurus goes hunting for his favorite sweets. Help the funny creature get to the treat. Carefully inspect the location he got to and find the perfect path, overcoming which the hero of the game will be happy to have a bite of a delicious sugar-coated donut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teen Titans Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/teen-titans-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/teen-titans-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Incredible adventures await you in one of the pirate hideouts. A huge metropolis inhabited exclusively by thugs and their families, threatens the safety of navigation throughout the Pacific Ocean. Try to destroy the army of pirates with the help of various explosive devices and wipe out a terrible city from the face of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toon Halloween Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/toon-halloween-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/toon-halloween-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>All fans of the popular animated series &amp;ldquo;Danny Phantom&amp;rdquo; will enjoy playing Solve in puzzles. The insidious Vlad Plasmius found a spell in one of the ancient magical artifacts, with the help of which he enclosed Denny&amp;rsquo;s family and his friends in a photograph, and then tore it into many pieces. We need to fix the situation. Collecting plasma means correctly connecting pieces with the image of cartoon characters to each other and, thanks to this, to break the monstrous spell.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
