<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paints on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/paints/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paints on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/paints/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Drawing And Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/drawing-and-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/drawing-and-coloring/</guid>
      <description>A unique and at the same time very interesting game Coloring and drawing will give you a lot of fun and will take you for a long time. A map will appear on the screen, which you need to go through, calling for help a number of wild animals that act as such pawns. During the game about drawing, you just need to “grab” them with the mouse and move them to free places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oceania Princess Moana Face Art</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/oceania-princess-moana-face-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/oceania-princess-moana-face-art/</guid>
      <description>Paint game will give you the opportunity to turn a black and white drawing into a color image. Today you will color a cute kitten. It is necessary to combine the colors chosen for coloring in such a way that they look natural. To do this, you have at your disposal an amazing palette of colors and a variety of brushes. The game is controlled with the mouse. When you&amp;rsquo;re done, don&amp;rsquo;t be surprised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where`s My Avocado Draw Lines</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheres-my-avocado-draw-lines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wheres-my-avocado-draw-lines/</guid>
      <description>You will definitely enjoy the game in which you have to color funny vegetables. So far, only black outlines are visible on a piece of paper, and in order for the picture to become color, you will have to show all your creative abilities. On the left and right side of the screen you will see circles with paints. Take a virtual brush with the mouse and start creating.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
