<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manicure on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/manicure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manicure on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/manicure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Audrey Beauty Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/audrey-beauty-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/audrey-beauty-salon/</guid>
      <description>The game Manicure for Girls invites you to decorate the girl&amp;rsquo;s nails in a beach style. The process consists of two stages. At the first one, it is proposed to use manicure tools to tidy up the surfaces of the nails: remove old varnish, shape, file. The second stage is devoted to applying varnish. You can choose the usual one-color option, but you can turn on the fantasy and use a variety of decorative stickers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audreys Glam Nails Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/audreys-glam-nails-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/audreys-glam-nails-spa/</guid>
      <description>Turn into a real manicurist and please the heroine of the game with gorgeous nails. For this, the screen has everything you need. Choose the right nail polish color, add patterns or stickers, decide on decorations. Of course, you need to take care of the shape of the nails, choosing the most attractive, in your opinion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beauty Influencer Make Up Tips</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/beauty-influencer-make-up-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/beauty-influencer-make-up-tips/</guid>
      <description>Work on the modern look of the girl in the game for girls Makeup and manicure. Here you have a wide range of opportunities. Get a manicure using different shades of nail polishes. You can choose a monophonic option, or you can stop at a pretty pattern. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget about make-up too - in the menu of the game for girls you will find a huge amount of decorative cosmetics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Nail Art</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fashion-nail-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fashion-nail-art/</guid>
      <description>Give your girl a great manicure! To do this, at your disposal is a large number of different varnishes. You can choose a solid color option, you can add patterns, you can decorate your nails with stickers. If desired, add a bracelet or watch, a tattoo, change skin color. The result must be original.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Floral Realife Manicure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/floral-realife-manicure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/floral-realife-manicure/</guid>
      <description>The heroine of the game is getting ready for the Halloween celebration and is going to put her nails in order. You need to give the girl a manicure and pedicure, using a variety of varnishes and decorations. Choose the color in which the nails will be painted, add stickers, patterns. The finished image can be saved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Princess Nails Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-nails-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-nails-spa/</guid>
      <description>Give a manicure to a cute girl who is used to taking care of her nails. Decide on their shape and varnish color. There are a wide variety of shades here. Apply nail polish and add stickers to make your manicure look even prettier. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the opportunity to choose rings and bracelets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Queen Glamorous Pedicure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-glamorous-pedicure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen-glamorous-pedicure/</guid>
      <description>Any girl wants her legs to look attractive. Now you will need to do a pedicure to the heroine of the game. To do this, you have at your disposal a variety of nail polishes, choose any shade and apply it. Also here it is proposed to decide on jewelry and shoes. You can also change skin color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessie Beauty Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessie-beauty-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessie-beauty-salon/</guid>
      <description>During the game Nail Salon you have to handle the girl&amp;rsquo;s hands. She wants to get a cool manicure. Decide for a start with the length of the nails. There are many different varnishes at your disposal, choose the one that you like the most. It is not at all necessary to make plain nails, you can add a pretty pattern. Stickers, which are also presented in the nail salon in the widest assortment, will not be superfluous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessies DIY Nails Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessies-diy-nails-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessies-diy-nails-spa/</guid>
      <description>Become a manicurist and give your client superb nails. Before you is a huge number of different varnishes, and there are monophonic options, and complemented by drawings. Also on the menu you will find cute decorative items that can be attached to your nails. And don&amp;rsquo;t forget the rings!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic Nail Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/magic-nail-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/magic-nail-salon/</guid>
      <description>Create an original manicure using the presented features. Decide on the shape of the nails, choose the color of the varnish with which you will paint your nails. You can choose a solid color, or you can use attractive patterns. Also, if you wish, you can add decorative stickers in the form of cute figures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Princess Nails Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-princess-nails-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-princess-nails-spa/</guid>
      <description>Create a great wedding manicure for the princess. The game consists of two stages. To begin with, it is proposed to use different tools to put your nails in order. Once this is done, the second stage will open. There you will need to choose the shape of the nails, the color of the varnish, cute tattoos, stylish rings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Beauty Nails Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/modern-beauty-nails-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/modern-beauty-nails-spa/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you have to work on the image of a charming girl. Choose the color of the lacquer that will cover her nails, add a pattern, stickers. You can also choose jewelry and tattoos. The game also involves applying makeup, there are a lot of attractive decorative cosmetics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Nail Art Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-nail-art-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-nail-art-salon/</guid>
      <description>The girl is preparing for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day and she needs a good manicure. The task is to treat the heroine&amp;rsquo;s nails with high quality. There are many different varnishes at your disposal. You can make plain nails or use drawings. You can also add stickers. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget the pretty ring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nails Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/nails-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/nails-makeover/</guid>
      <description>After launching the Nail Salon game for girls, you have to work on the nails of cute girls. To get started, choose one of the three charms, which you will do a manicure. Then it remains only to process the nails, having carried out various useful procedures, removing the old varnish and giving the nails a shape. The final stage is the application of a new coating. At the same time, you can choose a monophonic option or stop at a nice pattern.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natalie Nails Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/natalie-nails-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/natalie-nails-spa/</guid>
      <description>While playing Barbie Manicure you have to take care of the nails of a cute girl. To begin with, they must be put in order using special manicure tools. Next, you can proceed to the application of varnish. Choose the most suitable shade and paint your nails to make them look chic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princesses Nails Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-nails-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-nails-salon/</guid>
      <description>Excellent game Manicure invites you to help a girl take care of her nails and prepare for the Christmas holidays. To begin with, it will be necessary to carry out useful procedures that allow you to put your hands and nails in order. Then take care of applying varnish, in the menu you will find many different shades. In addition to plain options, you can safely use different Christmas patterns, as well as cute decorative decorations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping Princess Nails Spa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sleeping-princess-nails-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sleeping-princess-nails-spa/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game, you will turn into a manicurist. A girl came to you who wants to get beautiful nails. Use the presented varnishes and stickers in order to achieve an original result. If desired, jewelry can be added to the manicure - rings or bracelets. They complete the picture perfectly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow White Nails</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-white-nails/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-white-nails/</guid>
      <description>Give a manicure to a girl who always looks after her appearance. Your task is to decide on the shape of the nails, the color of the polish, the type of pattern. If desired, you can add decorative elements that will make the manicure even more original. And here you need to choose the color of the dress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superhero Doll Manicure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-doll-manicure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-doll-manicure/</guid>
      <description>During this game you have to do manicures. Proceed to the processing of nails, using the proposed opportunities. Here you will find a huge number of different varnishes, stickers, patterns. Also in the game there is a good assortment of rings and bracelets, which definitely will not be superfluous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superhero Princesses Nails Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-princesses-nails-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-princesses-nails-salon/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game for girls Paint nails you will turn into a manicurist. The task is to take care of the nails of another fashionista who always looks after her appearance. There is a large number of varnishes in front of you, choose any shade and apply on your nails. You can even use different options to get the original result. In addition to varnishes, stickers of various shapes and colors are presented here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
