<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ben 10 on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/ben-10/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ben 10 on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/ben-10/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ben Ten game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ben-ten-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ben-ten-game/</guid>
      <description>Addictive game Ben Ten invites you to the city where lives a boy who has the ability to turn into a variety of creatures. In addition, from time to time Ben saves the world, and today he just has to help humanity by eliminating the chaos that reigns in his hometown. The boy has already reincarnated as one of the characters available in the game, and you need to control him, destroying all the enemies prowling the local streets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dimension Threat 12 Game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dimension-threat-12-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dimension-threat-12-game/</guid>
      <description>You are the captain of a star cruiser and sent to Earth to protect it from insidious alien invaders. Hurry up to join the battle and destroy the robots and alien ships before they land on the planet. But do not forget, aggressive enemies will attack your hero and are quite capable of destroying his ship with a few well-aimed shots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morning Catch</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/morning-catch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/morning-catch/</guid>
      <description>Instead of going to the lessons, the obnoxious boy Ben rushed to go fishing. That&amp;rsquo;s the backstory. Now about you. Moving back and forth on the boat, you must catch the maximum number of fish in the allotted time. Points are awarded for fish. The larger the crucian, the more points. Joy is added by a thundercloud, which periodically beats you with current.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Union of Heroes game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/union-of-heroes-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/union-of-heroes-game/</guid>
      <description>Ben and his friends are forced to fight a whole army of aliens who, under the leadership of an insidious villain, decided to take over the planet. Help a boy with unusual abilities to save humanity. Before starting the next task, listen carefully to the professor. He will tell you how to effectively destroy this or that monster and deal with their villainous commander.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
