<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mahjong on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/mahjong/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mahjong on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/mahjong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deep Sea Trijong </title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/deep-sea-trijong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/deep-sea-trijong/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a quiet way to pass the time, Artifact Mahjong is the way to go. Especially if you are a fan of logic games. It is available in three modes, however, only one is possible online. The other two can only be launched after downloading. As for the passage, you will have to collect almost classic Chinese mahjong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover Ancient Rome</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/discover-ancient-rome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/discover-ancient-rome/</guid>
      <description>If you want to have fun and exercise your logical thinking at the same time, the Mahjong Titan game is quite suitable for this. It is a kind of solitaire, in which chips are used instead of cards, like in dominoes, only with different patterns instead of dots. The task of the gamer is to find the same drawings. Two identical pieces are selected with the mouse and disappear from the board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-hunt/</guid>
      <description>If you want a quiet entertainment and at the same time exercise logic and attention, then the game Mahjong Connect Pairs is quite suitable for these purposes. And don&amp;rsquo;t let the second part of the title fool you. You will have to connect not lovers, but the same, that is, paired chips. They can be in the same row next to each other or at a distance. Unlike the classic Mahjong, here it is not necessary that the chips have two sides open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Mahjongg</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-mahjongg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-mahjongg/</guid>
      <description>The game process for girls Mahjong is based on the classic Chinese game of the same name. The goal is to clear the board of all chips. This toy is very similar to solitaire. But unlike the Asian version, here various delicacies are drawn on the knuckles. You need to find two identical drawings to remove them from the field. However, nothing will come of it if the chip is closed on two or more sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ez Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ez-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ez-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>The game will appeal to active users, because instead of incomprehensible hieroglyphs, instead of incomprehensible hieroglyphs, the logos of programs for modern computers are drawn on it. As for the passage, here, as in the classic Chinese fun, you need to find the same chips in the layout, select them with a mouse click and remove them from the field. Time is unlimited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fairy Triple Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fairy-triple-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fairy-triple-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>If you enjoy playing classic Chinese mahjong, you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place. For those who are not in the know, the rules are simple: you need to find two identical chips and remove them from the field by selecting them with the mouse. Each piece must have at least one free side. Before the start of the mono, choose the option of passing: normal or for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farm Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/farm-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/farm-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>If you need a toy that develops logical thinking and attention for the smallest gamers, then you have a very suitable option. Users need to find chips with paired images and remove them from the screen. The drawings are very simple and all dedicated to the theme of pets. So it will be easy for children to work with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Mahjon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fish-mahjon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fish-mahjon/</guid>
      <description>No, this is not a special mahjong for sailors. In the marine style, there are only drawings on the chips. Well, and the background of the entire image. By the way, thanks to him, the game is great for relaxing after work. Otherwise, everything is as usual: find and remove chips with the same pictures. The time for passing is limited to forty minutes. You can include a pause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fruit Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fruit-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fruit-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>A funny, but very gluttonous caterpillar decided to eat all the fruits in the garden. She asks you for help. In order for the fruits to get into the stomach of a cute glutton, you must find all the same fruits on the playing field. As soon as a match is found, it immediately becomes the dinner of a green baby who dreams of becoming a butterfly someday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kris Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kris-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kris-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>What programmers will not come up with to diversify the most common toys and make their brainchild unlike other similar products. This is how the game Mahjong Fruit appeared. But just putting pictures of a certain theme on the chips was not enough, so it was also endowed with a developing function. After all, young children, looking for the same chips, will be able to simultaneously study a variety of fruits and vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahjong Connect</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mahjong-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mahjong-connect/</guid>
      <description>Mahjong 1 is an almost classic version of this Chinese solitaire game. It consists of several levels, the transition to which looks like a journey through the map. Time to complete each stage is limited. There are several auxiliary buttons on the right side of the screen that either remove chips or give a hint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahjong Gardens</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mahjong-gardens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mahjong-gardens/</guid>
      <description>Dragon Mahjong game is not very similar to the classic version of this puzzle. The only thing they have in common is the need to search for and remove chips with the same pictures from the field. On the right side of the screen is a set of mahjong tiles. On the left, a dragon flies slowly, on which &amp;ldquo;bones&amp;rdquo; are also located. You need to quickly find pairings. Any gamer can play the exciting Mahjong Dragon for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahjong King</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mahjong-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mahjong-king/</guid>
      <description>Quite interesting will be the passage of the game Mahjong paired patterns. Yes, it only remotely resembles the Chinese version of solitaire, but it is not without its charm and even originality. The rules will become more difficult from level to level. The number of hints when moving to the next stage is not restored (if you used them). In a word, vivid impressions are guaranteed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahjong Titans</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mahjong-titans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mahjong-titans/</guid>
      <description>Solitaire is a traditional Chinese board game. It consists of tablets with hieroglyphs, which are laid out on the playing field face down in the form of a pyramid or a simple platform. The goal of the game of mahjong is to disassemble the figure by removing cards with paired images from it, but only those that are on top and have already been opened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahjong: Age of Alchemy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mahjong-age-of-alchemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mahjong-age-of-alchemy/</guid>
      <description>Puzzle games Mahjong Shanghai Dynasty take you back to ancient times. It was there that the logical fun was born, which eventually became popular all over the world. According to the rules of the game, you need to find two identical tiles in a pyramid of tiles. Carefully inspect the structure and try to find bones with an identical denomination in it. You can play this old but very exciting Shanghai mahjong both on your own and with your parents, competing with them in observation skills and the ability to think logically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moon Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/moon-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/moon-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>Tired of the usual solitaire card games? Then try this mahjong variant. Here, instead of hieroglyphs, card suits are drawn on the chips. The rules for passing are also somewhat different from the usual Chinese entertainment and are somewhat reminiscent of Solitaire solitaire. To make it easier to understand, you should read the instructions before starting the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PartyJong</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/partyjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/partyjong/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the patterns on the surface of the chips (they depict different sweets), this mahjong variant is suitable for children. Otherwise, everything is the same as in the classic game. To get started, choose one of the layout options and get started. Time to pass is unlimited, so you can think as much as you like. You can also use the hint button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Mahjong The Tower</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/power-mahjong-the-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/power-mahjong-the-tower/</guid>
      <description>Regular Chinese mahjong often causes difficulties for beginners, and especially for the youngest users. The reason is simple: small drawings and hieroglyphs similar to each other. It also offers a somewhat simplified puzzle with clear for everyone, large pictures. By the way, it was also developed by the Chinese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweety Mahjong 1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweety-mahjong-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweety-mahjong-1/</guid>
      <description>This game invites you to become a graphic designer for a while and understand a huge number of original patterns. Among the many pieces of the puzzle, try to find pairs of the same and point to them with the mouse cursor. If you can&amp;rsquo;t complete the task in the allotted time, ask your parents to join you and help a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toys Mahjong Connect</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/toys-mahjong-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/toys-mahjong-connect/</guid>
      <description>Mahjong connect game is one of the variants of the well-known oriental logic puzzle. Many, for sure, have seen it on their computers in the standard sets of entertainment applications of the operating system. But in this case, there are a number of differences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/winter-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/winter-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>From the very first seconds, the game New Year&amp;rsquo;s Mahjong Connect Pairs cheers you up with a picture on the main page, as well as cheerful music. Jazz, by the way, which, in general, is very rare in computer toys. The second pleasant surprise is the Russian-language interface and menu. Another language can be selected from two dozen options. Gamers are offered a simplified, so to speak, children&amp;rsquo;s version of the Mahjong game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woodventure Mahjong Connect</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/woodventure-mahjong-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/woodventure-mahjong-connect/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t be fooled by the romantic pink ambiance of this unusual puzzle. You will have to move your brains in it no less actively than when unfolding the classic mahjong. And the very principle of the game has not changed: look for identical paired fragments on the screen and click on them with the mouse, removing them from the field. If you do everything right, you can clear the entire screen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
