<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mutants on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/mutants/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mutants on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/mutants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Challenge Of The Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/challenge-of-the-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/challenge-of-the-zombies/</guid>
      <description>A well-drawn toy in which zombies scatter in bloody lumps is what you need at the end of a hard day. Your character is a funny dude with a hand grenade launcher. It is necessary to shoot so that the grenades hit the zombies or fall next to them. They explode with a three second delay. Enemies are often in cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Swarm</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dead-swarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dead-swarm/</guid>
      <description>Do you know that rabbits can be dangerous? Of course, not all, but only those who came out of the harsh Chernobyl forests. After getting drunk on radioactive cabbage, they became predatory and very tenacious. We have to shoot these creatures. There are five types of weapons at your disposal. The supply of ammo is limited, but you can buy more. First-person view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eg Zombies War</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-zombies-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-zombies-war/</guid>
      <description>Stunning graphics and a simple plot - these are the two main features of this dynamic shooter. Imagine that you are alone, in an abandoned park, where crowds of hungry and aggressive mutants roam. Your task is not to turn into their today&amp;rsquo;s dinner, shooting back from the zombies with all your might.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guardians Vs Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/guardians-vs-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/guardians-vs-zombies/</guid>
      <description>The graphics in this game are quite attractive. In any case, it creates an atmosphere of complete post-apocalypse. The genre can be described as &amp;ldquo;building defense&amp;rdquo;. Your character sat on the roof of the house. A wave of zombies is coming from all sides. It is necessary to kill them on the approaches, otherwise the creatures will destroy the building. Press the buttons in the sequence indicated next to each enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night Watchmen Stories Zombie Hospital</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/night-watchmen-stories-zombie-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/night-watchmen-stories-zombie-hospital/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s safe to say that you&amp;rsquo;ve never seen anything scarier than mutant hamsters. They filled the city with themselves, and now your task is to kill every single creature. First-person view. All you see is the barrel of your gun. It&amp;rsquo;s simple: met a mutant - turn it into a puddle of green slime. But be careful - they shoot back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tap The Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tap-the-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tap-the-zombies/</guid>
      <description>The game Mutants is not distinguished by any advanced plot. But in it you can let off steam after a hard day. View from above. The adventure begins in the store, but you still won&amp;rsquo;t be able to buy new weapons, because they are not available by level. However, you can take an additional grenade by spending all the money at once. Next, you will find yourself in a room, go through a short training and start repelling mutant attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrible Wasteland</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/terrible-wasteland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/terrible-wasteland/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a very useful shooting game where zombies act as enemies. First-person view. The action takes place on a moonlit night in the forest - atmospheric, but visibility is quite tolerable. Initially, you have a gun and a thousand rounds of ammunition. Shoot zombies coming out of a lonely house. Pick up the weapons that have fallen out of them, but remember - there are not many cartridges in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undead Drive</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/undead-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/undead-drive/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever thrown a Molotov cocktail? In this game you have such a unique opportunity. Your character is a hefty redneck in military uniform. He stands behind the barrier (by the way, it&amp;rsquo;s funny, but you see him from the front), and hordes of disgusting mutants are attacking him. Aim and throw a bottle to set the specimen on fire. Creatures must not be allowed near the barrier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie D Survival Offline</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-d-survival-offline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-d-survival-offline/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a cruel world where real monsters fight in the arena! The essence of the game Create your own mutant is that your character (by the way, initially it is a very cute dog) will have to participate in the world championship of very strange fighters. Before each fight, you can change its genetic code and equip it with new properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Target Shoot</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-target-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-target-shoot/</guid>
      <description>The name of the game speaks for itself. Users need to fight off mutant attacks. Wave after wave. The character stands behind the barricade (side view) and has a pistol in his hands. The attackers must not be allowed to destroy the fortification. In addition to the pistol, there is also a super-weapon that can not always be used - it takes a long time to reload.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombies Eat All</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombies-eat-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombies-eat-all/</guid>
      <description>During the game Zombie mutants you will control an unknown hero who blocked the path of evil spirits. Initially, he was armed only with a revolver, which had to be reloaded frequently. However, from time to time, as monsters are destroyed, bonuses drop out. For example, huge shoes that you can drop on enemies and crush them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
