<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dress up for school on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/dress-up-for-school/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dress up for school on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/dress-up-for-school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Around the World: Fashion in France</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/around-the-world-fashion-in-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/around-the-world-fashion-in-france/</guid>
      <description>Who would like a teacher in strict old-fashioned outfits and heavy horn-rimmed glasses? Such a mere appearance brings melancholy to the students, oppresses any desire to learn. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty teacher in modern stylish clothes. In this game, you have the opportunity, by choosing hairstyles, outfits and accessories (including a teacher&amp;rsquo;s pointer), to create the image of an ideal teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Around the World: German Fashion</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/around-the-world-german-fashion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/around-the-world-german-fashion/</guid>
      <description>The schoolgirl has an age-old problem: she doesn’t know what to wear on a date. Help her sort out her own wardrobe and make an attractive costume. By sorting through things, hairstyles and choosing accessories that suit your style, you will develop your skills as a stylist and fashion designer. The game has an option to suggest ready-made outfit options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audreys Fashion Blogger Story</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/audreys-fashion-blogger-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/audreys-fashion-blogger-story/</guid>
      <description>Is it really so difficult to come up with a beautiful and comfortable school uniform? Many schoolgirls ask themselves this question and dream of a new style of clothing for classes. You have the opportunity to take your own step towards your dream. To do this, you just need to dress up the heroine of the game the way you like. A rich selection of clothes will help you create the perfect fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audreys Valentine</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/audreys-valentine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/audreys-valentine/</guid>
      <description>Pairs are often sent to the prom. And whether this couple is beautiful or not, largely depends on how well the outfits are matched. In this game, you will have to dress up a guy and a girl so that they become the most beautiful couple at the prom. It’s easier to dress up a guy, since you only need to choose a suit for him. But you will have to tinker with the girl, choosing not only clothes, but also a hairstyle, jewelry, accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back To School Fashionistas</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/back-to-school-fashionistas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/back-to-school-fashionistas/</guid>
      <description>Riding a school bus, like going to school, requires careful preparation. In your case, preparation begins with dressing a high school girl who is standing by the side of the road waiting for a bus with her classmates. Help her choose a beautiful and comfortable outfit. At your disposal are clothes, jewelry, shoes and some useful accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonnie Galaxy Faces</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-galaxy-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-galaxy-faces/</guid>
      <description>At first glance, this is a traditional dress-up game. By selecting the details of clothing, jewelry, shoes, you dress up the girl Emma for an ordinary school day. The background of the picture corresponds to the task - this is an average classroom (although not ours, but a Western one). However, after you finish the work, a surprise awaits you: the ability to change the background. And then Emma will be on a walk or at a resort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonnie In Riverdale</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-in-riverdale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-in-riverdale/</guid>
      <description>The task of cheerleaders is to support their team. And, of course, the athletes are cheered up not only by chants, but also by the spectacular appearance of the cheerleaders. You need to dress up the cheerleader of the sports team as effectively as possible. To do this, the game has a chic assortment of sports uniforms. If you find it difficult to choose, click on the light bulb icon in the upper right and see the ready-made options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonnie Rocker Chick</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-rocker-chick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-rocker-chick/</guid>
      <description>This time you need to dress up Meloni for school. Probably, in her hometown, the requirements for a school uniform are very arbitrary, since the choice of all kinds of things allows you to create an outfit for every taste. Dressing up Meloni is easy: just drag the piece of the outfit to the right place and that&amp;rsquo;s it. You can thus hang two clothes side by side (for example, blouses) and compare them, leaving the most suitable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gothic Princess Real Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gothic-princess-real-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gothic-princess-real-makeover/</guid>
      <description>Contrary to popular belief, emos can and love to have fun too. Of course, participating in the general fun, they still strive to be different from others. It&amp;rsquo;s up to you to make an emo character inimitable at the upcoming prom. At your disposal are clothes, jewelry, shoes and even skin color change functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/graduation-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/graduation-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>Graduation is an important and exciting event in the life of every person. And, of course, it is very important to choose the right outfit for the moment. You have a unique chance to give free rein to your imagination and thirst for creativity, and at minimal cost and without risk. Start by choosing a hairstyle, after which you can move on to dresses, stockings and accessories. The finished costume can be saved on the computer as a picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kawaii Beauty Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kawaii-beauty-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kawaii-beauty-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Schoolgirls in Japan also love to dress up. Fans of Japanese cartoons must have considered the outfits of Japanese students. In this game, they are given the opportunity to get to know them in more detail and create their own unique uniforms for Japanese schools. The game has the usual set for such cases: hairstyles, clothes, shoes and accessories, among which there is an unusual one - an electric guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moody Ally Back to School</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/moody-ally-back-to-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/moody-ally-back-to-school/</guid>
      <description>Melisa was originally naked and bald. That&amp;rsquo;s what I want to say when the game starts. But it&amp;rsquo;s up to you to fix it. How well you manage to choose a hairstyle and dress up the heroine of the game for going to school depends only on your abilities and imagination. Well, for those who find it difficult to do this, the game will be an excellent opportunity to develop a sense of taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Back School Lockers</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-back-school-lockers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-back-school-lockers/</guid>
      <description>The game starts with makeup. On the left you have a choice of subsections: eye color, shadows, eyebrows and so on. After that, you go to the section for choosing clothes and modeling hairstyles. It should be noted that the makeup and clothes in the game look quite realistic. When you&amp;rsquo;re done, try submitting your model to an online competition (there&amp;rsquo;s a button at the bottom of the screen).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Casual Cosplay Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-casual-cosplay-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-casual-cosplay-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This game is a rather colorful dress up game in which you need to work on three characters at once: two girls and one boy. They need to be properly dressed up for lessons at school. Remember that a school suit should be not only beautiful, but also comfortable. The funny thing about the game is that the boy can be dressed up in girly things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Maxi Dress</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-maxi-dress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-maxi-dress/</guid>
      <description>Senior classes are not only a lot of complex subjects and preparation for entering a university, but also the need to dress spectacularly and tastefully. You can practice and let your imagination run wild in this game. A good selection of blouses, blouses, skirts, trousers and other items of clothing will help you create the perfect outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Sorority Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-sorority-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-sorority-rush/</guid>
      <description>This game will allow you to attract girlfriends and have fun. The fact is that the computer automatically evaluates the final result in points, that is, you can arrange competitions. Well, you will have to do the usual things: dress up a schoolgirl and bring beauty to her face (make-up).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruby Dressing Room</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ruby-dressing-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ruby-dressing-room/</guid>
      <description>And again, the Japanese give you scope for the realization of any design fantasies, offering to dress up a Japanese schoolgirl. To do this, she has dozens of different items of clothing and jewelry in her wardrobe. And, of course, you can choose a hairstyle that suits the occasion with a headdress. Take action!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Divas</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/social-media-divas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/social-media-divas/</guid>
      <description>For those who are bored of playing ordinary dress-up games, the developers of this game gave the opportunity to dress up several characters at once. Here you can choose a hairstyle, jewelry and, of course, the top and bottom of the school costume. Shoes are also available. As a finishing touch - the selection of the background, on which the final picture will appear, where all the girlfriends will stand side by side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Top Model Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/winter-top-model-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/winter-top-model-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Games for girls Dress up for school in the winter will take you to visit a girl whose thermometer outside the window has dropped many divisions below zero. They say about such weather that a good owner will not kick the dog out into the street, and our little one needs to hurry to school. Help her dress as warmly and beautifully as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
