<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coloring pages for girls on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/coloring-pages-for-girls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coloring pages for girls on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/coloring-pages-for-girls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Birds Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/birds-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/birds-coloring/</guid>
      <description>The process of playing Coloring Pages for Girls will turn you into a real artist. Here you are invited to color pictures with cute animals. Choose any image from the proposed assortment, and then proceed to the creative process. To do this, you have many different colors at your disposal. Choose any color, and also decide whether you will act with a brush or use a fill. If something goes wrong in the coloring, you can always use an eraser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Me Jungle Animals</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/color-me-jungle-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/color-me-jungle-animals/</guid>
      <description>The game Coloring for girls is dedicated to the fairy tale about Cinderella. You are invited to color the cute images of this cute princess. Choose one of the four pictures, and then select the colors you want to use and apply them to the elements of the picture. After you finish coloring the image, admire the color result - Cinderella, who is definitely ready to go to the ball in a chic dress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Princess Drawing Party</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/disney-princess-drawing-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/disney-princess-drawing-party/</guid>
      <description>Feel like an artist in this wonderful game. Here you have to color the image of a cute princess. You have a lot of different colors at your disposal, and you can choose any colors to apply them to the appropriate elements of the picture. If necessary, use an eraser to erase unnecessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will see a huge number of Easter eggs that you will need to color. To do this, you have a large number of colors at your disposal. Dip the brush into any paint, and then click on the part that you are now going to color. It will be fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mandala Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mandala-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mandala-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>During this wonderful game you will be able to create your own coloring book. On the screen you will see an image of a girl, choose the background on which she will be, as well as clothes, shoes and accessories. Then it remains only to color the resulting picture using a variety of colors. The finished result can be printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentine Pets Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/valentine-pets-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/valentine-pets-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Do you like to draw? Then this game is made especially for you. Here you will find black and white pictures related to the theme of love. Choose any image and then start creating. You have many different felt-tip pens at your disposal, pick up the one you like and click on the part you want to color.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
