<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Salon on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/salon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Salon on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/salon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Amandas Summer Festival Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/amandas-summer-festival-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/amandas-summer-festival-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game, you will find yourself in an excellent hairdressing salon that allows you to create original hairstyles. It is only necessary to use the proposed tools, transforming the appearance of the heroine. You can cut her hair, change the color, curl her curls, add cute accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angelic Charm Princess</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/angelic-charm-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/angelic-charm-princess/</guid>
      <description>After launching the game Angel and Demon Barbershop 3, you will find yourself in an unusual beauty salon, where you will manage an imp hairdresser who wants to create hairstyles in his own, very specific style. But this can only be done when the angel is busy with extraneous matters and does not see what is happening in the salon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audreys Glamorous Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/audreys-glamorous-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/audreys-glamorous-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>An excellent Hair Salon game will turn you into a real stylist who knows a lot about fashionable fantasy looks. You are invited to work on the image of a cute girl, using a variety of wardrobe items. And most importantly - in it you can change hairstyles without any problems, like in a real hairdresser. Just choose the option that suits you and then add stylish details to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonnie Hair Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-hair-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-hair-doctor/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Plyusheva, despite her young age, loves a variety of cute hairstyles. Work on the girl&amp;rsquo;s hair, because now they do not look very attractive. At your disposal are all the necessary hairdressing tools that will allow you to cope with the problem and create a new hairstyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burd Festival Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/burd-festival-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/burd-festival-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you are invited to work on the image of an informal girl. She loves rock music and looks the part. Choose a hairstyle for the heroine of the game, change the hair color, decide on the outfit and accessories. Also here you can change the color of the skin, the shape of the eyes and mouth. Progress is displayed on a special scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edc Vegas Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/edc-vegas-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/edc-vegas-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>During this exciting game you will be able to work on the image of a pretty girl who has decided to change her hairstyle. It is necessary to use all the proposed tools in order to end up with an attractive result. You can cut your hair, curl it, recolor it and add cute accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizas Neon Hairstyle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elizas-neon-hairstyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elizas-neon-hairstyle/</guid>
      <description>The girl is preparing for school, and you need to help her create a suitable image. To do this, a large number of clothes and shoes, as well as accessories are provided in the virtual wardrobe. In addition, here you can choose a cute hairstyle and apply makeup using a variety of cosmetics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French Fashion Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/french-fashion-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/french-fashion-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>The hairdresser</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>During the game Face and Hair Care you will be asked to help the girl get ready for the party. Naturally, she wants to look as attractive as possible at this event. Your task is to make the heroine of the game a cool hairstyle and apply makeup on her face. You are provided with hairdressing tools that will allow you to get an original result. You can cut your hair or leave it long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Princess Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you will find tasks related to the creation of hairstyles. To get started, choose the styling you want to reproduce, and then get to work. Use hairdressing tools to achieve the desired result. After you finish, your efforts will be evaluated in percentage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Queen - Christmas Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen---christmas-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-queen---christmas-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>Princess Elsa always takes care of her appearance and now she has gone to the hair salon to get a new haircut. You need to work on the girl&amp;rsquo;s hair in order to achieve excellent results. To get started, use a variety of useful tools, and then proceed to the formation of styling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natalies Boho Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/natalies-boho-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/natalies-boho-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>Become a real hairdresser after launching this exciting game! There are two modes of passage: free and with tasks. In free mode, you can use your imagination and create any hairstyle you want. If you choose the second mode, then there you need to act according to the model, which is shown for a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olivia Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/olivia-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/olivia-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>A young girl is getting ready for school and she needs a cute hairstyle. Help the heroine of the game transform using a variety of means and tools. Game tips will help you understand the hairdressing process. Follow them, and then you will definitely get the intended result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Cheer Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/popular-cheer-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/popular-cheer-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>The process of the game for girls Barber Sony 2 will turn you into a beauty salon worker for free. Keep track of what your visitors want and provide them with the services they need. To pass each level, you need to earn the specified amount. Start playing right now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess April Fools Hair Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-april-fools-hair-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-april-fools-hair-salon/</guid>
      <description>Spectra - one of the students of the school of monsters, decided to change the image. It is proposed to start with a hairstyle. Imagine yourself as a hairdresser and give Spectra a great hairstyle that will make her look even more attractive. To do this, you have at your disposal a variety of tools and means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Silver Hair</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-silver-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-silver-hair/</guid>
      <description>Rapunzel&amp;rsquo;s long hair needs quality care and you should try to create a cute hairstyle for the fairy princess. Go to the hairdresser, where the heroine of the game is already waiting for you, and get to work using a variety of hairdressing tools. Hair color can also be changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pure Princess Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pure-princess-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pure-princess-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will meet three charming girls who want to transform. You are invited to make the heroines of the game new hairstyles, thanks to which the beauties will become even more attractive. Choose any of the girls and then go to the gym to work on her hair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainbow Pony Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rainbow-pony-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rainbow-pony-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>The game Pony Creator 3 with a new hairstyle invites you to create adorable little horses. At your disposal will be a real virtual designer, in which you can choose the body, mane, tail, eyes and other elements of the pony&amp;rsquo;s appearance. The color of any part can be changed, choosing the most suitable one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping Princess Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sleeping-princess-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sleeping-princess-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will need to create fashionable hairstyles for charming princesses. First, choose the heroine whose hair you will work on. Then decide on the shape of the hairstyle, indicate the desired shade of paint and proceed to the process. You need to follow a strict sequence of actions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow Queen Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-queen-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-queen-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>The Snow Queen, despite all her coldness, strives to look attractive in any situation. In this game, you are invited to work on the image of a girl. There are three stages here: first you need to do your hair, then apply makeup, and at the end you can choose an outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow White Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-white-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-white-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game, you will turn into a real hairdresser who can do a variety of hairstyles, even the most complex ones. You have a huge number of professional tools at your disposal, and you can use them in any way you like to end up with a nice result. Don&amp;rsquo;t hold back your fantasy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprout Hair Pins</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sprout-hair-pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sprout-hair-pins/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to work on the appearance of a girl who works as a hairdresser in a salon. Think about what she might look like. Choose a hairstyle, outfit, shoes, accessories for the heroine of the game. Do not forget to give the girl some hairdressing tool to emphasize her profession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day Hearty Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/valentines-day-hearty-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/valentines-day-hearty-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>The heroine of the game Hair care does not like her hairstyle at all. You need to act as an experienced hairdresser and correct the situation. The game consists of several stages. To begin with, it is proposed to wash the hair and dry it, after which it will be possible to use scissors and form a haircut. Next, take care of styling, using curlers or an iron. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget about the hair color, the game for girls has a fairly large selection of different shades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vixys Sweet Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/vixys-sweet-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/vixys-sweet-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to take care of cute pets. They also want to get cute hairstyles, so it is worth taking care of kittens and dogs. Choose any animal, and then proceed to its transformation. You need to choose the shape of his future hairstyle, its color, and add stylish accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warrior Princess Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/warrior-princess-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/warrior-princess-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>During the game Hair Cut you need to help Snow White. She ate a poisoned apple, and now something terrible is happening on the girl&amp;rsquo;s head. Your task is to work with the fairy tale heroine&amp;rsquo;s hair. To begin with, wash them and use various useful products that will restore beauty and radiance. Further in the game for girls, it will be possible to proceed directly to the haircut and the formation of hairstyles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winx Club Hair Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/winx-club-hair-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/winx-club-hair-salon/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will need to work on the image of a charming forest fairy. Choose a great hairstyle for her, add stylish accessories, decide on an outfit. In a word, do everything to make the fairy look really attractive and attract exceptionally admiring glances.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
