<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3D Tuning on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/3d-tuning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3D Tuning on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/3d-tuning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3D Formula Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/3d-formula-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/3d-formula-racing/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful cars don&amp;rsquo;t just happen. They are made so by tuning masters. Use every opportunity to create an original design for the car. There are many details in your garage that can drastically change the look of the car. After you finish your work, you can go to the track and drive a tuned car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burnout Drift 2: Hilltop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/burnout-drift-2-hilltop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/burnout-drift-2-hilltop/</guid>
      <description>The 3d tuning game will give you the opportunity to change the appearance of a Dodge car. This is a really cool car with a unique design and a powerful engine. Tuning this particular car you have to do today. A huge selection of parts awaits in the workshop. Everything you need is here - wheels, rims, fenders, grilles, headlights, spoilers and exhaust pipes. Your imagination is unlimited, so get down to business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Car Race</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/deadly-car-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/deadly-car-race/</guid>
      <description>A sports car will appear on the screen in front of you in all its glory, which needs to be slightly redone. In the virtual garage you will find many different parts that you can install on your car. Think over the appearance of the car and tune it with those fragments that you like the most. Well, then you can admire your creation on the track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drift Car Driving</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/drift-car-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/drift-car-driving/</guid>
      <description>Your task in this game is to design your own sports car. First you need to decide on the color of the car. Then choose the desired shade of neon lighting. Following this, you can choose wheels for wheels, as well as a bumper and spoiler. At the end of the game, you must drive the car to the exhibition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elite Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elite-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elite-racing/</guid>
      <description>Today you have to do car tuning, having all the necessary tools for this. The game bar is located on the left side of the screen. On it you will find several sections with different details of your future cool car. Just choose what you liked the most and drag it to the car. Change color, wheels, headlights and everything else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Drift 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-drift-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-drift-2/</guid>
      <description>A big lover of vintage cars came to your workshop and asked to find out what was noisy in his car, and then fix the breakdown. In order to do this, I had to disassemble the car completely, and now that the broken part has been replaced, all that remains for you is to completely reassemble the car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Luck Racer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/good-luck-racer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/good-luck-racer/</guid>
      <description>Surely, every boy loves cool cars, and tuned ones - especially. So, today you can not only ride a cool car, but even get the opportunity to remake it. Change the color, body parts, bumpers, wheels, headlights and much more at your discretion. The result should be a luxurious supercar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GTX Racing 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gtx-racing-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gtx-racing-2018/</guid>
      <description>During the game VAZ 2112 play 3d tuning you have a unique opportunity to create with your own hands the kind of car that you would like to have in the near future. After all, every guy dreams of his beautiful and fashionable car. Start with a basic drawing. Pick colors for different parts of your future car and enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamborghini Car Drifting</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lamborghini-car-drifting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lamborghini-car-drifting/</guid>
      <description>If you like cool and powerful cars and everything connected with them, this wonderful game was created especially for you. It can completely remake the latest Lamborghini model. Change the color of the body, wheels, windows and even apply stylish airbrushing to the car. Create as many different variants of the sports car as you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nascar Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/nascar-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/nascar-racing/</guid>
      <description>You are a car designer who urgently needs to present a new modern car for the Motor Show. For these purposes, you have been given a model of a Ford supercar. Try to apply all your design talents and tune the car so that it wins first place at the exhibition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Cars Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-cars-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-cars-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you are invited to dream up a little and practice car design. You can change windows, headlights, wheels, brakes and more. Many auto repair shops nowadays have enough resources to make a cool car out of an ordinary car. Today you will also have the opportunity to turn an ordinary Lada into a supercar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformers Robots in Disguise: Combiner Force</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/transformers-robots-in-disguise-combiner-force/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/transformers-robots-in-disguise-combiner-force/</guid>
      <description>The car of the transforming robot has become partially unusable and now it will have to be overhauled. Hurry up and drive the car to the garage and call an experienced auto mechanic for help. Under his guidance, take care of straightening the side doors of the car, tapping with a hammer the places that have deformation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
