<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shooting on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shooting on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apple Shooter Remastered</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/apple-shooter-remastered/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/apple-shooter-remastered/</guid>
      <description>With the help of the game Shooting people with archery, the gamer will have to become a super accurate shooter performing dangerous stunts for a while. Before you stands a girl with a red apple on her head. You need to aim well and make a well-aimed shot that will bring down the fruit. But be careful, any mistake will lead to the death of a person. You will choose the shooting parameters with the mouse, focusing on the scale at the top of the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archery Training</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/archery-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/archery-training/</guid>
      <description>Almost every boy&amp;rsquo;s first weapon was a homemade bow. Today you have to test your accuracy in shooting from this ancient device. You have to take into account all the little things that are important for a successful shot. After all, even a breath of wind or a falling leaf can prevent you from hitting the target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bow Master Stickman Hero</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bow-master-stickman-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bow-master-stickman-hero/</guid>
      <description>According to the terms of the shooting game Little People, you will have to control a drawn stickman who acts as a special agent and performs super complex and responsible tasks. You will have to take part in skirmishes on the streets of the city, in the bank, in the subway and at the airport. It&amp;rsquo;s hard enough to play. The enemy appears suddenly and instantly opens fire. Black men are everywhere, so be careful and careful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Noon Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/high-noon-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/high-noon-hunter/</guid>
      <description>Once again, all the inhabitants of the city of Minecraft have turned into bloodthirsty monsters. You have to survive among minecraft zombies and destroy them as much as possible. For each monster you kill, you get gold coins that you can use to buy new weapons and ammunition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Left 4 Dead</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/left-4-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/left-4-dead/</guid>
      <description>An exciting shooter with a very unusual entourage. All the characters in it are made of paper, which does not prevent them from fighting fiercely. You will control one of the fighters, whose task is to clear the building from terrorists. And you will shoot directly from the finger. In this game, the main thing is to dodge enemy shots and collect bonuses as the battle progresses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warzone Online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/warzone-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/warzone-online/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to take part in the battles in the arenas of the Minecraft country. Choose one of the characters provided to you in the menu and one of the locations. On it you have to meet in a combat clash with other players online. Try to destroy the maximum number of enemies in a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
