<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Motorcycles on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/motorcycles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Motorcycles on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/motorcycles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Free bike stunts game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/free-bike-stunts-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/free-bike-stunts-game/</guid>
      <description>A motorcycle is a dangerous form of transport, especially when it is used in mountainous areas. You are fully equipped to overcome the dangerous path, so get ready to descend steep hills and jump over gorges at high speed. Complete all levels, demonstrating flawless execution of the most difficult tricks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moto Stunts 3d game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/moto-stunts-3d-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/moto-stunts-3d-game/</guid>
      <description>In this racing game, you have 4 scenic routes to choose from, each consisting of 6 levels. Perform breathtaking jumps and other stunts to score more points. Be sure that thanks to the realistic gameplay, graphics and sound effects, you will feel every bump on the road and get an unforgettable experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nitro motocross game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/nitro-motocross-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/nitro-motocross-game/</guid>
      <description>Only professionals can participate in arctic races. Surf the snowy expanses on a motorcycle or ATV in this exciting game. Climb and descend the snowy hills without falling or flipping over. Do not forget to collect bonuses that will provide you with additional benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turbo motocross game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/turbo-motocross-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/turbo-motocross-game/</guid>
      <description>In this motorcycle race at each level, you need to score the required number of points to move up the standings. For overtaking rivals, additional bonuses and money are awarded. After the race, you can buy improved motorcycle parts and new clothes for the rider. Use arrow keys to control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X-Trial Racing Mountain Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/x-trial-racing-mountain-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/x-trial-racing-mountain-adventure/</guid>
      <description>There is nothing more pleasant than riding a motorcycle through the forest in warm weather. Race your bike along the mountain trails performing spectacular somersaults. Enjoy driving on different types of terrain, show off your skills behind the wheel of this nimble vehicle. Try to complete all the pirouettes to get the maximum experience and don&amp;rsquo;t be lazy to collect fuel along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
