<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dolphins on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/dolphins/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dolphins on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/dolphins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dolphinarium game for girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dolphinarium-game-for-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dolphinarium-game-for-girls/</guid>
      <description>In this game you find yourself in a small dolphinarium, where you can become a temporary trainer. By controlling the movements of one of the participants in the show, try to perform as many tricks as possible to attract the maximum number of spectators to the water park and earn gold coins to buy new stage costumes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Dolphin Performs 6</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-dolphin-performs-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-dolphin-performs-6/</guid>
      <description>The game Dolphin Performs 6 takes you to the Pacific coast, where the next season of the world-famous dolphinarium begins. It is necessary to organize the work of this entertainment center once again. As in previous seasons, not only administrative work, procurement and employee control will fall on your shoulders, but also the training of the star of the program - the famous dolphin Quickie. Kviki is happy to meet again and will start training with great pleasure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Dolphin Show 7</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-dolphin-show-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-dolphin-show-7/</guid>
      <description>During the game Dolphin Show 7 you go to a small but very cozy dolphinarium, located on the ocean. In it, you will meet wonderful sea animals that regularly delight numerous spectators of the circus on the water with their talents. The hero of the game Dolphin 7 is an excellent actor and a wonderful friend, a favorite of the public and the first star of the show. He invites you to perform with him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Dolphins 5</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-dolphins-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-dolphins-5/</guid>
      <description>The hero of the game Dolphins 5 Fluffy and his friends are going on another tour of the dolphinariums of the Pacific coast. The guys invite you to join them and help Fluffy become the most popular circus animal in the world. Controlling the movements of the dolphin, try to perform all the tricks that the baby&amp;rsquo;s trainers will offer you, and collect the maximum number of spectators who dream of watching the dolphin perform.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
