<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>breadwinners on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/breadwinners/</link>
    <description>Recent content in breadwinners on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/breadwinners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Breadwinner game for two</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/breadwinner-game-for-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/breadwinner-game-for-two/</guid>
      <description>According to the terms of the Breadwinners game for two, you can choose one of the kingdoms inhabited by famous cartoon characters and start playing on behalf of your favorite characters. According to legend, in each magical country there is a special relic that has miraculous properties. And if you collect them all, you can get complete control over the surrounding lands. In the process of playing 2 Duck Bread, you have to organize a competent defense of your kingdom, and then attack others, trying to get all the artifacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breadwinner Kingdom game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/breadwinner-kingdom-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/breadwinner-kingdom-game/</guid>
      <description>Surely, many guys dream of becoming the rulers of an entire kingdom. This game gives you that chance. Create your fortress from scratch, buy new types of weapons and mercenaries for it. Build defensive redoubts, improve your defense and combat skills. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget, Sponge Bob, ninja turtles, bakers, and many other cartoon characters can become your comrades in arms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breadwinners fighting game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/breadwinners-fighting-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/breadwinners-fighting-game/</guid>
      <description>Breadwinners are famous for always organizing some kind of entertainment. This time they decided to hold a tournament of fighting without rules among all the inhabitants of the universe. You will have the opportunity to fight Shredder, SpongeBob, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles and many other cartoon characters. But first you need to choose a fighter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
