<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cowboys on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/cowboys/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cowboys on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/cowboys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cowboy game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cowboy-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cowboy-game/</guid>
      <description>In order for the Cowboy game to start, you will need the Firefox browser. But all possible inconveniences are more than compensated by the gameplay and good graphics. So, the essence of the passage is that the main character must participate in endless fights on the streets of the town of the times of the Wild West. Fights are group fights. The number of participants is 5-6 people. Principle: every man for himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cowboy vs Zombies game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cowboy-vs-zombies-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cowboy-vs-zombies-game/</guid>
      <description>A merciless fight against ungodly zombies is the sacred duty of every real cowboy! For nothing, or what, revolvers in holsters dangle? You are waiting for the passage from the first person. With two Smith &amp;amp; Wessons at the ready, move through the maze and shoot the walking dead. But watch out - they fire back. Collect bonuses falling out of the bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Cowboy Saloon Fight 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cowboy-saloon-fight-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cowboy-saloon-fight-2/</guid>
      <description>Gambling entertainment for fans of a good fight! We bring to your attention the perfect way to let off steam without endangering the peace of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Dangerous Cowboy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-dangerous-cowboy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-dangerous-cowboy/</guid>
      <description>This is a very interesting game, despite the fact that it belongs to a series of shooting games in a virtual shooting range. First, each level consists of several stages. You can shoot hundreds of enemies, but not go to the next stage. And the point is to kill a certain number of bandits in the allotted time. Buy useful things with the money you earn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
