<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>star Wars on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/star-wars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in star Wars on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/star-wars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game for two star wars rebels</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-two-star-wars-rebels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-two-star-wars-rebels/</guid>
      <description>During the game for two Star Wars Rebels, you will be transported to the planet Lothal, which is controlled by the galactic empire. The common people are poor and starving. Once he got tired of it, and brave residents appeared who rebelled against the conquerors. But the enemy forces outnumber the rebels. It takes tactics and planning to win this war. Complete missions one by one and free the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Star Wars episode 4</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-star-wars-episode-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-star-wars-episode-4/</guid>
      <description>Together with the famous captain of the ship &amp;ldquo;Ghost&amp;rdquo; Kanan Jerus and his team, you have to go on a dangerous mission. By controlling the movement of the ship, try to break through the protective formations of the imperial troops, knock out a transport ship and free one of the leaders of the republican underground from captivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Star Wars episode 7</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-star-wars-episode-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-star-wars-episode-7/</guid>
      <description>While playing Star Wars Episode 7, you meet the crew of a rebel ship with the formidable name &amp;ldquo;Ghost&amp;rdquo;. Over the years, the brave men under the command of Kanan Yarus have been destroying the bases of the emperor&amp;rsquo;s troops and performing other dangerous tasks of the rebel leadership. By controlling the movements of the Ghost, try to destroy as many ships of the imperial fleet as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost raid game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ghost-raid-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ghost-raid-game/</guid>
      <description>The crew of the famous spaceship &amp;ldquo;Ghost&amp;rdquo; went on another dangerous mission. Help Captain Kanan Jaruss and his team overcome a huge distance and destroy the warships of the emperor&amp;rsquo;s troops. Chase the space courier ship and take the secret information to the rebel base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebel Chase game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rebel-chase-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rebel-chase-game/</guid>
      <description>The Space Ghost team is on their next mission and invites you to join them. Controlling the movements of the space wanderer, try to break through the armada of the Dark Lord&amp;rsquo;s space cruisers and destroy the huge planet of death that his engineers began to build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Rebels game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/star-wars-rebels-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/star-wars-rebels-game/</guid>
      <description>The Star Wars Rebels game introduces you to the new crew of the famous space shuttle, the Millennium Falcon, and its leader, Kannan Jerus. Together with them, you will once again enter the battle with the army of the Empire. By controlling the movements of the spaceship, try to destroy the maximum number of cargo ships of the imperial fleet carrying building materials to create another planet of death. The passage of the game about the star wars of the rebels will require you to have a good reaction and the ability to make decisions quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star wars the force unleashed game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/star-wars-the-force-unleashed-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/star-wars-the-force-unleashed-game/</guid>
      <description>The game Star wars the force unleashed will tell you about the struggle of the rebels against the forces of the galactic empire. In the dark years of the tyranny of the invaders, there were still a few heroes who risked starting a resistance movement against Sith rule. You have to control a space fighter and perform a variety of missions on enemy territory. The main task is to capture the supplies of the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
