<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logic for girls on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/logic-for-girls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logic for girls on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/logic-for-girls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Draw One Line</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/draw-one-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/draw-one-line/</guid>
      <description>Logic games for girls 8 9 years old offer to help a flying kitten. They have a huge number of levels, on each of which you will see a construction of ice and stone blocks of various shapes. The cat is inside the building, and you need to clear the way for him to fly upstairs. The level will be considered passed when the character of the game for girls 8 9 years old takes off into the air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eater Egg Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/eater-egg-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/eater-egg-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Help the Easter bunny to cope with the invasion of eggs. They rise from below in the form of a wall of elements of different colors. You need to swap eggs, making combinations of four or more identical pieces. After that they will disappear. You need to act as quickly as possible so that in the end the wall does not grow too high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancy Birds Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fancy-birds-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fancy-birds-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Play an exciting game with funny birds. You need to swap feathered characters in order to get combinations of three or more identical individuals. Such combinations of birds will disappear. The task is to score the specified number of points. Try to act fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Glass Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-glass-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-glass-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to fill bottles with water. But it won&amp;rsquo;t be easy to do so! Before you will be several vessels of different sizes, and the task will be presented in the upper part. It will tell you exactly how many liters of water and in which bottle you need to pour. As soon as you do this, a new level will open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Cats Love Story</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hello-cats-love-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hello-cats-love-story/</guid>
      <description>You are waiting for a game that will require maximum care. A field with multi-colored hearts will be displayed on the screen. Your task is to swap adjacent elements, forming combinations of three or more identical fragments. Such combinations will disappear. You need to score a certain number of points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Balls 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/love-balls-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/love-balls-2/</guid>
      <description>Help the character of this game to meet his beloved. You will find a huge number of levels, on each of which you need to get to the bench where the girl is sitting. Overcome various obstacles, collect sweets and turn the world around if necessary. With each stage, the game becomes more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rat And Cheese</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rat-and-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rat-and-cheese/</guid>
      <description>The mouse loves cheese very much, but is afraid to leave the mink to get a treat. You need to help the rodent. The task is to move the cheese so that it ends up in the mouse hole. At each location there are many obstacles, but there are also useful items that will help you cope with the task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snail Bob 7 Fantasy Story</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/snail-bob-7-fantasy-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/snail-bob-7-fantasy-story/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will meet a snail named Bob. It is necessary to help him deal with the obstacles that interfere with the path. This will help all sorts of mechanisms that are activated when using levers and buttons. The game consists of a huge number of different levels, where you can not do without ingenuity and attentiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
