<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hidden Objects on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/hidden-objects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hidden Objects on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/hidden-objects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Desert Flower</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/desert-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/desert-flower/</guid>
      <description>Games Finding objects for girls is a training of attentiveness and perseverance. Every girl dreams of a luxurious wedding. But marriage is not only a colorful solemn part, it is also a huge amount of trouble. You need to prepare everything, dress, jewelry, shoes. Absolutely free of charge you will travel from location to location, where in a short time you need to find all the items that are simply necessary for the celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/essential-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/essential-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Today you will have to plunge into the world of cinema. To shoot a real masterpiece, you will need a lot of scenery and all kinds of attributes, from clothes to shooting tools. You have to find all the things indicated at the bottom of the screen for a certain period of time. The task is not easy, so do not waste time and start searching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farm Rules</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/farm-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/farm-rules/</guid>
      <description>Uptasia Hidden Object Game is designed for toddlers. You have to find all the numbers in the photo of two cute cats. There are no hints in the game, and this is a very big minus. But the good thing is that time is not limited here, so you can search for numbers indefinitely without worrying that the game will end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Hidden Stars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/food-hidden-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/food-hidden-stars/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will need maximum attention and observation. You have to look for the stars hidden in the picture. But during the day, such searches are very difficult. You have only 5 minutes to complete the task, and you can earn bonus points if you meet this time. In total, you need to find 40 stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess the Murderer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/guess-the-murderer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/guess-the-murderer/</guid>
      <description>You have to play the role of a detective, whose main task is to find one or another missing item. This time, the search for the boot will take place in a large room, and you need to find everything that is shown at the bottom of the screen. Use the mouse for this purpose and, as soon as you find the item you are looking for, click on it with the left button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Christmas Cookies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hidden-christmas-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hidden-christmas-cookies/</guid>
      <description>There is a huge amount of food hidden in this restaurant. And you have to use your bow and arrows again to search for different goodies. Look carefully at the picture and try to find all the &amp;ldquo;edible&amp;rdquo; objects in the allotted time by sending arrows at them. Food can be not only on the tables, but also in other places that are not at all intended for food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Jingle Bells</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hidden-jingle-bells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hidden-jingle-bells/</guid>
      <description>In the game you will have a great chance to test your powers of observation. Find all the letters in each level of this colorful game dedicated to your favorite fabulous holiday - New Year. Use your mouse to search. Try to avoid random clicks on empty space, because then your points will decrease. And remember, time is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Object Game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hidden-object-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hidden-object-game/</guid>
      <description>Today you have a dangerous job. You need to find and neutralize a certain number of bombs in the picture. For this you have a bow and arrows. Having found another explosive device, feel free to send an arrow at it. So you can neutralize the dangerous object and save the locals from disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitchen Secrets</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kitchen-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kitchen-secrets/</guid>
      <description>You are participating in the city competition - &amp;lsquo;Cleanliness and order in the workplace&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;. But the local storekeeper went on vacation, and at the end of the working day, the store is in complete chaos, in which it is simply impossible to make out where and what is. You need to quickly remove all unnecessary items in all rooms, referring to the list at the bottom of the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magicians Carnival</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/magicians-carnival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/magicians-carnival/</guid>
      <description>In front of you is a football stadium tribune filled with fans. But some of them are wearing masks. These people obviously planned some kind of provocation from which civilians could suffer. Now you are entrusted with a responsible mission - to find among the countless crowd of fans in masks. You need to do this with a bow and arrows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saving Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/saving-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/saving-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Today you have to cope with the New Year&amp;rsquo;s task, namely, to decorate the Christmas tree. But for this you need toys and decorations. Here they will have to be found in this motley picture. Click the mouse button on the necessary things, and they will immediately be on the forest beauty. Everything you need will be marked on the bottom line of the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Railway Detectives</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-railway-detectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-railway-detectives/</guid>
      <description>The inspector is approached with a very delicate request, as the police are unable to help. Your task is to investigate the crime, find evidence that was not seen, and get on the trail of the suspect. To do this, you need to carefully examine all the rooms in the house and find evidence that will help unravel the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Pyramid</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-secret-pyramid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-secret-pyramid/</guid>
      <description>According to the terms of the Hidden Object mini-game, you will have to help the main character, the clever and beautiful Natalie Brooks, over 7 levels. This time she needs to save the life of her grandfather, who was kidnapped by unknown villains. The girl has only 24 hours to find artifacts, and at the same time unravel some important secrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valley of Mummies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/valley-of-mummies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/valley-of-mummies/</guid>
      <description>In the picture, which shows various household items of Ancient Egypt, you need to find the disguised objects. The list of things to find is at the bottom under the main image. A certain amount of time is given to complete the task. If you fail to meet the allotted limit, the level will have to start from the very beginning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
