<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ABC on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/abc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ABC on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/abc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse &amp; Friends Learn ABC</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/arty-mouse--friends-learn-abc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/arty-mouse--friends-learn-abc/</guid>
      <description>The ABC game will appeal to the smallest fans of computer entertainment. You find yourself in a magical land and become the head of the railway station. He is instructed to seat animals on the wagons and load objects into them, the first letter of the name of which corresponds to the letter on the locomotive pulling the train. Hurry up, because the machinist mouse is in a hurry to hit the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cars Hidden Alphabet</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cars-hidden-alphabet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cars-hidden-alphabet/</guid>
      <description>The Alphabet game for children aged 3-4 invites gamers to visit a fabulous city where wonderful letter-men live. You have to go through its streets and find all the locals. Carefully inspect every nook and cranny and find letters that dream of hiding from you. Your finds will go to the bottom of the screen and line up there in even rows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Fun</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/school-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/school-fun/</guid>
      <description>The Alphabet game sends you to a fairy-tale kingdom, where you will have to demonstrate all your attentiveness. Carefully inspect one of the most beautiful corners of the magical land, try to find all the letters of the Russian alphabet placed on it. Use the mouse cursor to point to the found letters, and they will instantly disappear from the screen. In order not to make a mistake and not miss anything, at the bottom of the game screen there is a hint with a list of letters that you need to find.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
