<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shooting games for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting-games-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shooting games for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting-games-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blob Tank Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/blob-tank-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/blob-tank-wars/</guid>
      <description>You have an unusual tank at your disposal. And his shells are not simple - multi-colored paints. So you are waiting for a fun shooter and no violence, just a lot of bright colors. For killing an enemy, a certain amount of points is required, which can be used to buy new abilities that are valid throughout the entire level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bois.io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bois.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bois.io/</guid>
      <description>You are one of the rebels who have been preparing all their lives for a decisive battle with a formidable enemy in the form of artificial intelligence. And now the moment has come when the robots are not yet very strong and are busy creating their own kind. You will have to get into the very heart of their colony in order to destroy the enemy base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Pixel Apocalypse 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-pixel-apocalypse-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-pixel-apocalypse-3/</guid>
      <description>Your task is to save your home planet from the attack of invaders who are not very friendly towards the locals. Who wins this war depends on your reaction and dexterity, since at the same time you have to make sure that you are not bombed and attack yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freaky Factory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/freaky-factory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/freaky-factory/</guid>
      <description>You have to manage a little gnome who went to the dungeon in search of a treasure. On the way, a lot of green monsters are waiting for him, which can only be destroyed with the help of a magic staff. After each enemy killed, energy crystals remain. They need to be collected in order to increase their strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martian Alien Combat</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/martian-alien-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/martian-alien-combat/</guid>
      <description>Terrorists have seized 10 very important objects and are going to blow them up. To prevent this, a special elite detachment of the tactical unit is taken to work. Your task is to eliminate the emerging threat, destroy the bandits and free the captured hostages. You have to go through 10 difficult levels and complete the mission without loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Invasion</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-invasion/</guid>
      <description>The main condition for playing a shooter game for two Weapons of Chaos 2 is to survive, which means you need to move quickly, jump from platform to platform and shoot at the enemy with all types of weapons available. By the way, machine guns and pistols can be picked up right during the game. And the more powerful your gun, the more chances to win. But with each next level of the shooting game for two, the conditions of the struggle become more difficult, so you need to act quickly and shoot accurately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neon Tank Arena</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/neon-tank-arena/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/neon-tank-arena/</guid>
      <description>An exciting tank battle in which the winner is the one who has a more accurate eye and a good reaction. You have to develop your own battle strategy, which will take the enemy by surprise. Use the mouse to choose the trajectory of the projectile and open fire on the enemy. When shooting, do not forget to take into account the strength and direction of the wind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Battle Royale Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-battle-royale-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-battle-royale-multiplayer/</guid>
      <description>Fights in the sky are getting fiercer, the only way to get the upper hand in air combat is to use the latest fighters. Thanks to improved engines and weapons, your aircraft is capable of single-handedly fighting an entire enemy army. Use arrow keys to control. Space button - shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Warrior</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-warrior/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-warrior/</guid>
      <description>The essence of the game for two Shooters against zombies is that you just need to stop the horde of the dead heading into the city. This exciting flash toy allows you to create warriors and send them along the selected paths towards the enemy. Use the money you earn from battles to buy new troops and equip them with more powerful weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pubg Pixel</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pubg-pixel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pubg-pixel/</guid>
      <description>A rather simple game in which you have to quickly destroy your opponent. At the beginning of the battle, you have a certain amount of money to purchase weapons. And the outcome of the battle may depend on how correct his choice will be. Each accurate shot brings additional income that can be spent on character upgrades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TankHit</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tankhit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tankhit/</guid>
      <description>During the game for two Shooters 1 on 1 you have to survive during the battle in the jungle with the local natives. To provide more effective resistance to the enemy, break all the wooden boxes that will catch your eye during the battle. There are more powerful weapons and explosives. But from time to time you will have to participate in hand-to-hand combat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
