<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>old games on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/old-games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in old games on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/old-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Candy Blast</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-blast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-blast/</guid>
      <description>In candy land, you are invited to solve a Tetris-like puzzle by finding straight or broken lines from colored candies. If found, click. Accumulations of sweets are burned, the top ones are shifted down and new ones are added. And you get points accordingly. The more lollipops you burn at once, the more points you earn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Prophecy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dark-prophecy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dark-prophecy/</guid>
      <description>How good it is to while away the long winter evenings with friends in a cozy country house near the fireplace. Today you are just waiting for guests, and the room, to put it mildly, is a mess. Therefore, rather, take the mouse in your hands and put everything in its place. At the bottom of the screen you will see items and things that you need to remove by clicking on them with the left button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>game siding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-siding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-siding/</guid>
      <description>Have you been playing with the railway and trains for a long time? In our game, you can remember this fun, and even engage in cargo transportation. The task of the gamer is to switch the arrows in time and direct the train along the desired route so that he can collect the cargo, take it to the right place, and also collect the reward due. The number of wagons will grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latina Princess Spa Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/latina-princess-spa-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/latina-princess-spa-day/</guid>
      <description>masks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Drop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/red-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/red-drop/</guid>
      <description>The hardest in the world 3</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
