<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dress up on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/dress-up/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dress up on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/dress-up/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adventure time dress up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/adventure-time-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/adventure-time-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>If you love inventing new outfits, then funny dress up games for girls are just for you. Here you will get to London, where you can go shopping, getting fashionable things. Use purchased wardrobe items to create party outfits and get reward points to increase your ranking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Girls Dress Up Fun</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-girls-dress-up-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-girls-dress-up-fun/</guid>
      <description>During the family dress up game for girls, you will have to choose clothes for a young mother who has decided to go for a walk with her little daughter. But first, come up with original hairstyles for mom and daughter. Then pick out clothes for the whole family. Try to make it not only comfortable, but also stylish. Do not forget to pick up original jewelry for the adorable mother that will emphasize her beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bff Matching Tattoos</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bff-matching-tattoos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bff-matching-tattoos/</guid>
      <description>For girls dress up girlfriends 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonnie Christmas Parties</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-christmas-parties/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-christmas-parties/</guid>
      <description>During the game Dress Up Models, you are invited to prepare the girls for the performance on the podium. To start, choose three fashion models, and then prepare outfits in accordance with the style of each of them. At the end of the game, your results will be evaluated by a specialist who will certainly point out the mistakes made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonny Spy Squad</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonny-spy-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonny-spy-squad/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you can become a cute girl&amp;rsquo;s stylist for a while. Try to create a nice image for her, using all the possibilities offered. Here you can change the outfit, hairstyle and even facial expressions. Thanks to the variety of elements provided, you can even come up with several options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Model Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/car-model-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/car-model-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Gossip girls just need to go out in public so that they have someone to discuss the latest rumors with. But how do you leave the house without a good outfit? After all, friends will start gossiping here! Help the girl not to lose her face and dress her up to the highest standard. In this game, you can even choose the skin color of the heroine, and print the finished version on a printer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Girl Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cat-girl-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cat-girl-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Many people know the interesting cartoon &amp;ldquo;Fairy Tail&amp;rdquo;. The process of playing Fairy Tail Dress Up invites you to dress up Lucy - the heroine of this cartoon series. There are many interesting little things that will perfectly fit the girl and make her even more pretty. In addition to a variety of outfits, the game features a huge number of accessories to help complete the look. The finished result can be saved or printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colors Of Spring Princess Gowns</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/colors-of-spring-princess-gowns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/colors-of-spring-princess-gowns/</guid>
      <description>While playing Princess and Queen Dress Up, you become one of the dressers involved in the filming of a new horror movie. You have to prepare a young actress for one of the scenes in the movie. Make her an original hairstyle and choose a costume that matches her role. The outfit you created will give confidence to the actress-princess, and the shooting with her participation will go as well as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dove Shopping Day Dolly Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dove-shopping-day-dolly-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dove-shopping-day-dolly-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Start the process of hairdresser and dress up game for girls and become a hairdressing specialist. Here you will perform the functions of an employee of a beauty salon, to which girls invariably come who want to get an excellent hairstyle and makeup. To get started, choose the hairstyle that you want to do to the client, and then get to work, following the prompts. First you need to wash your hair, and then use a comb to form the selected styling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elsa Ice Skating Injuries</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-ice-skating-injuries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-ice-skating-injuries/</guid>
      <description>While playing Ice Skating Girl Dress Up, you will prepare an outfit for a girl who skates. She&amp;rsquo;s got a big performance coming up, and you need to think carefully about the right look. It will consist of a dress, tights, skates, gloves, various cute additions, like a headband.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Girl New Dress</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fashion-girl-new-dress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fashion-girl-new-dress/</guid>
      <description>dressers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forest Fairy Dressup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/forest-fairy-dressup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/forest-fairy-dressup/</guid>
      <description>During the Fairy Tail anime dress up game, you have to come up with an image for the cartoon character. Everyone who has seen this animated series has a rough idea of ​​how the heroines Elsa, Lucy and others look like. And if you start playing this game, you can create an anime girl like them yourself. To do this, you are provided with a huge variety of outfits, as well as hairstyles, shoes and accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girls Fix It - Bunny Car</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/girls-fix-it---bunny-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/girls-fix-it---bunny-car/</guid>
      <description>During the Spring Dress Up game for girls, you meet a couple of young people. The lovers are preparing for the wedding, but before that they want to have a fun photo shoot. You have to prepare the guys for filming. Spring, warm weather and sunshine leaves its mark on the style of clothing. Choose for each of the lovers a fashionable hairstyle, stylish clothes and shoes. Thanks to your help, the photo shoot will be great, and her best photos will take their rightful place in the future family album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gwens Holiday Closet</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gwens-holiday-closet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gwens-holiday-closet/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to dress up a girl in punk style. For this, the most informal things are collected here, which, however, look very nice. Combine wardrobe items in the most harmonious way to get a cool new outfit option. And the finished image can be saved or printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Princess In Nyc</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-in-nyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-in-nyc/</guid>
      <description>One of the heroines of the animated film &amp;ldquo;Frozen&amp;rdquo; - Elsa, is invited to the New Year holidays in her fiancé&amp;rsquo;s house. The girl really wants to make a good impression on her lover&amp;rsquo;s parents and asks you to help her in choosing the right outfit. Create an original New Year&amp;rsquo;s sweater for her and pick up festive accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jenner Sisters Buzzfeed Worth It</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jenner-sisters-buzzfeed-worth-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jenner-sisters-buzzfeed-worth-it/</guid>
      <description>A couple in love decided to organize a photo shoot on the beach. The guys invited you as a stylist and photographer. During the House 2 dress up game, you have to choose original outfits for lovers, a suitable landscape for a photo and shoot, which will be remembered by young people for a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jenner Sisters Spooky Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jenner-sisters-spooky-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jenner-sisters-spooky-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to dress up an adorable elf who loves cute things. Even forest dwellers want to look attractive! So start working immediately. Choose the right hairstyle, clothes, shoes and accessories for the girl. The heroine of this interesting game will definitely like the result!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessies Shiba Dog</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessies-shiba-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessies-shiba-dog/</guid>
      <description>Many owners take care of their pets as well as their family members. Dogs often get cool outfits! In Dog Dress Up game for girls you have to dress up your four-legged friend, turning an ordinary dog ​​into a real fashionable creature. You will have a lot of stylish things at your disposal!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians Graduation</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kardashians-graduation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kardashians-graduation/</guid>
      <description>In Celebrity Dress Up you will have to become the personal stylist of famous actress Kristen Stewart. Kristen is getting ready for a photo shoot for a popular fashion magazine. Successful makeup and hairstyle are very important for a popular actress. After that, choose from the rich play wardrobe for girls the things you need to create a fashionable look, as well as jewelry and accessories that will emphasize the beauty of their owner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians Spooky Makeup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kardashians-spooky-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kardashians-spooky-makeup/</guid>
      <description>During the Zombie Dress Up game for girls, a rather unusual model is waiting for you. The heroine of the game is a zombie, but nevertheless looks quite feminine and attractive. Your task is to come up with a stylish look for the girl using any of the suggested elements. The game consists of two stages, first you need to do makeup, and then you can start shaping the outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Land Vs Sea Moana Vs Elsa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/land-vs-sea-moana-vs-elsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/land-vs-sea-moana-vs-elsa/</guid>
      <description>Cute cartoon princess Elsa always strives to dress up in cute outfits and do cool hairstyles. This time she decided to turn to you for help. Choose from the proposed range of the most fashionable little things and create an attractive image for the heroine of the game. It is also worth doing makeup!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Fashion: Greek Goddess</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/legendary-fashion-greek-goddess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/legendary-fashion-greek-goddess/</guid>
      <description>The game Tudor Dress Up invites you to invent characters in a medieval style. First, decide who you want to create - a guy or a girl. Next, proceed to the selection of elements of the image, and you can change the color of any thing at your discretion. If desired, you can even add patterns that make clothes even more original.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mabel Dress Up Game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mabel-dress-up-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mabel-dress-up-game/</guid>
      <description>In Girls Coloring Book Dress Up you will see a fashionable girl who loves to dress stylishly. It&amp;rsquo;s time to show your creativity, creating modern images from the presented elements. The game is good because it allows you to slightly change the appearance of things you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Baby Bath</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-baby-bath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-baby-bath/</guid>
      <description>Little girls also want to look attractive and dress up in beautiful dresses. And if we are talking about a princess, then a lot depends on the outfits! You have to create a chic image for the baby using a virtual wardrobe for this. There you will find dresses, and crowns, and shoes, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Mix N Match</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-mix-n-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-mix-n-match/</guid>
      <description>Mermaid Dress Up game invites you to join Ariel and her friends for a photo session. The company decided to take some funny photos for memory and invites you to help them in choosing funny images. Choose original costumes for each of the characters, and when you&amp;rsquo;re done, take pictures of your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miss Halloween Princess</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/miss-halloween-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/miss-halloween-princess/</guid>
      <description>During Girls Dress Up Game for Girls you have to choose clothes for a guy who is getting ready to meet his sweetheart. Help the young man to choose stylish clothes and accessories. With this colorful dress up game you will be able to prove that not only girls need the help of a professional stylist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monsterfy Lady Gaga</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monsterfy-lady-gaga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monsterfy-lady-gaga/</guid>
      <description>During the game Dazzlings Dress Up, you will meet a girl who personifies the pony Twilight Sparkle. Usually she dresses in purple and pink, but now you can expand the heroine&amp;rsquo;s wardrobe and choose completely different colors for clothes. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget the variety of accessories!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Pretty Doll Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-pretty-doll-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-pretty-doll-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>After starting Stardoll Dress Up game you will see Snow White who lives in the forest. You need to come up with a new outfit for her, complementing it with stylish accessories. Do not forget about the hairstyle, because even living in a dense forest, you want to look as impressive as possible. Especially when it comes to the princess!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party Time Ocean Princesses</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/party-time-ocean-princesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/party-time-ocean-princesses/</guid>
      <description>Any representative of the fair sex always wants to look attractive and fashionable. Game for girls Dress Up invites you to work a little as a stylist and create new spectacular images for the heroine. You have a huge variety of clothes at your disposal, and you can combine any elements of the wardrobe as you wish. The result will be incredibly spectacular! And do not forget to pay attention to the compatibility of the selected parts of the image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Prom Dressup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/perfect-prom-dressup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/perfect-prom-dressup/</guid>
      <description>And again the theme of prom dresses. This time you need to dress up the girl so that she will definitely receive the audience award and become the queen of the prom. If you find it difficult to harmoniously select the details of the costume, look at the ready-made options by clicking on the question mark image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant Anne Dressing Room</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pregnant-anne-dressing-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pregnant-anne-dressing-room/</guid>
      <description>Pregnant Mommy Dress Up introduces you to a wonderful mom-to-be who needs help. She is just going to visit and can not choose the right clothes. During the free game for girls, you have to choose a beautiful outfit for the pregnant beauty. Do not forget to give her a stylish hairstyle and original makeup that will emphasize the natural heroine. The beauty will be grateful for the service rendered and, for sure, will turn to you more than once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Dress In Incredible 2 Style</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-dress-in-incredible-2-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-dress-in-incredible-2-style/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to become a stylist for a cute girl. Your task is to make her makeup and choose the perfect outfit for the festive event. For make-up, the game features a large number of decorative cosmetics: blush, mascara, lipstick. And in addition to chic dresses, there are tiaras, gloves and other accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess dressing room</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-dressing-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-dressing-room/</guid>
      <description>Snow White was walking in the forest and tore her beautiful dress. Therefore, you should create a new, no less charming outfit for her. To do this, it is proposed to use several parts. Choose the style of the top and skirt, and then decide on their colors. Complete the game by choosing your hairstyle and shoes. Hair color can be changed too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Dressup 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-dressup-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-dressup-3d/</guid>
      <description>The exciting process of playing Dress Up 3D implies that you need to create a cool image for the main character. In it, players are given ample opportunities, and you can choose fashionable blouses, skirts, trousers, and dresses for the girl. In addition to outfits, various accessories are presented that will complement the image of the heroine. Do not forget about the possibility of choosing a hairstyle, try to find the best styling option for the girl, which will make her even more beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Fanny Packs</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-fanny-packs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-fanny-packs/</guid>
      <description>Two sisters are going on a summer outing and you need to create cool fashionable outfits for the girls. To do this, the assortment of the game Dress Up for Sisters Girls provides a large number of blouses, skirts, trousers and other clothes. There are all kinds of accessories here, and you can also change the hairstyle of each of the heroines. Try to achieve the most attractive result!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Met Gala</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-met-gala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-met-gala/</guid>
      <description>During the game Ariel Dress Up for Girls you will see the famous Disney underwater princess. You have to work on her image, using decorative cosmetics and an assortment of stylish swimsuits. In addition, you can change her hairstyle by choosing a new stylish option. The game features several hair styling options that differ in shape and color. As a result, you can change the well-known Ariel beyond recognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Sweater Weather</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-sweater-weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-sweater-weather/</guid>
      <description>During the Autumn Dress Up game for girls, you are invited to work on the image of a girl who is going for a walk. She needs to choose the right outfit in which the heroine will look spectacular and in which she will be as comfortable as possible. Use all kinds of wardrobe items for this, which are perfect for cool autumn weather. There are jackets, trousers, hats, scarves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Winter Olympics</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-winter-olympics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-winter-olympics/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will be taken to a gym where a girl is playing basketball. She needs comfortable and at the same time cute clothes in which she can have a great time playing sports. Choose the right suit for the heroine of the game and change her hairstyle to get a harmonious look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queen Of Glitter Prom Ball</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/queen-of-glitter-prom-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/queen-of-glitter-prom-ball/</guid>
      <description>This game will surely appeal to most girls. But boys can also like it, because the princess who needs to be dressed up is quite capable of taking a prize at a world beauty contest. It is possible that the ball is arranged on this occasion. For such an event, the heroine of the game must be dressed appropriately. Gamers have an impressive wardrobe at their disposal, as well as a good selection of hairstyles and accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sailor Scouts Summer Style</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sailor-scouts-summer-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sailor-scouts-summer-style/</guid>
      <description>Start the process of playing Sailor Moon dress up for girls and meet the heroine of the famous animated series. Your task is simple: you need to create a new image for her, using any of the proposed elements. Here you are provided with all kinds of blouses, skirts and cute dresses. The chosen outfit should be supplemented with gloves, earrings and other accessories. And Sailor Moon can&amp;rsquo;t do without a magic wand!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sery Shopping Day Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sery-shopping-day-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sery-shopping-day-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Informals always stand out from the crowd, striving to achieve originality with the help of bright and unusual outfits. The fascinating process of playing Dress Up for informals invites you to meet a girl who knows a lot about everything unusual. Now she wants to get a new outfit for herself, and you will definitely help her with this. Use the suggested t-shirts, skirts, jeans and other informal wardrobe items to get an attractive result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow White Fairytale Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-white-fairytale-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-white-fairytale-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>Everyone knows the fairy tale about Snow White - a sweet princess who lived in the forest with seven dwarfs. Launching the Snow White Dress Up game will take you to visit her and offer you to create a new outfit for the girl. Everything is as simple as possible here: change the headdress, jewelry, dress and accessories in your hands. Nothing else needs to be done!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stranger Things Christmas Party</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stranger-things-christmas-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stranger-things-christmas-party/</guid>
      <description>The process of the game for girls Dress Up for 6 years involves choosing an outfit for a young fashionista. Here you will meet a cute girl who, despite her age, already knows a lot about fashionable outfits. You are invited to create a cool image for her. The game has everything a little fashionista needs: fluffy skirts, colorful corsets, huge bows. Do not forget about choosing a hairstyle, try to find an option that is most suitable for a 6-year-old girl.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
