<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Football for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/football-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Football for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/football-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Funny Soccer Game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/funny-soccer-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/funny-soccer-game/</guid>
      <description>In this fun football simulator, you have to control a big-headed player, fighting 1 on 1 with opponents. A distinctive feature of the match is a huge number of bonuses. In order to get them, you need to touch a certain icon with a ball. But be careful, try not to take those that will only complicate your passage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer Master</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/soccer-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/soccer-master/</guid>
      <description>According to the rules of the Football 2013 game for two, you will have to fight with an opponent, hitting the ball only with your head. For each win or draw, money is awarded for which you can upgrade your player. For example, it is possible to increase the height of the jump, make a stronger blow or speed up the player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Soccer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/winter-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/winter-soccer/</guid>
      <description>In this football confrontation, you are given the choice of championship mode, where you need to go through the entire standings, or a single match against an opponent. There is a training mode that will help novice gamers get comfortable with the controls. Crazy Games as many balls as possible to the opponent and try not to miss a goal in your own net.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
