<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Car racing on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/car-racing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Car racing on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/car-racing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ambulance Driver</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ambulance-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ambulance-driver/</guid>
      <description>In Fire Truck Racing you will feel like a firefighter. But this time there is no need to extinguish the fires, because the firefighters simply decided to drive along the tracks in order to determine the fastest driver. Drive your car, overtake rivals and finish first. Don&amp;rsquo;t run into black puddles, they slow down your car a lot. You can play these firefighter racing games online for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Hills</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/high-hills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/high-hills/</guid>
      <description>During the game Car racing in the dirt you will find a unique competition on tracks that not every car will pass. But you got a unique racing car, on which you will definitely pass any obstacles. In addition to you, several other drivers are participating in the race, and you need to overtake all rivals in order to win and go to the next stage. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect coins and other bonus items along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racing Cars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/racing-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/racing-cars/</guid>
      <description>An excellent Car racing game invites you to go on a race along a dangerous track. In it you have the opportunity to choose a car, but at the very beginning only one option is open. You can unlock the rest of the cars as you progress, collecting a certain number of colorful cubes that will often be found along the way. Also during the race you will come across gold coins, they are also worth collecting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
