<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shooting games for kids on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting-games-for-kids/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shooting games for kids on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting-games-for-kids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Archer Master 3D: Castle Defence</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/archer-master-3d-castle-defence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/archer-master-3d-castle-defence/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to test yourself, can you become a sniper? This game offers to shoot at targets, and determine if you are suitable for joining the army as a marksman. The meaning of the game is quite simple. Targets appear ahead at different distances, and you need to shoot them. Moreover, it is desirable to do this quickly and accurately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billy The Kid</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/billy-the-kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/billy-the-kid/</guid>
      <description>Today you have to fight alone with a whole army of bandits and criminals. There is nowhere to retreat, so shoot at your enemies or throw dynamite at them - it will be easier to get rid of a whole group of enemies at once. Collect coins that fall out of the defeated enemy and buy yourself new weapons and additional protection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Sniper</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ghost-sniper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ghost-sniper/</guid>
      <description>A huge and terrible dragon kidnapped the princess and took her to his castle. In fact, it was just a transformation that allowed the evil wizard to take possession of the charming girl. You must urgently save the heir to the throne. Armed with a bow and arrows, you need to get through the forests and swamps, trying to save the princess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hitman Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hitman-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hitman-rush/</guid>
      <description>German invaders roam the streets of your city, and you, like a true patriot, stood up for his defense. You have a machine gun, cartridges, grenades and a great desire to free the area from the enemy. Use the slightest cover to fire, collect first-aid kits that will allow you to restore health, and do not forget to pick up boxes of ammo in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neon Battleground</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/neon-battleground/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/neon-battleground/</guid>
      <description>Shooting games for 4 years old are not provided, so they are not fully understood in this game. But there are funny cat characters that you need to control. There is a whole team in front of you, and it must be brought to the finish line in full force. Management is simple and is carried out only with the mouse. The stages are relatively short, but very varied. The game is distributed free of charge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Man Invasion</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/one-man-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/one-man-invasion/</guid>
      <description>You have to, driving a small plane, break through to your base, which will not be so easy, because hundreds of enemy planes are moving towards you. Destroy the enemy and collect the coins that have fallen out of him. With this money you can buy extra lives, new weapons and equipment for the aircraft. During the battle, make sure that the gun does not overheat, otherwise problems cannot be avoided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Warfare 4 WebGL</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-warfare-4-webgl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-warfare-4-webgl/</guid>
      <description>You play on behalf of a special agent of the ninja task force, whose task is to carry out a secret intelligence operation. There is information that a large-scale creation of nuclear weapons has begun in North Korea in order to prepare for a long-planned war. Use your skills to destroy all blueprints and documents of the secret laboratory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shooterz</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/shooterz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/shooterz/</guid>
      <description>Zombies have infiltrated the city and are trying to infect the locals with a deadly virus. Destroy them, collecting cash bonuses, which will give you the opportunity to improve your combat arsenal. The character is controlled using the arrow keys, shooting - with the left mouse button. Kill all the monsters before they infect the population of the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Untamed</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/untamed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/untamed/</guid>
      <description>Terrorists have infiltrated the White House. President Bush was under threat - the bandits got to the Oval Office. But Bush is a good guy: he takes out a rifle and starts shooting back. Your task is to help the head of state deal with the attackers. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to dodge shots and reload the magazine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
