<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mahjong butterflies on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/mahjong-butterflies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mahjong butterflies on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/mahjong-butterflies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Black And White Dimensions</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/black-and-white-dimensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/black-and-white-dimensions/</guid>
      <description>An interesting game, captivating, first of all, with its design. All chips on the playing field are divided into black and white. Thanks to this, an exciting gameplay awaits you, which consists in removing pairs of identical tiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butterfly Kyodai</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/butterfly-kyodai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/butterfly-kyodai/</guid>
      <description>In order to become the winner of the game Mahjong logical butterflies, you will need attentiveness and ingenuity. The authors propose to collect butterflies from individual wings placed on the playing field. As soon as two identical wings are found, they turn into a beautiful butterfly, which, waving its newly acquired wings at you, flies off the screen. Be careful and try to create all the butterflies as quickly as possible, because the time to complete the task is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flower Slide Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/flower-slide-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/flower-slide-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>The Butterfly Mahjong game is one of the variants of the popular puzzle game, which is laid out on the table not in the form of a pyramid, but in one plane. The rules, however, do not change in this case - only tiles located at the edges work. They depict halves of beautiful butterflies, and if you find paired fragments, they will connect, and the whole butterfly will fly away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flower Tower Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/flower-tower-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/flower-tower-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>A very beautiful and well-known mahjong logic game &amp;ldquo;Flowerland&amp;rdquo; will appeal to all lovers of puzzles. You will find a huge number of different colors on the screen. Similar images need to be removed. A little time is allocated for the passage, but for each pair found, you are added a few seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jungle Connect</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jungle-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jungle-connect/</guid>
      <description>Destroy the tiles, with the same images printed on them, in pairs. You can remove no more than two identical pictures from the field at a time. The selected tiles must be open on three sides: right, left and top. A simple layout option is available for amateurs and a timed game for professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
