<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>paw patrol on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/paw-patrol/</link>
    <description>Recent content in paw patrol on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/paw-patrol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Paw Patrol 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-paw-patrol-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-paw-patrol-2/</guid>
      <description>Today the puppies have master classes in rescue missions. The rider starts first. He will race in his police car along the track. All he has to do is collect nine little ducks. Every time when, together with the racer, you collect the first three, a truck will drive up to you and the ducks will jump into the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Paw Patrol 2 Find Your Mate</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-paw-patrol-2-find-your-mate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-paw-patrol-2-find-your-mate/</guid>
      <description>To successfully complete this game, you will need to get together and get ready to press the mouse button. One of the dogs will appear in front of you. You need to quickly find the same puppy at the bottom of the screen, and click on it with the mouse. Before the end of the level, you need to find as many identical dogs as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Paw Patrol catch food</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-paw-patrol-catch-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-paw-patrol-catch-food/</guid>
      <description>Help the paw patrol collect as much food as possible. At your disposal is a special device from which chops, chicken legs and other goodies are thrown out. It remains only to choose the right flight path so that the food is right inside the fire tower. Time to pass is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Rocket Paw Patrol</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-rocket-paw-patrol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-rocket-paw-patrol/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you have to help a cute dog who needs to collect a lot of bones. Move forward and only forward, jumping up if necessary. Try to avoid dangers, otherwise, if you encounter a trap, the game will immediately end. After the loss, if desired, you can restart the process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
