<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robber Bob on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/robber-bob/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Robber Bob on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/robber-bob/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bob The Robber</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber/</guid>
      <description>The protagonist of the game Bob the Robber 1 is a police officer who works as a night watchman in a history museum. Usually, his work is boring, but one night a robber got into the room. The user&amp;rsquo;s task is to help the guard to detain the thief before he escapes. View from a third person, control - keyboard. The process of the game about 1 robber Bob looks like a race along the corridor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob The Robber 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-2/</guid>
      <description>Take control of the thief Bob and roam the city wreaking havoc on your way. Taught by bitter experience, the townspeople are trying to protect their home. But no matter what alarms and guards they install at their homes, Bob can bypass any obstacles. Often a strong wooden bat comes to his aid. She easily neutralizes all kinds of security robots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob the Robber 5 The Temple Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-5-the-temple-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bob-the-robber-5-the-temple-adventure/</guid>
      <description>In this game, the user (first-person view) will have to steal the century from the Museum of History. Initially, he did not have any equipment for this. But if you look around carefully, you can find a lot of useful things. All of them fall into the inventory and you will have to think carefully about what and how to apply. If it&amp;rsquo;s really difficult, press the hint button.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
