<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cars on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/cars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cars on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/cars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Car Wash</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/car-wash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/car-wash/</guid>
      <description>The process of playing Cars on Big Wheels allows you to take part in an extreme race. Drive a fast and powerful car, moving along the track, equipped with a variety of jumps and other add-ons. Along the way, try to collect bonus items to earn more reward points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Car Driving Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-car-driving-simulator-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-car-driving-simulator-3/</guid>
      <description>The hero of the game Military vehicles are sent to one of the bases of marines in Africa. There he becomes the driver of a new super-secret car. Help him complete all the tasks set by the command, destroy the maximum number of enemy troops and arrive at the end point of the route in an undamaged car. In order to pass all the stages of the War Machines game for boys, you will have to demonstrate the ability to make quick decisions and excellent reaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Derby Crash</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/derby-crash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/derby-crash/</guid>
      <description>According to the plot of the game Drive a car, you get to the test site of one of the automakers, where you will have to take part in testing a new supercar model. Try to complete all the tasks offered to you by the company&amp;rsquo;s specialists and check the characteristics of its new offspring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Cars 2 mission</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cars-2-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cars-2-mission/</guid>
      <description>McQueen was furious. He fastened two rather big cannons under the hood and a gas installation in the back. Now he shoots everyone in front of them in the trash, and on those who are dragging in the tail, he blows pink clouds. By the way, Lightning also painted himself in some strange color, which indicates a problem with his head. And he can now transform into a plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Cars 3 drift</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cars-3-drift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cars-3-drift/</guid>
      <description>Lightning McQueen is back on the race track! In this winter race, cars are moving at high speed, which naturally creates a risk of collision. Your task is to bring the car to the finish line, changing lanes in time and smoothly avoiding turns. Do not forget to collect prizes during the passage, which give extra points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Cars 8</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cars-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cars-8/</guid>
      <description>Cars 8 games are urban 3d competitions in cars with a lot of obstacles, bonuses and strong opponents. Flip the cars of your rivals, accurately enter the turns and be the first on each of the 6 tracks to get money and open the next track. In the garage there is a huge selection of cars that differ from each other in speed, handling and weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Cool Cars 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cool-cars-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cool-cars-2/</guid>
      <description>During the passage of the game Cool cars 2 you are waiting for unprecedented races in street racing. Stages open gradually. Initially, only one will be available, and even then, only at the simplest difficulty level. It consists of several races. In the first you need to compete with several opponents. On the next three you will drive alone, which will allow you to better get used to the controls and earn money for upcoming upgrades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Lego Cars 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-cars-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-cars-3/</guid>
      <description>In this race you have to drive a Lego car. In total there are 4 tracks in the game. But at the beginning, only one is available. The races are short, easy, so it will not be so difficult to defeat all rivals on them. Your task is to be the first to reach the finish line in the shortest possible time in each competition, bypassing numerous obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Service Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/public-service-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/public-service-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to pass the time near the computer together with a friend? Then, perhaps, the variant of the game For two cars will suit you. Football is to be played. Two cars, two goals and one ball. Everything is extremely simple. The screen is divided into two halves horizontally. Control is possible both from the keyboard and from joysticks, which is not often found in such entertainment. In the case of a game with a keyboard for two, the cars will be controlled by different keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Hill Driver</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-hill-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-hill-driver/</guid>
      <description>While playing with Russian cars, you become a member of the famous rally-raid passing through the tropical jungles of South America. It is here that you need to demonstrate not only your driving talent, but also the capabilities of a heavy Russian car. Try to overcome all the stages of this exciting rally race as quickly as possible and become its undisputed leader. Follow the track carefully and try to bring your car to the end point of the route in the best possible technical condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SplatPed Evo</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/splatped-evo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/splatped-evo/</guid>
      <description>Car games for boys 4 years old will make you feel like a magic artist. Here, the usual car parking in the city turns into a real show of talent. You will use the brush to paint the road to the parking lot. But remember that the path that you are preparing for the movement of the machine must be free from obstacles. Try to avoid collisions with other vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
