<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Survival on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/survival/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Survival on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/survival/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hopping Boys</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hopping-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hopping-boys/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to control an astronaut floating in zero gravity. He needs to get into the remote compartment of the starship, but the guy has not been able to cope with gravity yet. Help him go to the next level after collecting all the stars in this location. Use the mouse to control and beware of &amp;ldquo;black holes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Minecraft</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-minecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-minecraft/</guid>
      <description>During the game Survival Simulators, you will have a difficult path, the purpose of which is to help the natives save the island from wild animals and pirates. To cope with this difficult task, you will have to learn how to control the forces of nature and even time itself. If everything works out, you can become the leader of the tribe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama: Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-shooter/</guid>
      <description>The school building is under threat. Former students - losers, disliked the &amp;ldquo;alma mater&amp;rdquo; so much that they decided to destroy it to the ground. You also study at this school and do not want to give it to hooligans. That is why, taking a pistol and sitting on the roof, you shoot back from the attackers. For each kill, a monetary reward is due, which can be spent on ammunition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Survivors</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-last-survivors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-last-survivors/</guid>
      <description>Your ward is besieged by hordes of zombies. In this hell he has to hold out for seven days. Don&amp;rsquo;t let the monsters destroy the hero and turn him into the same walking dead as they are. Fight off enemies coming from all directions with the help of available firearms or machetes. The game has a shop where you can buy ammunition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World 2 Survive In Zombie World</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/world-2-survive-in-zombie-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/world-2-survive-in-zombie-world/</guid>
      <description>You may be the only survivor on Earth after the zombie apocalypse. So you have to deal with crowds of evil monsters alone. Fortunately, there is also a weapons store in the city, which will help you a lot in the fight, though not for free. Collect coins near each dead zombie and buy more powerful weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
