<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logic Balls on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/logic-balls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logic Balls on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/logic-balls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Boys &amp; Girls Bubble Pop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/boys--girls-bubble-pop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/boys--girls-bubble-pop/</guid>
      <description>Now you can have a lot of fun popping balloons! On the screen you will see a large number of balls, and some of them contain gifts. Click on groups of elements of the same color to make them burst and disappear from the screen. You need to release all the cute balloon toy gifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Shooter Gold Mining</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-shooter-gold-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-shooter-gold-mining/</guid>
      <description>Logic shooting games Balls are able to capture attention for a long time. Here you will need to control a funny monkey, which you need to help pop the balloons with the help of darts. The game consists of a large number of levels, and each of them features an original construction of balls. You need to choose the direction of the dart&amp;rsquo;s flight and the strength of the throw in order to burst as many balls as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Balls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/love-balls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/love-balls/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will find interesting puzzles with the participation of colorful balls. There are several levels, and on each of them a circle filled with balls will be displayed on the screen. There is also a pattern by which you need to reproduce the order of the balls. Rotate them until you achieve your goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack Fall 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stack-fall-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stack-fall-3d/</guid>
      <description>The puzzle game Ball Attack will introduce you to a monkey that throws darts at colorful balls. The game offers a huge number of levels, on each of which you need to destroy the specified number of balls. Please note that the number of darts is limited, so you need to shoot as accurately as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack Fire Ball</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stack-fire-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stack-fire-ball/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to build a structure of balloons, ensuring that the same balls form combinations of three or more pieces. Such combinations will immediately disappear, bringing bonus points. The game has three modes of passage: it is proposed to hold out as long as possible, play against the clock or Crazy Games a given number of points.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
