<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strategies on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/strategies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strategies on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/strategies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Overlord</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/corporate-overlord/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/corporate-overlord/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to take a break from virtual wars and destruction, having tried your hand at creation. This can be done through the building strategy game. The main task for the players in it will be to build an amusement park and make happy a certain number of visitors (at each level this number increases) for a certain period of time. For a successful game, the strategy must be correct and you will have to develop it in the shortest possible time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goldtrain FRVR</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldtrain-frvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldtrain-frvr/</guid>
      <description>Transport strategy game is an exciting train driving simulator. Become the owner of the railways and decide for yourself where the train will go. In fact, at each stage of the game you will find a certain task, having coped with it, you can go to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habbo Clicker</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/habbo-clicker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/habbo-clicker/</guid>
      <description>The new strategy game Oligarch Business gives you the opportunity to build a global oil company. Explore new deposits, negotiate with buyers and supply black gold to all countries of the world. Master new branches of production, open branches and attract customers with tempting advertising.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Army The Defenders</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-army-the-defenders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-army-the-defenders/</guid>
      <description>In order to play Prison Escape strategy games, you need to have a good reaction and the ability to quickly navigate in an unfamiliar room. Your task is to help the character leave the confined space and go free. In addition to the policemen guarding the building, there are many traps on the way to release, so try to act carefully and thoughtfully.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wars Of Worlds</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wars-of-worlds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wars-of-worlds/</guid>
      <description>Clicking on the &amp;ldquo;how to play&amp;rdquo; button is probably not worth it. Anyway, after downloading, you will be taken to a page with an English-language instruction. Better to spend some time and figure it out yourself. Games such as Strategy for the development of civilization are intuitive for every gamer. The process is quite simple in itself: guard your home and try to destroy the enemy&amp;rsquo;s. To do this, you need to build defensive fortifications and call different units.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
