<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tower Defense on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/tower-defense/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tower Defense on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/tower-defense/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Base Defense game for kids</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/base-defense-game-for-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/base-defense-game-for-kids/</guid>
      <description>In this game you need to resist the zombies that come from all sides. In the arsenal there is a pistol and cartridges for it, but if you score the required number of points, it will be possible to use a bomb against the monsters. Don&amp;rsquo;t let the dead get too close to you. Controls: mouse - shooting, R - reloading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commando Turrets game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/commando-turrets-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/commando-turrets-game/</guid>
      <description>Your squad will have to resist the pressure of an entire enemy army, consisting of infantry, aircraft and armored vehicles. Create a strong defense by placing defensive structures in the most unsafe places that will fire at the enemy. Apply all the military technologies available to you, holding back the increasing attacks of the enemy with their help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elven castle defense game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elven-castle-defense-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elven-castle-defense-game/</guid>
      <description>The kingdom of elves was attacked by unknown monsters. Your task is to help fairy tale characters defend their castle. Standing on the fortress wall, try to destroy all opponents by shooting from a bow. To do this, simply move the sight with the mouse to the desired point, and the warrior will begin to send his arrows there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fortress defense game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fortress-defense-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fortress-defense-game/</guid>
      <description>The Fortress Defense game will tell you about the bloody war of people and orcs who lived in peace for a long time. But the barbarians made an agreement with the demons and decided to destroy the inhabitants of the kingdom. You have to protect humanity from evil creatures by building defense towers and creating new, well-trained and trained warriors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Calabash Turrets</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-calabash-turrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-calabash-turrets/</guid>
      <description>Hordes of treacherous and vicious creatures have invaded the lands of the Calabash brothers. Help the heroes of the game build towers to repel enemy attacks. There are several types of buildings at your disposal. Barracks put up a barrier of warriors, frosty towers slow down the enemy, dealing damage along the way, magical barricades throw lightning at the enemy, and artillery covers several enemies at once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Castles 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-castles-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-castles-3d/</guid>
      <description>You act as the protector of the ruler and the entire castle, and this is a huge responsibility. It is necessary to competently build the defense of the fortress in order to prevent the enemy from even getting close to the walls. Build towers and fences, but don&amp;rsquo;t forget that resources are limited. If you manage to beat off the first attack, there will be additional opportunities for protection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>game elemental towers</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-elemental-towers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-elemental-towers/</guid>
      <description>The bright graphics of this game will attract the attention of everyone who likes puzzle games like &amp;ldquo;three in a row&amp;rdquo;. However, in this case, your task is not only to remove identical cells, but also to protect the tower from enemy attacks. Connect the elements of the elements vertically or horizontally, directing their blow to the enemy. Pick up coins and chests on the battlefield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game High-quality castle defense</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-high-quality-castle-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-high-quality-castle-defense/</guid>
      <description>They declared war on you, but not people, but an army of monsters. Orcs have been planning to attack your kingdom for a long time, but only now have they gathered enough forces to attack. Do whatever you can to make sure they don&amp;rsquo;t fail. Standing on one of the walls of the castle, hit the enemy with accurate bow shots. Aim aim with the mouse cursor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>game spongebob tower defense</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-spongebob-tower-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-spongebob-tower-defense/</guid>
      <description>The Krusty Krab and SpongeBob SquarePants have built a defensive tower in order to protect themselves from the attack of the treacherous Plankton&amp;rsquo;s army. You have to help the guys repel the attacks of the enemy. But first you need to correctly place the defensive guns in order to prevent the enemy from even getting close to the tower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Turrets 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-turrets-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-turrets-3d/</guid>
      <description>Horseman, warrior and sorcerer are sent to fight against the army of enemies that attacked their kingdom. In addition to the arsenal of traditional combat techniques, additional features are available to each of them. For example, if an icon with a shield falls out, the warrior becomes invulnerable, if with a horse&amp;rsquo;s head, the rider will break forward, crushing all enemies on the way. And the icon with a droplet will help the wizard cast a spell that partially restores the life of all your heroes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Tower Defense</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-tower-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-tower-defense/</guid>
      <description>It is necessary to repel the attack of the monsters that attacked your state. For defense, you can use towers that can destroy the enemy moving along the road. By upgrading your defenses, get the opportunity to effectively defend against stronger monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Defense Breakthrough game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tower-defense-breakthrough-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tower-defense-breakthrough-game/</guid>
      <description>The game is dedicated to the war with dinosaurs and time travel. You ended up on Earth during the Jurassic period and must help the scientist fix the time machine. Create impregnable defenses, extract resources and invent new ways of defense. Use the power of future technology to turn attacking dinosaurs into piles of bones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turret type game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/turret-type-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/turret-type-game/</guid>
      <description>In a game like Turrets, you need to build defensive structures along the road that can destroy monsters passing by. Under no circumstances should they enter the castle gates. Having accumulated the required number of coins, you will be able to install new weapons on combat positions and improve the ones you already have, trying to inflict the most tangible blow on the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
