<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Flying on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/flying/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Flying on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/flying/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Chopper</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-chopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-chopper/</guid>
      <description>During the game Flight Simulators on Airplanes you have to control a huge passenger liner. At the first level, you have to master landing on the runway. When approaching the airfield, reduce altitude in advance, reducing engine speed, extend flaps and landing gear. Control the flight of the aircraft with the mouse. Land smoothly and stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helicopter Parking And Racing Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/helicopter-parking-and-racing-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/helicopter-parking-and-racing-simulator/</guid>
      <description>According to the rules of the game Airplane Flying Landing and Takeoff, you have to control a rescue transport helicopter. This heavy colossus is equipped with two propellers at once and is capable of carrying up to several tons of cargo. But your task is to save the tourists who got lost in the forest. The difficulty of landing and takeoff depends on the terrain and other factors. Therefore, it is better to immediately deal with the management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plane Go</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/plane-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/plane-go/</guid>
      <description>You have to become a pilot of a small sports plane and demonstrate various tricks in the air. When performing aerobatics, the pilot experiences huge overloads. Therefore, it is very important not to lose control of the aircraft. Otherwise something bad will happen. Follow the arrows, they will indicate the route of movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sky Fighters</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sky-fighters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sky-fighters/</guid>
      <description>Feel like a real military pilot who is not afraid of dizzying flights and steep turns. Shoot at the enemies from all guns, show who is the main ace in the sky!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
