<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kids racing on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/kids-racing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kids racing on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/kids-racing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cute Cars Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-cars-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-cars-racing/</guid>
      <description>An exciting car racing game for children 3 years old invites you to take part in the delivery of goods. After the launch, you find yourself on a dairy farm, where you have to work as a driver of a cute truck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drift Cup Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/drift-cup-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/drift-cup-racing/</guid>
      <description>Once a brave dinosaur Rex decided to show everyone what he is capable of in the game Racing for kids 5 years old. This character is sure to win you over with the incredible stunts he can perform on his motorcycle. Racing for children for 5 years allows kids to learn how to use a computer keyboard and clearly demonstrate that even a clumsy dinosaur after flying in the air can just as easily land on the ground as it took off before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moto Hill Bike Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/moto-hill-bike-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/moto-hill-bike-racing/</guid>
      <description>Kids Racing for Boys is an entertaining game that will take you on challenging tracks along the coast of the ocean. It&amp;rsquo;s time for amazing adventures in your life. Under the terms of the race, you have to drive one of the many rare cars. And even if it is an old car, it does not mean at all that it cannot participate in the race. We promise you will be surprised to the core by what speed this old woman can develop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Pony My Little Race</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-pony-my-little-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-pony-my-little-race/</guid>
      <description>Funny dinosaur Gizmo decided to do a bike trial. What came out of it, the Race for Kids game will show you. It is necessary to help this cheerful character to pass a difficult track on his bike. Along the way, you need to overcome all sorts of obstacles and try to collect all the stars and various bonuses. The game is against the clock, so don&amp;rsquo;t relax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puppy Ride</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/puppy-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/puppy-ride/</guid>
      <description>This time, Homer Simpson was incredibly lucky - in the Racing game for children 6 years old, he had a unique opportunity to eat hamburgers. Our hero went to the store to buy some groceries for home, when suddenly a truck delivering food rushed in front of him. According to the plot of the game on bumps, various goodies spilled out of the body. Homer, unable to miss this opportunity, gets on his ATV and rushes after the truck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/speed-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/speed-racing/</guid>
      <description>In the exciting game Racing under 3 you will be met by the well-known Angry Birds. Here they ride on aircraft. And you, too, have to take part in this unusual competition. Control one of 3 planes and try to overtake all opponents. Along the way, you will come across coins that you need to collect in order to later purchase upgrades for your aircraft. Their purchase is available to players after each successfully completed level, so you should try not to crash out of the game and save up more money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Skater</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/street-skater/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/street-skater/</guid>
      <description>Load the gifts into the truck and drive on the slippery snowy tracks of the Racing game for kids 4 5 years old. At New Year and Christmas, everyone is looking forward to surprises and new holiday experiences. Much depends on Santa Claus. He needs to quickly deliver all the gifts for the holiday so that the celebration comes true and everyone is satisfied. Help Santa take the right number of guests to their destination in this exciting online racing game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
