<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trains on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/trains/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trains on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/trains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cargo Carrier: Low Poly</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cargo-carrier-low-poly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cargo-carrier-low-poly/</guid>
      <description>When you need not only to distract the child with a bright toy, but also to give something that will be useful for development, this game will come in handy. Small users will have to load the approaching wagons. The boxes are painted with geometric shapes. Exactly the same are on the wagons. You need to have time to arrange the goods before the train leaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Engines - thrill 3 for girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-engines---thrill-3-for-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-engines---thrill-3-for-girls/</guid>
      <description>Hold on tight - the rollercoaster ride promises to be challenging. Choose normal or extreme mode and try to complete the track without falling out of the trolley. During the passage of the way, collect money, then to purchase improvements. Use the up or down arrow keys to duck or jump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Engines - thrill 4 for girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-engines---thrill-4-for-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-engines---thrill-4-for-girls/</guid>
      <description>Amusement park racing is a great way to have fun. Today you will ride the roller coaster. On the way there will be huge obstacles and abysses. Try to overcome all the tracks both in the daytime and at night. Collect money, which can then be spent in the shop to buy upgrades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Train Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-train-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-train-simulator/</guid>
      <description>If you have always dreamed of learning how to drive a train, today you will have such an opportunity. It is necessary to transport loaded wagons on roads, which most often pass through mountainous terrain. Be careful not to roll over while moving. For any cargo delivered to the customer, you will receive a good monetary reward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
