<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Avatar on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/avatar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Avatar on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/avatar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cora game - running around the city</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cora-game---running-around-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cora-game---running-around-the-city/</guid>
      <description>One of the heroines of a series of games based on the comic book and cartoon &amp;ldquo;Avatar&amp;rdquo; - Cora, decided to take part in a death race. This is a run around the city with picking up goodies and jumping over dudes with stun guns. However, these maniacs will not always be able to jump over. Sometimes they fly on cables, which makes jumping over impossible. Collisions with them lead to loss of health and, as a result, life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Avatar Korra dark and light</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-avatar-korra-dark-and-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-avatar-korra-dark-and-light/</guid>
      <description>The meaning of the game Avatar Korra dark and light is that the character must run forward all the time and collect gold coins. On the way, he, or rather, she, has various obstacles. The simplest is wooden boxes. However, the speed of the heroine is such that she crashes to death if she even crashes into them. With the click of a mouse button, it can take off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game The Legend of Kore - Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-the-legend-of-kore---escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-the-legend-of-kore---escape/</guid>
      <description>Run, Cora, run! That might be the motto of this toy. And this is no coincidence, because all the character, the girl Kora, needs to do is run. Well, of course, you still need to collect a maximum of gold coins, as well as useful goodies that give temporary bonuses. The main and, perhaps, the only goal of the game is to run the maximum distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game The Legend of Korra Escape from the Republic</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-the-legend-of-korra-escape-from-the-republic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-the-legend-of-korra-escape-from-the-republic/</guid>
      <description>Children&amp;rsquo;s toy with characteristic graphics. But the difficulty is not very appropriate for the expected age of the gamer. Although, the little ones are different. So, the little heroine of the game runs around the city (on her own), and the user only needs to jump in time (over enemies, obstacles or for coins). Each collision takes one life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purple Jewel Dress Up Game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/purple-jewel-dress-up-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/purple-jewel-dress-up-game/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you become a specialist animator who creates images for a new film about the magical planet Pandora and its inhabitants. Think of some original characters, make them hairstyles, pick up traditional Pandora clothes and jewelry. The images created by you will be highly appreciated by specialists and film critics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
