<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>War for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/war-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in War for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/war-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dino Squad Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-squad-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-squad-adventure/</guid>
      <description>You have to fight in the form of a young warrior with the fighters of the black legion. During the passage of the level, your opponents will be both ordinary soldiers with swords and ninjas, who, in addition to swords, can use shurikens. At the end of each mission there will be a decisive encounter with the boss. Use the arrow keys to control your character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robostorm io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/robostorm-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/robostorm-io/</guid>
      <description>According to the rules of the game for two Voynushki against each other, you have to save the kingdom from the invaders. At the very beginning, you will need to choose one of four difficulty levels, create an advanced detachment of warriors and start the battle. Fight with the enemy army, destroy the enemy and earn points that can be spent on improving your army. Be careful, the number of the enemy is many times greater than the strength of your army.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Game Online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-game-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-game-online/</guid>
      <description>You control a team of fighters who fight against the enemy on a randomly generated landscape. You can play with the computer or with your friends on the same keyboard. The rules are simple. Each of the belligerents in turn strikes the opponent using the weapons it has.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanks: Sci-Fi Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-sci-fi-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-sci-fi-battle/</guid>
      <description>Fantastic game takes you to the times of the distant future. Just imagine: earthlings discover new galaxies in search of a planet suitable for life. You and your friends are lucky: you are the first to discover a pretty planet and start settling it. However, local residents are extremely hostile. Fierce battles are ahead. Watch your back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TanksIO Online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanksio-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanksio-online/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been dropped off on an island where terrorists are holding American army soldiers hostage. It is necessary to get through the dense jungle to the location of the camp and free the prisoners. Complete the mission to the end and get a reward. Just be careful, there are a lot of guards around. And you have a limited number of lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warbot io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/warbot-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/warbot-io/</guid>
      <description>You have an entire army under your command. You have to defend the honor of your country and deal with the enemy in the last, decisive battle. It is she who will put an end to hostilities and resolve the long-standing conflict. Control your soldiers with the arrow keys, strengthen your defenses and constantly collect ammo and first aid kits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
