<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Attention and memory on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/attention-and-memory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Attention and memory on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/attention-and-memory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Motorbikes Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cartoon-motorbikes-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cartoon-motorbikes-memory/</guid>
      <description>Tighten your memory in order to successfully play this game. Several cards will appear on the screen, which will turn over to the side with images for a couple of seconds. You need to remember where the picture of the bomb is. Next, open all those cards where there is no bomb to complete the level. If you run into an explosive object, you lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find In Mind</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/find-in-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/find-in-mind/</guid>
      <description>The memory game will definitely appeal to fans of the Winx sorceresses. Three rows of closed cards will be displayed on the screen. You need to turn them over and look for the same images of fairies. Pairs of pictures disappear, bringing bonus points. The task is to get rid of absolutely all the cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cream Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-cream-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-cream-memory/</guid>
      <description>The attention and memory game offers to cook a variety of hamburgers. Fast food samples are displayed at the top of the screen, and you need to reproduce them using the right ingredients. Reward points are awarded for each correctly created hamburger. Don&amp;rsquo;t delay, otherwise there will be too many orders, and you will lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Education For Kids</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/math-education-for-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/math-education-for-kids/</guid>
      <description>The mindfulness game is dedicated to the adventures of Santa Claus. Your task is to help the New Year&amp;rsquo;s wizard deliver all the presents. Navigate through the labyrinth, collecting boxes of presents, then to get to the exit. You need to find absolutely all the gifts, otherwise you will not be able to get out of the trap!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offroad Trucks Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/offroad-trucks-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/offroad-trucks-memory/</guid>
      <description>This wonderful game is dedicated to the cartoon &amp;ldquo;Cars&amp;rdquo;. In it you can perfectly train your memory. Several rows of cards are displayed on the screen, and you need to turn them over to find the same pictures of cars. The goal of the game is to find all pairs of cartoon characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Word Search</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/word-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/word-search/</guid>
      <description>Play an exciting game with ponies and train your memory. On the screen you will see four pictures of cute little horses. Your task is to memorize the order in which the pictures are highlighted and reproduce it by clicking on the right ponies. If you click in the wrong place, you lose.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
