<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>drawing on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/drawing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in drawing on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/drawing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Draw Here</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/draw-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/draw-here/</guid>
      <description>Fans of logic puzzles will definitely like this wonderful game, which consists of a huge number of levels. At each stage, you have one goal in front of you: you need to throw the ball to the specified place. To do this, draw suitable shapes in the right places, which will help you cope with the task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garfield Connect The Dots</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/garfield-connect-the-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/garfield-connect-the-dots/</guid>
      <description>In this simple but addictive game, you are challenged to connect the numbered dots as quickly as possible. There are a large number of levels, which gradually become more difficult. Just move the cursor over the points, focusing on the numbers: they must be connected exclusively in ascending order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-coloring/</guid>
      <description>A wonderful character of this game will go on a journey through the world drawn on paper. He wants to get to the house where his family lives. Try to protect him during the journey from the nightmarish monsters that roam the forests of the painted world, using the mouse cursor in the form of a marker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kylie Jenner Halloween Face Art</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kylie-jenner-halloween-face-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kylie-jenner-halloween-face-art/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will open the original graphics editor, in which you can create a variety of images. There are several &amp;ldquo;pencil&amp;rdquo; shapes here, some of which allow you to draw animated lines. Choose the right shape, as well as the color you like, by combining different options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vannelope Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/vannelope-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/vannelope-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Drawing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xmas Draw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/xmas-draw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/xmas-draw/</guid>
      <description>In this game you are invited to help Santa Claus sort out the gifts for the children. More precisely, they need to be collected. To do this, draw a line along which Santa can drive his sleigh. The road must reach the place marked with the finish flag. If it fails, you can try again and draw another version of the path.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
