<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pizzeria on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/pizzeria/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pizzeria on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/pizzeria/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Pizzeria</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-pizzeria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-pizzeria/</guid>
      <description>This small pizzeria is the most popular place among urban youth. Every day, dozens of students and students come here to enjoy pizza prepared according to the best Italian recipes. Together with Chef Horatio, you need to feed all the young people, fulfilling the orders on time, which will be displayed in a cloud above the head of each client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Pizza Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/homemade-pizza-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/homemade-pizza-cooking/</guid>
      <description>Almost everyone loves pizza. And now you have to cook a variety of pizzas using a variety of ingredients. It is necessary to rely on the order forms, adding to the dough all the components that are indicated there. Try not to make mistakes, because after a few mistakes the game will end. With each level, the tasks will become more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Bar</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-bar/</guid>
      <description>Freddy&amp;rsquo;s Pizzeria game invites you to help the chef feed his many customers with delicious pizza. After receiving an order from a client, look in the recipe book how this dish is prepared. Use all the ingredients and sauces exactly according to the recipe, put them on the base and send the pizza to the microwave. But be careful and try not to confuse the components. After the pizza is ready, pack it in a box and give it to the customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Cafe</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-cafe/</guid>
      <description>Today you will have to work in the hottest spot in the city - a popular pizzeria. A lot of people dream of enjoying delicious local pizza. And behind the counter today you work alone. Carefully monitor what order the buyer makes, quickly prepare pizza, pack it and give it to the client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to make pizza according to your own recipe? Then get down to business. First, arrange your workplace: choose the color of the tablecloth and plate. Then we proceed to the most interesting - the filling. It can be meat or sweet pizza. When everything is ready, decorate the dish with the additional ingredients located on the right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Mania</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-mania/</guid>
      <description>Papas Pizzeria is a great simulation game that will teach you how to cook delicious pizza. There are many recipes for preparing this dish, all of which have been changed more than once and supplemented with new ingredients, but the base has always remained the same - dough, ketchup and grated cheese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Ninja</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-ninja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-ninja/</guid>
      <description>During the game Dad&amp;rsquo;s Pizza Restaurant you have to visit a small establishment where they cook an amazing Italian dish. That is why there is simply no end to customers here. You can even try making pizza yourself. On the right is a sample. Try to repeat it exactly using the dough and products on the left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Realife Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-realife-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pizza-realife-cooking/</guid>
      <description>You have to help the chef by preparing super delicious pizza and delighting customers. You need to act quickly before the buyer&amp;rsquo;s patience runs out and he leaves without lunch. At your disposal there is a detailed book of recipes and a complete set of necessary products and spices. If anything from the list runs out, you can immediately order and buy it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
