<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>parkour on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/parkour/</link>
    <description>Recent content in parkour on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/parkour/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Assault Course 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/assault-course-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/assault-course-2/</guid>
      <description>Fans of the sports and adventure genre will surely love this 3d parkour game. Firstly, the quality of the drawing will please. Secondly, the ability to control a realistically drawn third-person character and overcome obstacles that, thanks to 3d graphics, look like real ones. Management is quite simple. Many tricks, such as a somersault softening the fall, are performed by the character himself. The task of the gamer is to move at maximum speed along the distance (time is limited) and collect the signs necessary to complete the level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Free Run 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-free-run-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-free-run-2/</guid>
      <description>This is a wonderful third-person parkour toy. This means that you will see your character from the back. Management is simple, you will not have to get used to it. The goal of the game is to collect the required number of dragon signs in each level and get to the portal. It is also worth collecting other items - they are useful. For example, they can add time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama: 25 Level Parkour</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-25-level-parkour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-25-level-parkour/</guid>
      <description>Minecraft has nothing to do with the process of playing 3D parkour. First-person view. At the very beginning, the user can choose the option of passing (you need to run under the appropriate inscription). In total, three options are available: running through the maze, running through the beautiful wild landscape and parkour through the stone columns. In any case, the goal is the same: to get to the transition to the next stage faster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vex 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/vex-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/vex-3/</guid>
      <description>A toy about a little man, whose face no one will ever see, because he does not exist at all, and the little man himself looks like someone&amp;rsquo;s shadow. However, he wants to run forward with the standard controls and overcome obstacles with parkour moves. You simply have to help him with this. By the way, if you wish, you can design levels yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
