<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dentist on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/dentist/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dentist on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/dentist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Become A Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/become-a-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/become-a-dentist/</guid>
      <description>The little prince is a real child, both physiologically and in terms of the degree of development of thinking. It is not surprising that he stubbornly did not brush his teeth and did not follow his oral cavity at all. Now he will endure hardships and deprivation of treatment. And you will heal him. To do this, the game has everything you need: drills, tongs, spacers and other tools. Try to figure out exactly how to use each of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draculaura Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/draculaura-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/draculaura-dentist/</guid>
      <description>Who wants to mess with a monster girl? By the way, apparently, this is a vampire. But how can you refuse the baby when her angry mother looms behind her. Your task is to make sure that the baby does not cry, otherwise the game will end, and you will turn into a vampire. Therefore, think and act quickly. You have a large set of tools. Just don&amp;rsquo;t use silver!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-dentist/</guid>
      <description>A hard life befell Cinderella. Either the stepmother got it, then I had to fight for the love of the prince. And now the teeth are flying. And, judging by the picture, the fairy princess not only does not observe hygiene, but also smokes. However, the prince will pay you well if you fix his wife&amp;rsquo;s mouth. Use the suggested tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princy Throat Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princy-throat-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princy-throat-doctor/</guid>
      <description>The game Dentist will show you that the work of a dentist is not only about rowing money with a shovel. You have to work in almost extreme conditions, and even with jewelry accuracy. Each mistake can become irreparable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
