<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Penguin Games on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/penguin-games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Penguin Games on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/penguin-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eg Penguin Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-penguin-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-penguin-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Mad penguins attack your ward. It is necessary to repel all their attacks and protect your home. With each level of enemies, he has more and more and they are much stronger. It&amp;rsquo;s good that you have the opportunity after each round to buy new types of weapons and bombs to deal with impudent ones. Use the mouse to control the aim. Shot - left button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eg Penguin Puzzles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-penguin-puzzles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-penguin-puzzles/</guid>
      <description>The penguin has to get to the opposite bank of the river on a surfboard. The whole path is divided into small sections, on each of which you need to collect more fruits, because it is for them that points are awarded. They can be spent in a special shop to purchase upgrades and bonuses. To make the penguin jump, click on the left mouse button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penguin Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/penguin-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/penguin-adventure/</guid>
      <description>The Flying Penguin game invites you to be smart, using the help of your feathered brothers. The task is to lift the penguin into the air. At the first level, this is easy to do - you just need to click on the bird and it will fly. But further her flight will be hindered by obstacles in the form of wooden bars and sharp needles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penguin Fish Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/penguin-fish-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/penguin-fish-run/</guid>
      <description>The penguins lived peacefully at their South Pole and enjoyed every day. But the unexpected happened: they were attacked by polar bears. Two brave penguin friends came to the defense of the whole flock. Help them defeat enemies and reclaim their native lands. Use the A and D keys to control. W button - jump. Button S - pick up props.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penguins Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/penguins-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/penguins-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>The game Penguins will tell you about birds that cannot fly, but feel like fish underwater. This innate ability helps penguins get their own food. After all, they feed mainly on small fish. Our penguin game has one interesting feature. This is an inversion. To turn left, you must press the right arrow key, and vice versa. Acting in this way, you have to help the little penguin catch as many fish as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
