<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Similar to GTA on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/similar-to-gta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Similar to GTA on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/similar-to-gta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adventure City</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/adventure-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/adventure-city/</guid>
      <description>Looking for games similar to GTA 5 but more accessible? You already found it, run it. At the very beginning, you can choose which mode to play in: a single mission or a career path. Career, in any way, is more interesting. So, your character starts his journey first as a pedestrian, but there is a bicycle next to him. You need to get to a certain point on the map (it is indicated in green).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agent Smith</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/agent-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/agent-smith/</guid>
      <description>A game based on the most popular action movie of all time, in which almost all the stars of the genre starred. You will control these characters, completing mission after mission. The first stage is training, you will have time to get used to the process. But first, it is recommended to familiarize yourself with the control buttons and some other moments of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cars Thief</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cars-thief/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cars-thief/</guid>
      <description>So, it&amp;rsquo;s time to see which car thief you are. Your task is not just to steal a car in the parking lot, but to drive it to a certain place. Yes, and with minimal damage. It&amp;rsquo;s simple: you get into the indicated car and drive to the green dot. At the first level, this is easy. But the farther, the more obstacles on the way, and the time for the mission is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cars Thief 2 Tank Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cars-thief-2-tank-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cars-thief-2-tank-edition/</guid>
      <description>The plot of this detective game is revealed in the introductory video. After it, you realize that your character is a policeman. He has a gun and a car that even has flashing lights. You have to drive around the city and kill bandits to complete the mission (see intro video). Bandits are destroyed only with a pistol. You can&amp;rsquo;t push them with a car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime City 3D 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crime-city-3d-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crime-city-3d-2/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will be in the shoes of either a cop or a gangster. In any case, with a gun drawn, you will find yourself in the middle of a busy city square. Various people are scurrying around, and you must determine by the inscriptions above them who needs to be filled up. If you kill too many innocents, you will have to start the game again. The point is to score the maximum number of points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gangsta Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gangsta-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gangsta-wars/</guid>
      <description>In this game, gangsters drive around in vintage cars, and money is lying right on the sidewalk. And you start with the fact that you need to park the car in the specified place. If you do not invest in the standard, you will return to the beginning of the level. After parking, a bank robbery will follow, and then you will need to get out of the cops. Try to collect more money along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gangster Man 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gangster-man-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gangster-man-3d/</guid>
      <description>A very simple game. All that is required of you is to shoot non-stop and collect prizes. Your character is running. You can only speed it up or slow it down. If you grab a grenade, then all the enemies on the screen will explode. Collision with them leads to loss of life. You need to get as far as possible before all lives are lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Gang Crime Island</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/grand-gang-crime-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/grand-gang-crime-island/</guid>
      <description>Do you like to play cool pepper who lives by his own laws and rules? Then you must like games like GTA 4. From the very beginning, only one mode is available. The second one will open after a successful career as a criminal. After launch, a rather lengthy introductory video follows with a lot of dialogue. Then you have to steal a car (you will be shown which one) and proceed to the tasks of criminal bosses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Shift Auto</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/grand-shift-auto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/grand-shift-auto/</guid>
      <description>Taxi is often associated with crime: sometimes taxi drivers are attacked, then taxi drivers carry criminals, drugs and all that. But in this case, you do not have to plunge into all this dirt. Your whole crime is that you are a taxi driver without a license. You drive, pick up passengers and deliver them where they need to be. But be prepared for the fact that the cops will sit on the tail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miami Crime Simulator 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/miami-crime-simulator-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/miami-crime-simulator-3d/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to participate in real nigerian showdowns? This game is for you! Two clans clashed in the streets for the right to sell dope. Kill the required number of enemies on each level - and you will be happy! For Mochilov, you have several different barrels at your disposal, among which there is even a machine gun and a sniper rifle. First-aid kits and cartridges are selected by shots at them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Park The Taxi</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/park-the-taxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/park-the-taxi/</guid>
      <description>During the GTA Taxi game, you will have to drive around one of the largest cities in the world. You need to pick up passengers and take them to the specified destinations. The amount of money you earn depends on the time of the trip. The faster you deliver customers, the more tips you get. For more convenient orientation in the city, you need to follow the red arrow. During trips, fuel may run out, which will be notified by a special sensor, or the car may break down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Grand Auto Town</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/project-grand-auto-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/project-grand-auto-town/</guid>
      <description>In this game, everything that can be in a good action movie awaits you: fights, chases, gang wars and much more. For starters, it&amp;rsquo;s worth taking a little time to learn the interface and controls. Then follow the arrows and hints if you can&amp;rsquo;t read all the dialogues in English. To find useful bonuses, you should look into all the nooks and crannies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Sniper Tap To Kill</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-sniper-tap-to-kill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-sniper-tap-to-kill/</guid>
      <description>A new game about black and white men. First surprise: if you get hurt, try to approach the nurse (at the beginning of the game she is lying on the bed in a red dress). Or just come along - you&amp;rsquo;ll like it. When you need to shoot - press the spacebar to switch to combat mode and back. Also, with a gun, it is much more productive to talk to the characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Car Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/traffic-car-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/traffic-car-racing/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will again confront the terrorists. This time they need to be chased by car and neutralized before they throw off and detonate a bomb in the middle of the city. You need to go, guided by the arrow, however, it is not so easy. Your car has very poor handling and constant drifts do not allow normal acceleration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombies At The Beach</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombies-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombies-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to chase the policemen. You drive a cute Cadillac that can not only go fast, but also jump, do somersaults, and shoot rockets (although they still need to be picked up). From collisions, the car gradually breaks down, so you may not reach the finish line. Collect bonuses along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
