<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>injections on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/injections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in injections on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/injections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Amandas Hospital Recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/amandas-hospital-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/amandas-hospital-recovery/</guid>
      <description>During the game Injections for Girls, you will have to try on the role of a children&amp;rsquo;s doctor. Little patients will constantly look into your office. The task is to quickly diagnose them and carry out the necessary treatment procedures. The game consists of several levels and is constantly becoming more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moody Ally Flu Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/moody-ally-flu-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/moody-ally-flu-doctor/</guid>
      <description>During the game Injections in the ass, you will work in a children&amp;rsquo;s hospital. Little patients are constantly arriving here, and your task is to take care of them. Pay close attention to what the children want and satisfy their desires. Babies need to be fed, washed, played with and, of course, treated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vanellope Injured</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/vanellope-injured/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/vanellope-injured/</guid>
      <description>The game Give Injections to Kids invites you to learn how to make therapeutic injections in different parts of the body. You need to arm yourself with a syringe and get into the marked place on the arm, pope or leg of the patient. Try not to miss, otherwise you might lose. The game consists of several levels, and at each subsequent one it becomes more and more difficult to make an injection.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
