<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lego on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/lego/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lego on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/lego/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Candy Blast Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-blast-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-blast-match-3/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game you have to build houses for cute animals. In order to get the desired object, you need to make combinations of three or more identical elements on a special playing field. Swap adjacent parts to get the coveted combinations. Disappearing, they will give you one part of the house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Land</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-land/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that all children love sweets. You are also invited to work in a pastry shop, which offers a wide range of desserts. Try to fulfill all the orders of all the little visitors, selling them the desired treats. The game consists of several levels, and on each of them you need to earn a certain amount of money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert Storm game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/desert-storm-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/desert-storm-game/</guid>
      <description>For people who are at least slightly aware of the main military events of the twentieth century, the name of the game evokes associations with the war in Iraq. However, the game is not about that at all. Instead of fighting, gamers are invited to take part in the race on special motorcycles with inertial engines. Along the way, you need to collect bonuses and shoot down various targets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Constructor for girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-constructor-for-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-constructor-for-girls/</guid>
      <description>During the game Constructor for Girls you find yourself in the world of Lego, where you will have to solve various tasks, controlling one of the inhabitants of a fantastic city. Use the arrow keys to move. Overcome obstacles, destroy enemies and develop your character. Do not neglect the help of friends in especially difficult situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Extreme Lego Racing 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-extreme-lego-racing-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-extreme-lego-racing-2/</guid>
      <description>The leadership of the World Motocross Championship decided to hold one of its stages in Lego City. Many famous motorcycle racers were invited to the grand opening, including you. Demonstrate your talents as a motorcycle racer and try to perform as many tricks as possible that will amaze all the spectators of the holiday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Lego battle with the police</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-battle-with-the-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-battle-with-the-police/</guid>
      <description>This time you will control a criminal whose car is being chased by a police patrol. To break away from the persecution and get out to freedom, you will need to destroy the jeep of law enforcement officers. Use various aids to protect your car. It can be small bombs, shields, turbo boost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game lego captain america guard justice 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-captain-america-guard-justice-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-captain-america-guard-justice-2/</guid>
      <description>The famous Captain America goes in search of the villain whose army attacked New York and asks you to join him in this dangerous expedition. Help the legendary hero avoid all the obstacles on the way and destroy the invaders waiting at every turn. Know that you will have a tough fight with Loki, the god of Aasgard, who brought the invaders to earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Lego Coast Guard 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-coast-guard-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-coast-guard-2/</guid>
      <description>An unexpected storm has caused disaster in Lego City&amp;rsquo;s harbor. Help the Coast Guard to rescue all the victims. Go to the open sea together with the rescue team aboard the ship. Guide the rescue scooter to people in need of help. Try to save all the drowning people and make sure that the rescuer does not get into the teeth of hungry sharks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Lego Duplo Indiana Jones</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-duplo-indiana-jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-duplo-indiana-jones/</guid>
      <description>Help Indiana Jones cope with the danger that threatens him and escape from a huge rolling stone. You need to carefully monitor what is happening on the screen and click on the red objects in time so that Indiana can perform the necessary actions. Also, do not forget to collect coins and other valuable items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Lego grand prize 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-grand-prize-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-grand-prize-2/</guid>
      <description>Lightning McQueen and his buddies invite you to take part in competitions that will take place on the steepest tracks on the planet. Choose one of the main characters of the animated series and together with him try to win all the races of the exciting championship. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect bonus Lego bricks and use them to improve your friend&amp;rsquo;s stats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game lego ninja turtles 5</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-ninja-turtles-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-ninja-turtles-5/</guid>
      <description>While playing Lego Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 5, you meet brave mutant teenagers who protect the Earth from alien attacks. The main enemy of the four Lego heroes - Shredder, decided to create a huge underground base in the very center of the metropolis, and you have to help young ninjas destroy the plans of the insidious invader. Destroy as many criminals from the Nogi clan who have joined the alien invaders as possible and stop the construction process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Lego racing through the forest 3d</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-racing-through-the-forest-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-racing-through-the-forest-3d/</guid>
      <description>Lego City Hall decided to hold a competition and identify the best driver among emergency workers. Choose a car from one of the city&amp;rsquo;s services and show off your driving skills. Your victory in all the races of the championship will allow you to get the crown of the best driver of the city from Lego blocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Lego Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Collect and Conquer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-collect-and-conquer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-lego-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-collect-and-conquer/</guid>
      <description>In this game, the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles will have to sneak into a secret laboratory and collect ampoules with a dangerous chemical there. Help them complete this task. To move to a new level, you need to kill a certain number of robots. Look for the watch - this will extend the time you are in the game. And to become invulnerable, pick up pizza slices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Star Wars space agent</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-star-wars-space-agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-star-wars-space-agent/</guid>
      <description>The empire built a huge warship. Your task is to get there and save your failed agents. Make your way into the very bowels of the secret base and let all the villains regret that they got in your way. But remember, you have to run through endless corridors, climb walls, jump on numerous platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero Robot Factory game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hero-robot-factory-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hero-robot-factory-game/</guid>
      <description>The game is divided into several stages. The death of the hero on any of them leads to the fact that you have to start the process from the very beginning. At the first level, you will have a brief training in control, and then the character (this is a combat robot) will need to collect parts from his additional weapon. The second stage will have to be devoted to the battle with other robots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Avengers 2 game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-avengers-2-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-avengers-2-game/</guid>
      <description>While playing Lego Avengers 2, Tony Parker invites you to his secret lab where a famous engineer is designing new suits for Iron Man. Help a specialist flight test fresh prototypes. In each of them, you need to fly as far as possible, hitting educational targets with the help of a Lego laser and missiles. Do not forget that, despite the fact that the flight is a test, you will be fired upon with real weapons, testing the capabilities of one of the Avengers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Avengers game for two</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-avengers-game-for-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-avengers-game-for-two/</guid>
      <description>According to the plot of the Lego Avengers game for two, the greatest criminals have teamed up in order to capture an energy source developed by a famous inventor. A team of superheroes is sent to protect the scientific laboratory. Choose from them three characters and go to battle. Invite your best friend and you will be able to fight back against the insidious villains together, taking it in turns to control the brave Avengers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego barbershop game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-barbershop-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-barbershop-game/</guid>
      <description>Head to the salon equipped with the latest technology and start your career as a hairdresser. Your task is to delight clients with new hairstyles. The girls will tell you exactly what they want, and you just have to perform the appropriate actions based on the tooltips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego beauty salon game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-beauty-salon-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-beauty-salon-game/</guid>
      <description>The game offers gamers to take care of cute pets. Girls will bring their pets to you, and you will need to carry out the necessary care procedures for them. Take care of the hygiene and appearance of each animal, and when it becomes really attractive, feed it. For a meal, you need to choose the right food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego car game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-car-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-car-game/</guid>
      <description>While playing Lego cars you have to take part in a racing competition. Your task is simple: you need to drive as far as possible, moving along winding tracks in the company of other riders. Their Lego cars can interfere with yours, so try to find the best path for yourself without bumping into obstacles, because they slow down the car a lot. Before you start playing, you need to choose the car you like the most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Cars game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-cars-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-cars-game/</guid>
      <description>According to the plot of the Lego Cars game, you will, along with the heroes of the cartoon of the same name, take part in an exciting racing competition. Right at the start, you meet Lightning McQueen - the best racer in the world of Cars, it is with him that you have to fight for the crown of the tournament winner. Lego championship races are held all over the world, and you will have to make every effort to achieve victory in each of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego city game for girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-city-game-for-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-city-game-for-girls/</guid>
      <description>After launching Lego City for Girls, you will enter a special salon designed to take care of cute pets. You will be brought various pets that need to undergo scheduled procedures. To begin with, you should bathe the animal, comb it, and take care of the hygiene of teeth and claws. And after the care process is completed, you need to remember to feed the baby. To do this, a lot of different foods are presented on the screen, but you need to choose exactly what your pet loves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego city police game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-city-police-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-city-police-game/</guid>
      <description>Pay attention to the plot of the game Lego city police. In it, you can check how various services of the city work in emergency situations. For example, a convict escaped from prison - he must be caught, and the police take over the case. There is a fire, who can help? Certainly courageous firefighters. If a tire is punctured on the road or a car breaks down, a tow truck rushes to the rescue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego City Turtle game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-city-turtle-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-city-turtle-game/</guid>
      <description>The insidious Shredder and his minions from the Foot clan attacked the building under which the house of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles was located. Help the brave reptiles destroy the maximum number of enemies in a limited time. Carefully monitor the situation on the battlefield, try to meet Shredder himself on the battlefield and defeat him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Friends Heartlake Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-friends-heartlake-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-friends-heartlake-rush/</guid>
      <description>While playing Lego Friends Adventure you have to help cute girls to have a chic pool party. To do this, at your disposal is a huge number of different buildings. Choose any of them, and then install on one of the available places. You can change the color of the parts as you wish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego fun racing game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-fun-racing-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-fun-racing-game/</guid>
      <description>And again we will play with inertial cars. This time you will not have to overtake anyone, but it will be possible to show the skill of avoiding obstacles. Collect parts along the way - extra points are awarded for them. The number of starts in one run is limited, so handlebars are careful to stop less. New tracks open gradually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego game beautiful motors 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-game-beautiful-motors-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-game-beautiful-motors-2/</guid>
      <description>In Lego City, one of the stages of the World Motocross Championship is organized, in which you also take part. Show all your talents and win in each of the races of the tournament. Do not forget to please the audience with dangerous and spectacular stunts on the track. Your performance will not leave indifferent any person present on the track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego game for kids</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-game-for-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-game-for-kids/</guid>
      <description>While playing Lego for kids, you will be asked to take care of the pets. Pet owners will bring their pets to your hotel, and not only banal cats or dogs. This time you will be able to tinker with a bunny, a deer and many other animals. Children&amp;rsquo;s game consists of several stages, or rather, of five. To begin with, you will need to wash your pet, then take him to a haircut and brush his teeth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego game real cars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-game-real-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-game-real-cars/</guid>
      <description>Take control of a small clockwork car and take part in the races. Pull the car back with the mouse, and then release it to give it acceleration and get to the finish line as quickly as possible. Collect gears along the way - they will be useful when upgrading the car. Win races to unlock even more challenging races.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego heroic game - valley of the dead</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-heroic-game---valley-of-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-heroic-game---valley-of-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to destroy the dead, who are trying to take over the territory of the city and enslave all its inhabitants. At the very beginning of the battle, you have only one shooter. Aim with your mouse and destroy the monsters. After the first victory, you will be able to replenish the ranks of your warriors, as well as choose the right weapon for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Indiana Jones game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-indiana-jones-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-indiana-jones-game/</guid>
      <description>The protagonist of the game Lego Indiana Jones goes in search of rare artifacts and invites you to join him. In one of the ancient manuscripts, the famous archaeologist and adventurer discovered a map that indicates the places where parts of a mysterious object are hidden. Passing missions will require you to have a good reaction and attentiveness. Lego adventures capture from the first seconds and do not let you leave the monitor until Indiana Jones is able to collect all the parts of the artifact and restore the ancient relic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego iron man game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-iron-man-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-iron-man-game/</guid>
      <description>Renowned scientist and inventor Tony Stark has developed several new Iron Man suits and invites you to test them. While Tonny is testing the systems in his lab, you must operate the suit in real-life conditions. On the track you will find many challenges that you will have to overcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Marvel Hero Factory game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-marvel-hero-factory-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-marvel-hero-factory-game/</guid>
      <description>Lego Heroes are sent to fight terrible alien monsters. The aliens tried to capture one of the cities of the home planet of Lego heroes, and now you have to help the brave defenders repel the attack. Control your character&amp;rsquo;s movements, destroy enemies and collect parts that will allow your hero to transform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego McQueen game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-mcqueen-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-mcqueen-game/</guid>
      <description>The process of playing Lego Makvin echoes the plot of the famous cartoon &amp;ldquo;Cars&amp;rdquo;. In it you will not only take part in the race, but also win. At the beginning of the game, you can only control Lightning McQueen, but other cars from the cartoon will gradually open. You can choose any of the unlocked cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego police assistants game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-police-assistants-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-police-assistants-game/</guid>
      <description>Feel like a popular superhero - Batman, who will have to race through the night alleys of the city with many obstacles. At the top of the playing field there is an indicator showing the cars of criminals that need to be neutralized. To do this, your Batmobile has a missile system installed. The shot is made by pressing the spacebar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego space game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-space-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-space-game/</guid>
      <description>After launching the Lego space game, you will find yourself in the world of Star Wars. Next, you need to decide which side attracts you more: dark or light. After the choice is made, indicate the location where you want to play and start your adventure in space. At each level, a separate task awaits you, and you need to complete it to complete the mission. Lego astronauts of the enemy army will attack you, so you need to act quickly and without too much fuss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Spiderman 3 game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-spiderman-3-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-spiderman-3-game/</guid>
      <description>While playing Lego Spider-Man 3 you have to join the famous hero in his fight against criminals. Go with Spiderman to patrol the streets of the city. Use the PC keyboard to control the movements of the main character and help to overcome the obstacles that are often encountered on his way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego star wars rebels game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-star-wars-rebels-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-star-wars-rebels-game/</guid>
      <description>Set six years before the Battle of Yavin, Lego Star Wars Rebels focuses on the actions of a small group of heroes who helped spark a liberation rebellion. Before you is an excellent turn-based strategy, where the Lego rebels are fighting to save the inhabitants of Lothal in order to give the universe new hope. Empire&amp;rsquo;s assault troops are very strong and you will have to use special tactics. Help the main characters Ezra and Kanan develop a strategic plan to strike back at the enemy troops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego superhero racing game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-superhero-racing-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-superhero-racing-game/</guid>
      <description>On a giant arena in the presence of a huge number of spectators, races to the bottom are held, the participants of which are the characters of comics dedicated to Batman. Choose one of the characters in the game and go to the track. Try to avoid collisions with opponents and try to destroy them with the help of devices that will meet on the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego Superheroes game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-superheroes-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-superheroes-game/</guid>
      <description>While playing Lego superheroes Peter Quill and his team of Guardians of the Galaxy go in search of a sphere that can destroy entire planets. Peter invites you to join his friends in this dangerous adventure. Choose one of the Marvel heroes and go to the labyrinths of the dungeons of the abandoned planet Mogar. The passage of this exciting toy from Lego will require you to have a good reaction and attentiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego turtle game for girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-turtle-game-for-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lego-turtle-game-for-girls/</guid>
      <description>Help the ninja turtle defeat the evil that has gripped the city. The streets and sewer passages are filled with enemies, and you need to navigate through the given locations and destroy the enemies. Try not to fall under their blows, otherwise you can lose all game lives and fly out of the game. You need to become a real hero!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racing game for real heroes</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/racing-game-for-real-heroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/racing-game-for-real-heroes/</guid>
      <description>In this game, interesting and exciting races on inertial cars await you. First, you accelerate it, and then you begin to deftly maneuver, avoiding collisions with barriers that greatly reduce speed. But you can dial it again if you run into the green arrows. Collect coins along the way and, of course, do not let yourself be overtaken by other participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superhero Confrontation game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-confrontation-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-confrontation-game/</guid>
      <description>Superheroes, like ordinary people, have quarrels and showdowns. In one of them you have to participate, almost personally. You will need to complete training before starting. It&amp;rsquo;s worth it, because the control keys are not quite familiar. During the fight, you can change characters (there are several of them in the team). Everyone has some special hit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
