<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cooking on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/cooking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cooking on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/cooking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Boys Cooking Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/boys-cooking-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/boys-cooking-challenge/</guid>
      <description>During the Cooking for Boys game, you will cook vegetable lasagna under the guidance of an experienced chef. Not every hostess can cope with such a difficult task. Therefore, the game will show all the stages of preparing a delicious dish, after which you can easily repeat the whole process in your own kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elsa Ice Cream Rolls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-ice-cream-rolls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-ice-cream-rolls/</guid>
      <description>This game will give you the opportunity to experiment in making a refreshing dessert. Follow the tips of an experienced chef and use the mouse to mix the ingredients. When the ice cream is ready, do not forget to add chocolate, vanilla or nuts, pour it with cream, syrup or jam. Serve on the table in the form of balls on a beautiful plate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Homemade Sugar Cookies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/how-to-make-homemade-sugar-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/how-to-make-homemade-sugar-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Macaroons are small, multi-colored, round cakes with a creamy filling, decorated with confetti, poppy seeds, powders and powders. Today with the help of this game you will learn how to cook this confectionery masterpiece. Beat the whites with powdered sugar, mix with almond flour, add dye, place circles on a baking sheet and into the oven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vincy Cooking Rainbow Birthday Cake</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/vincy-cooking-rainbow-birthday-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/vincy-cooking-rainbow-birthday-cake/</guid>
      <description>You need to bake a wedding cake. To do this, you need to purchase products in the store. When everything is in stock, you can begin the cooking process itself. Start with the dough, from which you can then bake two or three cakes. Then they need to be smeared with cream and connected. Next, decorate the cake with lots of fruit and figurines of the bride and groom.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
