<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simulators on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/simulators/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Simulators on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/simulators/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3d Airplane Race Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/3d-airplane-race-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/3d-airplane-race-simulator/</guid>
      <description>During this wonderful game you have to control a combat aircraft. High hopes are pinned on his pilot, it&amp;rsquo;s time to justify them. Enemy planes will appear in front of you, and the task is to destroy them by releasing powerful projectiles. The game includes many exciting missions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airport Manager Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/airport-manager-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/airport-manager-simulator/</guid>
      <description>The game Airport Simulator 2014 invites you to adjust the movement of aircraft. Aircraft will constantly appear on the screen, and you just have to land them correctly on the marked places. In no case do not let the planes collide, otherwise the game will immediately end with your loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boat Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/boat-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/boat-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Ship Simulator game invites you to take part in sea battles. Control the ship by firing cannons at your opponents. The moves are made alternately, first you launch the projectile, then your opponent. Choose the direction and strength of the shot in order to make the most effective attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bus Parking Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bus-parking-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bus-parking-simulator/</guid>
      <description>minibus gazelle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exotic Girl Washing Clothes</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/exotic-girl-washing-clothes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/exotic-girl-washing-clothes/</guid>
      <description>The Girl Simulator game invites you to turn into a beautician and help a cute heroine. She has some skin problems that need to be addressed urgently. For this, you have several useful means at your disposal. Apply them according to the tips and restore beauty to the skin of the heroine of the game. And then do your makeup and choose an outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feed The Frog</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/feed-the-frog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/feed-the-frog/</guid>
      <description>frog simulator</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Flight Sim</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/free-flight-sim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/free-flight-sim/</guid>
      <description>Launching the Flight Simulator game will turn you into a real pilot. The task is to control a military aircraft. Move it in the air, trying not to fall, otherwise the aircraft will crash and you will not be able to continue the game. Enemy planes will appear next to your car very soon, it is their destruction that will become the main goal. Shoot at your opponents in such a way as to blow up the equipment as quickly as possible and come to victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Anna Kiss</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/frozen-anna-kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/frozen-anna-kiss/</guid>
      <description>The Kissing Simulator game will take you to a park where people have a great time relaxing. There you will meet a guy and a girl in love who really want to be closer to each other. The couple is going to kiss heartily, but others do not approve of such behavior. So you have to help the lovers. Activate the kiss only when there are no unnecessary witnesses nearby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goat To The Moon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/goat-to-the-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/goat-to-the-moon/</guid>
      <description>Goat Simulator game invites you to a small abandoned farm, the inhabitants of which need help, attention and care. Due to the absence of the owner, the local economy has long collapsed, the animals have dispersed, and almost all the plants have died. You have to work hard to restore order here and turn a run-down farm into one of the best agricultural companies in the country. You can play the Goat Simulator game both on your own and in the company of your girlfriends, together ennobling the territory and caring for the living creatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Train Frvr</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gold-train-frvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gold-train-frvr/</guid>
      <description>Train Simulator will appeal to children and adults thanks to its excellent graphics, pleasant music and simple gameplay. At each stage, all kinds of cargo will have to be transported from station to station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Io Games Wormate 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/io-games-wormate-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/io-games-wormate-2/</guid>
      <description>The Slug Simulator game offers you to control a ball moving through the caves. On the way he is waiting for a large number of such creatures. Some of them are neutral or friendly, these balls can be safely attached to yourself to increase the mass. But there are also evil creatures, when touched, they, on the contrary, will take away a part of your body. And the most dangerous opponents are purple balls that can destroy your character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kung Fu Fighting</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kung-fu-fighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kung-fu-fighting/</guid>
      <description>The Fight Simulator game is designed for those who love a variety of fights. You need to choose a character for which you will play, and then go with him to the place of the battle. The fight can take place in a bar or in any other location. Hit your opponent to eventually take away all his health points. You can play with both a virtual opponent and a real friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make A Gingerbread House Cake</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/make-a-gingerbread-house-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/make-a-gingerbread-house-cake/</guid>
      <description>The Bread Simulator game invites you to make a variety of sandwiches. Control a funny character who needs to catch products falling from above. Inedible items should be avoided. If you catch some nonsense three times, then the game will end in a loss. So be careful!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Ariel Breakfast Cooking 1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-ariel-breakfast-cooking-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-ariel-breakfast-cooking-1/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to manage a wife who has to take care of her husband. The action takes place in a huge house, which has everything you need for a comfortable life. Move around the apartment, use different objects in order to create good conditions for your husband. The hints will help you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoot It</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/shoot-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/shoot-it/</guid>
      <description>Start playing Demolition Simulator game and control powerful rockets that explode when they fall. You need to destroy the structure in which the people took refuge. To be more precise, the main goal at each level is precisely the destruction of little men. Control the rocket, lifting it into the air and directing it where you need it. Please note that the fuel supply is limited, so try to do everything quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short Life</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/short-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/short-life/</guid>
      <description>If you want to get a portion of positive, you should start playing Homeless Simulator. Here you will meet a funny homeless man who slept peacefully in the city dump. Until the cop kicked him out. And now the bum walks the streets and attacks everyone who meets him on the way. Your task in the angry homeless simulator game is to help the character cope with the opponents. For this, only two keys are used - A and S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slenderman vs Freddy The Fazbear</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-vs-freddy-the-fazbear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-vs-freddy-the-fazbear/</guid>
      <description>The Springtrap Simulator game invites you to go on an exciting adventure with a funny digging robot. Help the kid go through all the tests, avoid the dangers that await him on the way, and collect the maximum amount of minerals that will improve the characteristics of the hero of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sochi Toilets Backstage</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sochi-toilets-backstage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sochi-toilets-backstage/</guid>
      <description>Do you want some fun? Then start playing Poop Simulator. Here you will meet a funny character in a red suit. He is ready to demonstrate his outstanding abilities. The fact is that the hero knows how to empty the intestines in ten different ways! In order to see how it might look, you need to click on the buttons located in the side areas of the screen. After that, a cheerful guy will show you a performance that does not look too aesthetically pleasing, but at the same time is able to cheer you up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tactical Weapon Pack 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tactical-weapon-pack-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tactical-weapon-pack-2/</guid>
      <description>The Weapon Crafting Simulator game takes you to a village where the inhabitants are about to fight their enemies. You will play the role of a blacksmith who makes a variety of weapons. Take orders from incoming soldiers, and then make swords, axes and other items for battle. The finished weapon will be evaluated by the client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Immersion</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-immersion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-immersion/</guid>
      <description>The Submarine Simulator game will take you to the ocean depths that you need to explore. First, create a suitable transport for yourself, using the available money to purchase the necessary parts. After you finish your work, set sail. The game about submarines will be very interesting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thief Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/thief-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/thief-challenge/</guid>
      <description>The Thief Simulator game offers you to help a boy whose apartment has been invaded by a robber. The task is to click on the items in time to help deal with the attacker. You can use those objects that turn red when you hover over them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tornado io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tornado-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tornado-io/</guid>
      <description>Destruction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truck Trials</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/truck-trials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/truck-trials/</guid>
      <description>The game Euro track simulator 3 in Russia invites you to turn into a driver of a huge truck. Your task is to transport goods from one place to another. Difficult tracks await you, which must be overcome with dignity. The main thing is to get to the finish line in the allotted time and not lose items from the body. The timer is displayed at the top of the simulator screen, where you will also see the amount of lost cargo as a percentage of the total.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vloggers Life Tycoon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/vloggers-life-tycoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/vloggers-life-tycoon/</guid>
      <description>The game creation simulator invites you to turn into the owner of a huge corporation. The company is engaged in the development of computer entertainment, and you need to establish its internal activities in order to earn money and invest in business development. In front of you is an office with computers for which you need to seat workers. After that, it remains to give them a task, indicating in detail what kind of game you want to receive this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolf Simulator Wild Animals D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wolf-simulator-wild-animals-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wolf-simulator-wild-animals-d/</guid>
      <description>While playing Wolf Simulator you will turn into a powerful predator. Your task is to move around the location and eat cows. Prize points are awarded for each cow eaten. The bottom of the screen displays the accumulated points and the number of livestock units that must be destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
