<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kick Butovo on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/kick-butovo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kick Butovo on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/kick-butovo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Kik Butovsky</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky/</guid>
      <description>The game Kik Butovsky will tell you about another invention of the famous cartoon extreme. Every day his tricks become more unusual and dangerous. Today, he uses a mega-cool trampoline that he made and installed in his backyard. Kik wants to make a crazy launch and set a new range for his flights. Now, for acceleration, he uses not just the angle of descent, but a mechanism with an elastic band.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Kik Butovsky - Halloween duel</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky---halloween-duel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky---halloween-duel/</guid>
      <description>Kik Butovsky got his own car. But to ride, like all people through the streets, he is bored, so he had to come up with fun for himself. His car will fly into the air like a pebble from a slingshot. You will have to help her: pull the elastic band as hard as you can, and then Kik will fly very high. And then do not yawn - with the help of buttons you can control the flight in the air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Kik Butovsky - Halloween Flight</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky---halloween-flight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky---halloween-flight/</guid>
      <description>On the eve of Halloween, Kik decided to organize new extreme tests. He will have incredible flights in specially designed snowmobiles, on which the guy will try to fly as far as possible. As always, there are heaps of upgrades and bonus items ahead that will help the hero to accelerate even more in flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Kik Butovsky - long distance flight</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky---long-distance-flight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky---long-distance-flight/</guid>
      <description>Kik Butovsky decided to test how far he could fly in a small cart on wheels if he launched it with the help of a super-elastic band. But even if you manage to fly really far, this does not mean at all that you can relax in the process. In flight, a lover of crazy ideas will face many obstacles and dangers. But there are also bonuses that he must collect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Kik Butovsky and Gunther for two</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky-and-gunther-for-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky-and-gunther-for-two/</guid>
      <description>In a 2-player game with Kik Butowski and Gunther, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to help your friends test out the new rocket launcher that Kik has come up with. Fasten your seat belts and set off with the hero on an exciting journey, trying to collect stars in flight and set new distance records on this cold winter day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Kik Butovsky for two 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky-for-two-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-kik-butovsky-for-two-2/</guid>
      <description>Kick Butt 2 Player Games 2 takes you to a mountainous area where the hero does his best to brighten up his boring life with new tricks. And today it is you who will become a participant in his crazy ideas. You need to go down the mountain as quickly as possible, and be sure to demonstrate a few somersaults in the air while jumping.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
