<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Madagascar on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/madagascar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Madagascar on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/madagascar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Madagascar 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-madagascar-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-madagascar-3/</guid>
      <description>The game Madagascar 3 introduces you to one of the characters of the popular cartoon. Granny goes racing across Europe and invites you to join her. Grandma does not like wild animals, and especially Alex and his friends, so she tries to hit them with her huge bag. Are you ready to help her? But keep in mind, the passage of the game Madagascar 3 will require excellent reaction and dexterity from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>game madagascar plane escape</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-madagascar-plane-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-madagascar-plane-escape/</guid>
      <description>Alex the lion and his friends travel to Africa in a small plane assembled by a team of penguins based on the drawings of the supergenius Kowalski. Help the brave residents of the New York Zoo get to their homeland by sitting at the helm of a small airplane. Control the movements of the plane on which the heroes of the game fly, and try to deliver them to their destination safe and sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Madagascar rpg in the zoo</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-madagascar-rpg-in-the-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-madagascar-rpg-in-the-zoo/</guid>
      <description>During the game Madagascar rpg around the zoo, a team of penguins led by the Skipper decide on another escape. To do this, they descend into the sewers that run under the zoo. Help the brave birds overcome all the obstacles on their way, get to the exit from the labyrinth of sewer pipes and breathe in the air of true freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocket penguins game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rocket-penguins-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rocket-penguins-game/</guid>
      <description>The heroes of the game - the penguins of the New York zoo, go to another battle with the famous Dr. Blowhole and invite you to join their squad. Choose one of the team members and help him complete some of the most dangerous missions. Your talents and skills will be highly appreciated by the Skipper, and he will definitely offer you the position of his deputy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
