<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Charlotte Strawberry on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/charlotte-strawberry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Charlotte Strawberry on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/charlotte-strawberry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Berry city game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/berry-city-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/berry-city-game/</guid>
      <description>The first thing you have to do during the game Berry City is to choose two girls who will pick strawberries. The harvest season has come, and the berry town invites everyone to work hard for glory. You, along with two heroines - Malinka and Blueberry, will go to catch strawberries falling from the sky. The more berries you catch, the more points you earn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Berry Pie Charlotte Strawberry</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-berry-pie-charlotte-strawberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-berry-pie-charlotte-strawberry/</guid>
      <description>While playing Berry Pie, Strawberry Charlotte will compete in a cooking contest. Her task is to bake a delicious cake. Help her earn the highest marks. Use all your imagination and create a real masterpiece that will delight all the guests of the competition. The game consists of several stages, at each of which tips will be waiting for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strawberry Shortcake Sweet Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/strawberry-shortcake-sweet-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/strawberry-shortcake-sweet-shop/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Charlotte Strawberry Café, where the main character and her friend prepare gourmet treats for visitors! The cafe opened recently, so the girls have not yet had time to hire employees to help in the kitchen. Help them cope with the influx of orders! An exciting process of cooking treats awaits you, from kneading dough to decorating desserts. There are three levels available in the game - making cakes, ice cream and milkshakes, in each of which you can show your creative side.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
