<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rockets on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/rockets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rockets on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/rockets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dash Rocket</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dash-rocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dash-rocket/</guid>
      <description>If all your life you dreamed of becoming a tester and pyrotechnician, then you definitely should try this game. Somewhere in the mountains there is a launch pad. You need to launch a rocket up and try to fly to the stars. It won&amp;rsquo;t work right away. But for each launch, money will be charged. And still collect crystals. Spend them on upgrades and climb higher and higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doodle God Rocket Scientist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/doodle-god-rocket-scientist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/doodle-god-rocket-scientist/</guid>
      <description>The Rocket game is designed for those who want to kill time, but not really strain at the same time. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be anything special. As well as frantically hitting the keyboard. All you have to do is launch the rocket and make it fly as high as possible. Collect bonuses along the way. Basically, these are coins and cans of fuel. By the way, it can be useful to fly not strictly up, but deviating to the sides - more surprises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr.Rocket</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dr.rocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dr.rocket/</guid>
      <description>A very simple toy. Yes, and the passage is not particularly difficult. But it is very bright and will appeal to even the smallest users. If only they knew how to hold a mouse in their hands and use it to move a flying rocket left and right. The goal is maximum points. To increase the speed, just collect the crystals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocket Clash 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rocket-clash-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rocket-clash-3d/</guid>
      <description>This game is somewhat similar to billiards. Only instead of balls here is a rocket. One. The goal is to pick up an astronaut. The trick is that the rocket needs to be launched in such a way that it, bouncing off the planets and the borders of the screen, catches the little man. Complexity - a limited supply of fuel. Each stage is more difficult than the previous one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocket Rodent Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rocket-rodent-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rocket-rodent-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>The backstory of the game Rocket to the Moon is very funny. Worth a look. By the way, the drawing is also top notch! And the process itself is amusing. The bottom line is that you have to pilot a spacecraft launched to the satellite of our planet. Use the keys and follow the instructions. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to upgrade before each new attempt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocketate</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rocketate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rocketate/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to launch into the sky not just a rocket, but a real carrier with a shuttle? Then you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place, friend! A ship is already waiting for you at the launch pad. It is necessary not only to launch it, but also to reach the maximum height, and then put the shuttle on the ground so that it does not explode. From the control you only have the arrows to the right and left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shadowhawks Squadron</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/shadowhawks-squadron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/shadowhawks-squadron/</guid>
      <description>War is always the same. Only the weapons change! Now you have rockets in your hands that can turn even the moon into radioactive ashes. By the way, your base is located there. And the enemies set out to destroy it, so that you could no longer sow reasonable, good, eternal. Shoot down their shells on the approach. Collect bonuses that descend on parachutes. Do an upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Blaze</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/space-blaze/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/space-blaze/</guid>
      <description>The goal of this game, as well as any other, is to go through all the stages. And during the passage you will be in the role of &amp;hellip; an alien minibus. Yes, you will have to deal with transporting green men from one point to another. Management of your &amp;ldquo;car&amp;rdquo; is quite complicated. Complete the task with minimal fuel and time costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spacecraft I</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/spacecraft-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/spacecraft-i/</guid>
      <description>In the very distant future, a new profession will appear - a rocket parker. But you can practice today. And if you live to see a bright future, you will be out of competition. So, using the arrow buttons, drive the vehicle past the obstacles to the parking lot. Take your time - even one touch of a foreign object leads to an accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Rocket</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-rocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-rocket/</guid>
      <description>While playing Rocket to Space you have to learn to think quickly and logically. To train this valuable quality, fifteen stages are given. They get progressively more difficult. The essence, by and large, is very simple. There is a rocket at the starting point. And there is a finish line. The spacecraft must get to it using intermediate stops - cubes. For maximum credit on points, you need to do everything in the minimum time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terre Defense</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/terre-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/terre-defense/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the test site where the Mars rocket will be tested. And you will do it. The essence is simple, like a cork: you need to launch a rocket as high as possible. It would be nice to collect bonuses along the way. But the aircraft is poorly controlled. An upgrade will help the case, with the help of which you will also attach all sorts of useful jokes to it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
