<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trucks on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/trucks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trucks on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/trucks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City truck driving game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-truck-driving-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-truck-driving-game/</guid>
      <description>Powerful American trucks will impress anyone. They are big and clumsy, but in the skillful hands of an experienced driver they demonstrate real miracles. You have to learn how to manage this type of transport. The first levels are just designed to get comfortable with the car, get used to its control system and dimensions. And then it will be more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Loader 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-loader-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-loader-3d/</guid>
      <description>Your task in this game looks simple - you just need to load the boxes into the truck. Use the mouse and keyboard to move the forklift, pick up the boxes and put them in the back of the car. This is not as easy as it seems - you will have to think through the sequence of actions in advance, overcome obstacles and carefully handle fragile cargo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Radioactive Trucks</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-radioactive-trucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-radioactive-trucks/</guid>
      <description>You have to drive a powerful truck carrying radioactive waste. Take a training course and prove your skills as a first-class driver. Pick up the cargo and deliver it to the burial place. Each new level starts from the parking point of the previous mission. This requires precise and careful driving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Trucking on Kamaz</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-trucking-on-kamaz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-trucking-on-kamaz/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to work in a delivery service. Just do not hope that they will immediately give you a new and modern car. To get started, test your strength on an old Kamaz. This is a large and powerful machine, so driving it is a very difficult task. It may take you hours of training to become a driving virtuoso of this giant on wheels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truck racing game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/truck-racing-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/truck-racing-game/</guid>
      <description>Truck racing game offers you to drive a giant truck. This car is equipped with a special nitro accelerator and can reach speeds faster than many sports cars. Racing games that involve trucks require the gamer to be attentive and careful. Develop speed, collect everything you see and look, do not roll over.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
