<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life simulators on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/life-simulators/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life simulators on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/life-simulators/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pro Gym</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pro-gym/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pro-gym/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you are invited to become the owner of your own fitness club. At each level, you need to serve all the clients in a limited time. Visitors to the hall are engaged in individual programs. Your task is to fulfill the requirements of clients in time, offering them the necessary simulators and choosing the appropriate level of load.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Chick Duck</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-chick-duck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-chick-duck/</guid>
      <description>Try to turn cute ducklings into world running champions. Make sure they get the right nutrition and exercise so that they can take first place in the duck race. And then, if you have enough patience and assertiveness, there is an opportunity to compete with a fat chicken already in the professional league.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survival Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/survival-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/survival-simulator/</guid>
      <description>The Life Simulator game will give you the opportunity, controlling one of 4 characters, to spend a whole month in a fairy-tale city, becoming truly happy. Feel free and find the best job in the world. But first you need to get an education. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget that you also need to make friends in order to be truly successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/virus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/virus/</guid>
      <description>Today you have to plunge into the microcosm and control the virus that lives in human blood. Your task is to infect red blood cells. Later you will receive evolution points with which you can multiply. But you should be wary of white blood cells and antibiotics. They have strong counteracting properties and can destroy your ward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
