<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sniper on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/sniper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sniper on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/sniper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elite Ghost Sniper</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elite-ghost-sniper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elite-ghost-sniper/</guid>
      <description>Ambush Sniper game will take you to the jungle of one of the Asian countries. According to the terms of this flash game, you need to destroy the base of terrorists. Shoot fast and accurately, reload your weapon in time and try not to get hit by a stray bullet. You can play for free, but keep in mind that the time to complete the task is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama: Pirate Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-pirate-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-pirate-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Today you will meet a sniper girl who is entrusted with a responsible task. Before starting the mission, carefully read the instructions to know which targets need to be eliminated. Use the space bar to turn on the optical sight. The mouse is needed in order to aim and shoot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rooftop Snipers</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rooftop-snipers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rooftop-snipers/</guid>
      <description>The game Sniper Ghost Warrior 2 tells the story of a super agent from the Alpha unit, who is entrusted with a responsible mission - to destroy a dangerous offender. The bandit settled in one of the districts of a small town. To complete the task, you need to identify the criminal from the available photo and make an accurate shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sniper Attack 3d</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sniper-attack-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sniper-attack-3d/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will participate in sniper training. You will have to shoot at moving targets. From level to level, the terrain changes and it becomes more and more difficult to navigate. But try to concentrate, if you miss more than 5 targets, the game will have to start over. Weapons are controlled with the mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sniper Ultimate Assasin</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sniper-ultimate-assasin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sniper-ultimate-assasin/</guid>
      <description>No one but you can help a man taken prisoner by terrorists. You are a retired sniper, but your knowledge and experience in this situation are simply irreplaceable. The goal is clear - the bandits must be destroyed, and the prisoner freed. But be careful, among the criminals there are also well-aimed shooters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sniper VS Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sniper-vs-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sniper-vs-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Game Sniper Ghost Warrior will take you to the years of the Great Patriotic War. The goal is the destruction of enemy soldiers who invaded the territory of the Soviet Union. To accomplish this task, you have a powerful sniper rifle in your hands, from which you will shoot, bringing victory over the Nazi invaders closer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soviet Sniper</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/soviet-sniper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/soviet-sniper/</guid>
      <description>In order to perform well the task assigned to you, you must strictly follow the instructions received. The terrorists have captured a whole block of the city. There are many professional soldiers among them, whom you were not recommended to fight with. You have to deal with them with a sniper rifle, shooting from a safe distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urban Sniper 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/urban-sniper-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/urban-sniper-3d/</guid>
      <description>The terrorists have seized the station with many hostages and are shooting with the special forces from all places where they can. Pick up a sniper rifle, take a comfortable position, and then try to track down the leader of the gang and his accomplices. Aim more accurately, because you have a limited number of rounds and very little time to complete the task.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
