<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Race on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/race/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Race on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/race/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City Driving Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-driving-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-driving-simulator/</guid>
      <description>During the game Bigfoot Racing you will be able to drive a car with big wheels to your heart&amp;rsquo;s content. To get started, select the difficulty level that best suits your virtual driving skills. Then you can safely press the start button. You will get to the track, where other participants of the competition have already gathered. Start playing online bigfoot competitions for free and try to overtake everyone. With control, you definitely will not have any difficulties, because the game uses a minimum of buttons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirt Bike Rider</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dirt-bike-rider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dirt-bike-rider/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to ride on a powerful bike! The game Crazy Racing is already waiting for you, launch it soon. It consists of several levels, and on each you will meet a unique track with obstacles: abysses, ascents, descents. Start your motorcycle and try to go all the way from start to finish without getting into an accident or falling into a hole. Another fun moment: when you play this crazy competition, you can collect donuts, and they will bring you reward points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eg Neon Rider</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-neon-rider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-neon-rider/</guid>
      <description>The game has the ability to choose a multiplayer mode or play alone. In any case, you will have to drive a funny jeep, collect stars, but also invest in the standard. Each stage has its own standard. If you invest, you will go to the next level, if not, try again. In addition to dynamics and drive, the game will delight you with bright graphics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endless Truck</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/endless-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/endless-truck/</guid>
      <description>Rollercoaster racing games are an incredible mix of car and motorcycle competitions. Choose your favorite transport and go to conquer the tracks, earning money to buy upgrades. Rollercoaster offers you several models of cars and motorcycles to choose from. To open the next track, you need to qualify and defeat all rivals. When the nitro sign turns blue, you can use the acceleration. Drive the car using the arrows on the keyboard, the X button is nitro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Racing cars 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-racing-cars-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-racing-cars-2/</guid>
      <description>During the game Racing Cars 2 you will be able to participate in the very competitions about which the famous cartoon was filmed. To begin with, you will be asked to play Lightning McQueen, but as you progress, other characters will open up, after which you can choose a new car for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Racing for two Hot Wheels</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-racing-for-two-hot-wheels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-racing-for-two-hot-wheels/</guid>
      <description>With the help of the Hot Wheels Racing game for two, you will get a unique opportunity to measure your strength with your best friend on the football field. Having at your disposal small but nimble cars, you need to Crazy Games as many goals as possible against the opponent. Before the start of the race, decide on the management, and forward - to new victories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jet Ski Boat Race</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jet-ski-boat-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jet-ski-boat-race/</guid>
      <description>Spectacular racing game in which you&amp;rsquo;ll race through the waves. But first, choose your vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorbike Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/motorbike-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/motorbike-simulator/</guid>
      <description>The exciting game American Racing 2 will appeal to all fans of high-speed racing cars. Test yourself as a pilot of such a car, earn money to buy upgrades, unlock new tracks and develop your driving skills. The 2nd Rollercoaster Challenge challenges you to complete the tracks of the biggest racing season ever, spanning an entire calendar year, with four rides in each of the twelve months. Take care of your car, it can be broken quite easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police vs Thief: Hot Pursuit</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/police-vs-thief-hot-pursuit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/police-vs-thief-hot-pursuit/</guid>
      <description>Roger is a master of his craft. He is able to change any car beyond recognition. No wonder he has a lot of clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian UAZ Offroad Driving 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-uaz-offroad-driving-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-uaz-offroad-driving-3d/</guid>
      <description>Game Test drive UAZ Patriot 2 invites you to test a domestic car. It is necessary to control the car so that it drives to the finish line as quickly as possible. In total, you need to conquer a distance of 7100 meters, but a variety of sections of the route await you ahead: urban road, rural, mountain, swamp and many more options. You need to try not to get stuck in a swamp and not get caught speeding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speedboat Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/speedboat-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/speedboat-racing/</guid>
      <description>During the Boat Racing game, you will find yourself on a dangerous water track, along which it is proposed to ride a boat. Control your boat, overtake your rivals and try to reach the finish line number one. You need to drive the specified number of laps and not let yourself be overtaken. The game uses a top view, which allows you to see large sections of the track. You can play online water races for free as long as you like, we recommend launching them right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Road</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/traffic-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/traffic-road/</guid>
      <description>The process of the City Racing game will enchant you with a mix of excitement and speed, which will help you overtake your rivals. If you decide to play it long enough, you can get great pleasure, because there are a lot of levels in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Scooter Mania</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/water-scooter-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/water-scooter-mania/</guid>
      <description>The Grand Turismo races were and are the most prestigious competitions in the world among professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
