<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cafe on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/cafe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cafe on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/cafe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crystals Sweets Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crystals-sweets-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crystals-sweets-shop/</guid>
      <description>Games Waitress in a cafe will plunge you into the atmosphere of a holiday, cheerful mood and a huge selection of all kinds of cakes and pastries. Every child dreams of visiting a fabulous establishment on New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, where the beautiful Snow Maiden delivers food, and at the same time fulfills any, even the most cherished desire. Today you have to become a cafe hostess and a waitress at the same time in a game for girls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Coffee Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-coffee-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-coffee-shop/</guid>
      <description>Game Cafe - an exciting economic strategy. The main goal is to build your own business so that it is guaranteed to bring income. Today you have the opportunity to become a fast food tycoon. To do this, you need to perform simple tasks and carefully calculate all your actions. It is necessary to build a network of shops, cafes and eateries, and lure as many people as possible into them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natalies Winter Treats</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/natalies-winter-treats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/natalies-winter-treats/</guid>
      <description>While playing Barbie Cafe you will help a pretty girl cope with the influx of customers and prepare a huge amount of delicious ice cream. This delicacy is made from many ingredients, so listen to the wishes of the client and prepare a special dessert for him. But keep in mind, the time of the game is limited, so you should hurry up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
