<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kisses on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/kisses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kisses on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/kisses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angelina And Brad Romantic Date</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/angelina-and-brad-romantic-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/angelina-and-brad-romantic-date/</guid>
      <description>The New Year is coming, and on such a holiday you want to receive only positive. The guy and the girl decided to kiss enough, but someone constantly interferes with them. Your task is to Crazy Games the specified number of points within the allotted time. But for this you need to stop kissing in time, otherwise you will lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dotted Girl Cinema Flirting</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dotted-girl-cinema-flirting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dotted-girl-cinema-flirting/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will be transported to another country. There, a couple of tourists decided to kiss during the tour. But this can only be done when no one is looking at the lovers. If there is a danger of exposure, as indicated by an exclamation point, then you will need to stop the kiss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dotted Girl Sauna Flirting</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dotted-girl-sauna-flirting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dotted-girl-sauna-flirting/</guid>
      <description>A loving couple from Thailand was able to set a record for the duration of a passionate hug. It is these heroes that the Kissing game is dedicated to. Here you will see the same guy and girl who again want to have a great time with each other. But no one should see them! Pay close attention to what is happening on the screen. If an exclamation mark suddenly appears above someone&amp;rsquo;s head, then this will be a sign that the person is going to look around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flirting On School</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/flirting-on-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/flirting-on-school/</guid>
      <description>After starting the Kissing at School game, you will be taken to a lesson where a girl and a guy are going to kiss each other to their heart&amp;rsquo;s content. But neither classmates nor the teacher should notice them. Activate the kiss only when no one is looking at the couple in love. And if someone pays attention to kissing students, you will have to urgently correct the situation. For example, the teacher gives a task, and you need to quickly give the correct answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Princess School Kiss</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-school-kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-school-kiss/</guid>
      <description>On Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day, the air is literally permeated with love. The guy and the girl are ready to kiss anywhere, but strangers should not see this intimate process. Therefore, you need to carefully monitor what is happening on the screen in order to avoid trouble and not lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ladybug First Date</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ladybug-first-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ladybug-first-date/</guid>
      <description>The girl and the guy are walking in the park, and they really like to spend time together. A couple in love is going to kiss a lot, but it is very undesirable to catch someone&amp;rsquo;s eye. If someone notices the kiss, the game will immediately end with you losing. Therefore, act as carefully as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Princess Mistletoe Kiss</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-princess-mistletoe-kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-princess-mistletoe-kiss/</guid>
      <description>Launching the Kiss game will take you to a music concert. Here you will see several musicians. The soloists of the group are not too willing to perform songs, they want to devote time to kissing. But you can do this pleasant thing only when no one is looking at the stars in love. Otherwise, you will lose your gaming life!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Sauna Flirting</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-sauna-flirting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-sauna-flirting/</guid>
      <description>Mermaid Ariel is having a great time with her beloved prince. They want to kiss a lot, but there is some problem - no one should see this. Therefore, if an exclamation mark appears on the screen, it means that an unexpected guest will soon appear. In such cases, quickly stop the kiss or you will lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miraculous Hero Kiss</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/miraculous-hero-kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/miraculous-hero-kiss/</guid>
      <description>The guy and the girl had a nice date on the street. But they are constantly interrupted by someone. You need to drive away uninvited guests who disturb the couple&amp;rsquo;s idyll. To do this, use the items that are around the characters in the game. If you can&amp;rsquo;t think of a solution on your own, use a hint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prince Princess Kiss Quest</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/prince-princess-kiss-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/prince-princess-kiss-quest/</guid>
      <description>A farm worker has fallen in love with his owner&amp;rsquo;s daughter, and she loves him back. You need to make sure that no one interferes with the couple kissing. If someone notices them, then you will lose one game life. An exclamation mark will serve as a hint, watch for its appearance on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Office Kissing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/secret-office-kissing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/secret-office-kissing/</guid>
      <description>The process of the game Love and Kisses is dedicated to Princess Mulan. She invited her chosen one to kiss her 80 times, but no one should notice this. Therefore, if you see that a stranger is going to turn towards the lovers, immediately stop the kiss, otherwise you will lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Love Trouble</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/valentines-love-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/valentines-love-trouble/</guid>
      <description>The girl and the guy have a great time on the beach, because they are in love with each other. The characters of the game are going to kiss a lot, but it is important not to allow prying eyes. Pay close attention to everything that happens on the screen, so that if necessary, immediately stop the kiss.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
