<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>School on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/school/</link>
    <description>Recent content in School on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Driving school game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/driving-school-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/driving-school-game/</guid>
      <description>You are taking your driving test. To obtain the coveted driver&amp;rsquo;s license, it remains to pass the last test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Ever After High rpg around the school</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-ever-after-high-rpg-around-the-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-ever-after-high-rpg-around-the-school/</guid>
      <description>While playing Eve After High rpg around the school, you get a book that tells about the curse imposed on Wonderland. Embark on a dangerous journey and help the inhabitants get rid of a terrible spell. The game consists of six levels, on each of which you will find a new adventure and a mandatory task to complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game how to train your dragon school of dragons</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-how-to-train-your-dragon-school-of-dragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-how-to-train-your-dragon-school-of-dragons/</guid>
      <description>The game How to Train Your Dragon School of Dragons 2 invites you to try your hand at dangerous flights. Control the dragon in such a way that you don&amp;rsquo;t run into obstacles on its way. If this happens, some of your health will be taken away from you. You can restore it by eating a sheep. The goal of the game is to fly as far as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama school game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-school-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-school-game/</guid>
      <description>Unforgettable adventures await you while playing Kogama School. This game is similar to the well-known Minecraft, and its characters look just as cubic. Create your own hero and start an exciting journey through the virtual world. In the game, you can even come up with an individual map, and then invite other players to it. Move around the locations, collect useful resources that may be useful in the future, and build buildings in the style of Kogama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Graduation</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-graduation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-graduation/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have the opportunity to dress up a young teacher for her first day at work. It&amp;rsquo;s so important to impress students and bosses! You can choose a hairstyle, clothes, shoes, and make-up. By the way, the game has an option that allows you to zoom in on the character&amp;rsquo;s face. When you&amp;rsquo;re done, save the finished image to your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
