<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>changing rooms on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/changing-rooms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in changing rooms on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/changing-rooms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Around The World: Japan Street Fashion</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/around-the-world-japan-street-fashion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/around-the-world-japan-street-fashion/</guid>
      <description>A famous actress turned to you with a request. For the summer season, she needs to pick up new stylish things and create original outfits for walking out of them. Try to come up with not only beautiful, but also comfortable costumes. The images created by you will please the beauty, and she will wear them with great pleasure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audrey Steampunk Fashion</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/audrey-steampunk-fashion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/audrey-steampunk-fashion/</guid>
      <description>In this toy you will be able to demonstrate your skills in creating costumes in the original steampunk style. As you know, this fantastic style boldly mixes modern fashion trends and Victorian motifs. Design your own steampunk outfit using items from the provided wardrobe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonnie Oktoberfest</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-oktoberfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-oktoberfest/</guid>
      <description>The heroine of this toy was invited to a Thanksgiving celebration. Choose an original outfit for the young beauty. Choose items from her wardrobe and create a real Thanksgiving outfit from them. The hosts of the celebration will appreciate your efforts and will definitely ask you to create festive outfits for them next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinderellas Closet</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cinderellas-closet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cinderellas-closet/</guid>
      <description>Princess Cinderella is preparing to meet her lover. Help the fairy tale girl choose a romantic outfit that will highlight her beauty. Give Cinderella an original hairstyle, then choose a romantic dress and jewelry. Feel like a real sorceress, creating a fabulous outfit for Cinderella.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Princess Christmas Ball</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/disney-princess-christmas-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/disney-princess-christmas-ball/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you are given the opportunity to evaluate your ability as a designer. In order to get an estimate, you need to create an original New Year&amp;rsquo;s outfit from the items provided. After your model is ready, press the rate button and see how many points you got. Try to come up with a festive costume that will score the maximum number of points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girls Photoshopping Dressup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/girls-photoshopping-dressup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/girls-photoshopping-dressup/</guid>
      <description>Baby Elsa, the heroine of the famous cartoon &amp;ldquo;Frozen&amp;rdquo;, went to the sea. Help the beauty to choose things from her wardrobe that will be needed on vacation. Create original beach outfits for Elsa that the girl will like and emphasize her beauty. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to pick up the right beach accessories and jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Princess Real Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-real-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-real-makeover/</guid>
      <description>A young beauty is invited to a fashionable party, she dreams of making a good impression on the guests of the celebration. The girl asks you to help her in choosing original clothes. First, give her a festive hair and make-up, and then start creating a stylish outfit. Choose the necessary things from the wardrobe of the heroine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagirls Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/instagirls-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/instagirls-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>A university graduate got a job at a well-known law office. Help the girl pick out some business suits for work. Choose the necessary things from the beauty&amp;rsquo;s wardrobe and create some stylish sets. Do not forget to make a suitable hairstyle that will emphasize her beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessies Winter Fashion</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessies-winter-fashion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jessies-winter-fashion/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have the opportunity to create a collection of stylish winter clothes for young people. Come up with some original outfits from the things in your wardrobe. In addition to clothing, take care of the hairstyle, which will harmoniously emphasize the originality and style of the costumes you have created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Diner De Blanc</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-diner-de-blanc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-diner-de-blanc/</guid>
      <description>During the fashion week held in Milan, the capital of European fashion, there is a show of works by young designers, to which you have received an invitation. Prepare some models to showcase your fashion design skills. Do not forget to save the images you created in the computer&amp;rsquo;s memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Mermaid Parade</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-mermaid-parade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-mermaid-parade/</guid>
      <description>In this wonderful game you have to take part in creating characters for a fairy tale cartoon. Its action takes place in the fairy kingdom of fairies. Try to come up with some funny fairies, dress them up in original clothes and jewelry. Your efforts will not go unnoticed, and the filmmakers will invite you to work on their next films.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Royal Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-royal-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-royal-wedding/</guid>
      <description>A famous model is preparing for her wedding and has chosen you as her wedding designer. Help the beauty turn her wedding into the best celebration of the season. Choose a chic wedding dress for the girl, pick up jewelry and accessories. Do not forget to give the bride an original make-up and a stylish hairstyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Sorority Pledges</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-sorority-pledges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-sorority-pledges/</guid>
      <description>Start the process of the Dress Up game and design an outfit for the girl in a pirate style. Here at your disposal is a huge assortment of clothes and all kinds of accessories, there is even a weapon. Use all this splendor in order to create a new excellent image for the heroine. You can use hints if needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock Band Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rock-band-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rock-band-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>The famous fashion house invites you to take part in the competition of young designers. The jury will evaluate each work in two stages. First, you need to choose original clothes, shoes and jewelry for the model, and at the second stage of the competition, come up with a fresh color scheme for the costume you created, which will captivate all members of the jury with its beauty and style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spongebob Crossdress</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/spongebob-crossdress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/spongebob-crossdress/</guid>
      <description>The famous SpongeBob goes to the New Year&amp;rsquo;s carnival at the Krusty Krabs diner. Help baby Sponge pick up a stylish fancy dress that will amaze all party participants with originality. The outfit that you propose to SpongeBob will be so liked by others that it will be recognized as the best outfit of the party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trend Girl</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/trend-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/trend-girl/</guid>
      <description>Model house Chanel invited you to become a member of a prestigious fashion show. You have the opportunity to demonstrate your skills and talents on the world-famous podium. At your disposal are two models and an unlimited selection of clothes, shoes, jewelry, make-up tools. Create looks that will impress the famous Chanel fashion designers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
