<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strategy about knights on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/strategy-about-knights/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strategy about knights on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/strategy-about-knights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Age Of Pixel</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/age-of-pixel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/age-of-pixel/</guid>
      <description>In the dark ages, the rules of survival are very simple: either you destroy potential enemies, or they destroy you and take over your lands. So in this game, the goal is to conquer the territory (see the map at the beginning) one by one and get to the castle. There are no special difficulties and strategies. The main thing is to send suitable troops towards the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Knight</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/black-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/black-knight/</guid>
      <description>This game has a lot from the legendary first &amp;ldquo;Diablo&amp;rdquo;. Choose a character, watch a video in which his bride is kidnapped, and go to the dungeons in search. Along the way, you will encounter battles with skeletons, the walking dead and other creatures. Pick up new weapons, develop and use magic. Extra items can be sold. For those who have never seen Diablo, there are clues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Castle Defense</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/castle-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/castle-defense/</guid>
      <description>The background of the game is revealed in the introductory video. But she doesn&amp;rsquo;t care about you. The bottom line is that the old king must fight off the zombies that hang around his castle at night. During the day, you can upgrade buildings, buy yourself new weapons, add health, and also look for treasures and resources to upgrade. After all, with each new night, zombies become stronger and faster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Building</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/city-building/</guid>
      <description>This game immerses you in harsh times. The intro video kind of shows them off, so it&amp;rsquo;s worth watching. Next, you choose your character. The range is simply huge. Each character has a description. For a successful passage, it is worth translating it from English. Well, then start to survive. It is recommended to follow the prompts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clash Of Warlord Orcs</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/clash-of-warlord-orcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/clash-of-warlord-orcs/</guid>
      <description>You can skip the long text background. There is nothing useful in it, except for 100500 English letters. Next comes the learning phase with endless instructions. Disabling will not work. But then everything is simple: build a base, train troops, rob caravans and wipe enemies with their castles into dust. In addition to conventional troops, you can choose magical support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Battles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fantasy-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fantasy-battles/</guid>
      <description>This game is somewhat similar to chess. In any case, in addition to brandishing a sword, gamers will also sometimes have to turn on their brains. As for the rest, everything is the same as in many similar games: you move from location to location on the map, and when you stop, you enter into an unequal battle with ghoul ghouls. There are all sorts of upgrades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lord Of The Knights</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lord-of-the-knights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lord-of-the-knights/</guid>
      <description>The game is as simple as a pine board! You choose a character: archer-man or archer-woman. All. You are standing on the right side of the screen in the outfit of an English archer, and on the left you are being attacked by enemies. Apparently, these are some kind of Saracens. If they reach your character, they will start slashing very quickly with a sword and then it will be over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Defense Z</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/medieval-defense-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/medieval-defense-z/</guid>
      <description>Everything is simple here: there are two locks. One belongs to the enemy, and the other belongs to you. The task is to protect your castle from destruction and wipe out the enemy. Before the start of the battles, you can choose the level of difficulty, the option of passing the game, as well as see the instructions (which will help you quickly understand the controls). The graphics do not shine, but they tried to compensate for this shortcoming with dynamism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protect The Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/protect-the-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/protect-the-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>The developer company &amp;ldquo;Armor Games&amp;rdquo; again pleases us with its creation. The gameplay is preceded by a story. It can be skipped. However, a quick immersion in the fever of battles still does not work. After all, you are dealing with a turn-based strategy. It is recommended to look closely at the tips and think through your moves well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quizland Conquest</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/quizland-conquest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/quizland-conquest/</guid>
      <description>A game that requires the player to be able to make decisions quickly is somewhat similar to checkers. The plot is like this. There are two castles: yours and the enemy&amp;rsquo;s. Troops are constantly generated there, which must be sent to capture buildings. On the first level, there are only two castles. The farther, the more buildings appear on the screen. The captured building automatically becomes a barracks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Defense D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tower-defense-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tower-defense-d/</guid>
      <description>You can start a new game or choose an old save if you have one. You can skip the long introduction, it&amp;rsquo;s still in English. Then, after some preparations, you can finally start playing. Its essence is reduced to the defense of your castle from enemies. The defense must smoothly turn into an attack, because the flow of enemies is endless. The purpose of the attack: destroy the enemy castle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
