<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Games For children 8 years old on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/games-for-children-8-years-old/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games For children 8 years old on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/games-for-children-8-years-old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adam And Eve Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/adam-and-eve-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/adam-and-eve-zombies/</guid>
      <description>The process of the game for children 8 years old Boys is associated with multi-colored magnets. A huge number of them will be displayed on the screen, and you need to rotate the magnets, trying to create combinations of three or more identical elements. Such combinations disappear, and new parts descend in their place from above. The game consists of a large number of levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amys New Look</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/amys-new-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/amys-new-look/</guid>
      <description>After launching the game for kids 8 years old for girls, you will see the famous traveler Dasha. This time she needs to take care of the horse, and you need to help her in this exciting children&amp;rsquo;s game. It consists of several mini-rounds, and you can complete tasks in any order. Just click on one of the five images, and then act according to the conditions of the mini-game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Block</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-block/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game, you will see the playing field, where colored cubes with white stripes applied to them fall from above. You need to install them so that the strips are in contact with each other. Three identical strips lying side by side will lead to removal. The blank block also disappears from the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fruit Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fruit-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fruit-escape/</guid>
      <description>Educational games for children 8 years old offer to solve exciting puzzles. You need to pour water through pipes from one vessel to another. At the same time, the allowable volume is marked on each of them. It is necessary to arrange the proposed elements in such a way that not a drop of water spills past, and all of it flows through the pipes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Bears</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/love-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/love-bears/</guid>
      <description>Entertaining games for children 8 years old offer you to help a little bird who really needs to get to his birdhouse. Guide the feathered heroine through the intricate labyrinth so that she can finally return home. Arrow buttons are used to control the cute bird.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unblock That</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/unblock-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/unblock-that/</guid>
      <description>Intellectual games for children 8 years old will introduce you to a little penguin who needs to get to the other side of the pond. And you need to build a bridge for him from ice blocks of various shapes. Think about exactly how they should be located so that the penguin can successfully cross to the opposite shore.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
