<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Winx on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/winx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Winx on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/winx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Disney Fairies: Pixie Party Couture</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/disney-fairies-pixie-party-couture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/disney-fairies-pixie-party-couture/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to collect images from pieces dedicated to the Winx sorceresses. The screen presents a large number of confused elements, and you just have to find the right places for them. The tooltip that opens when you hover over the question mark will help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game New Winx Bloomix</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-new-winx-bloomix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-new-winx-bloomix/</guid>
      <description>The new Winx Bloomix games invite you on an exciting journey through a magical dimension, during which, among other things, you will have to fight the insidious Trix and their minions. Wicked witches have come up with new traps for the Winx fairies and hope to lure them there. But, thanks to your help, the insidious plans of the villains will not come true. If you try, the Trix will be defeated in a fair fight, unable to withstand the magical power of Bloomix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game winx bloomix battle 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-winx-bloomix-battle-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-winx-bloomix-battle-2/</guid>
      <description>After starting the Winx Bloomix Battle 2 game, you will be transported to a magical world and go on an incredible journey with the sorceresses. But first you need to create a team of three Winx fairies, each of which will perform its function. Then it remains only to indicate the location and wait for the start of the battle. You won&amp;rsquo;t have to wait long, very soon monsters will attack you from all sides and need to be destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Perfect Wedding</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-perfect-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-perfect-wedding/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will find puzzles on the Winx theme in the style of Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. On the screen you will see several pieces that need to be correctly connected to each other. The game consists of several levels, and at each stage the number of elements will increase. The time for passing is limited and is only 30 seconds!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>winx bloomix battle game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/winx-bloomix-battle-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/winx-bloomix-battle-game/</guid>
      <description>Start the process of the Winx Bloomix Battle game and turn into an ally of sorceresses who are always on guard for good. The Winx fairies have to fight with a huge number of evil creatures, and you need to help them with this. Create your own team of three fairies and go to conquer the gaming space. During the battle, you just need to attack the enemies to destroy the entire enemy squad and get gold coins.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
