<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Baby girls on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/baby-girls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Baby girls on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/baby-girls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Avocado Toast Instagram</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/avocado-toast-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/avocado-toast-instagram/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to cook mouth-watering and delicious sandwiches! Here you will see various ingredients for sandwiches flying on one half of the screen. You need to catch them in order to end up with a big sandwich. Please note that the ingredients must be in strict order. Cooking time is limited!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Fun Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-fun-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-fun-day/</guid>
      <description>Princess Sophia has a little sister whom she loves to take care of. But the baby is very capricious, cries and wakes up even in the middle of the night. Help the heroine swaddle the baby and give her a bottle of milk. With your help, Sofia will become a caring nanny for her sister. And after the baby falls asleep, you can do a little to yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Differences</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-hazel-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-hazel-differences/</guid>
      <description>Dasha is waiting for her mother in the flower shop. She got bored and decided to have some fun. The girl is offered several short games to choose from. The only condition is to make sure that the girl&amp;rsquo;s mother does not notice what her daughter is doing. Just close the window with the game in time, if suddenly someone appears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonnie Gucci Vs Prada</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-gucci-vs-prada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-gucci-vs-prada/</guid>
      <description>Feel like a real hairdresser, making a variety of hairstyles for girls. Keep in mind that you will need to create beauty not at will, but based on the images presented. Use a variety of hairdressing tools to get the desired result. Try not to make mistakes to get more points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coachella Hairstyles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/coachella-hairstyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/coachella-hairstyles/</guid>
      <description>For girls 4 5 years</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>College Toga Party Dressup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/college-toga-party-dressup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/college-toga-party-dressup/</guid>
      <description>Makeup games for girls will show you a girl who has serious skin problems. Now you need to cope with all difficult situations using special cosmetics. And when the skin again shines with cleanliness and health, it remains to apply makeup and choose an outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cooking-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cooking-battle/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to cook delicious ice cream with various fillings. Order forms will be displayed on the screen, and you just have to create cold desserts in accordance with the specified information. Put ice cream in bowls, and then add berries and other additions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Queen Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dark-queen-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dark-queen-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>For girls for 8 years</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Princess Pet Salon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/disney-princess-pet-salon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/disney-princess-pet-salon/</guid>
      <description>Create an original horse by choosing a variety of cute appearance elements for it. Change the color of the pony, add a matching mane and tail, don&amp;rsquo;t forget the bridle and saddle. And here you can depict a nice drawing on the body. If you want, then change the background to make the horse look even more impressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doll House Cake Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/doll-house-cake-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/doll-house-cake-cooking/</guid>
      <description>For girls 8 years old 2nd grade</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Baby Bathing Time</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-baby-bathing-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/happy-baby-bathing-time/</guid>
      <description>Draculara and her little sister are preparing for a country walk after sunset. However, the child is so dirty during the day that he needs to be bathed immediately. Help him bathe in warm water with scented shampoo. Entertain the girl, give her favorite toys so that her mood is upbeat, otherwise she will be terribly capricious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cream Pancake</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-cream-pancake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-cream-pancake/</guid>
      <description>Get ready to make delicious pancakes! Here you will need to reproduce portions according to the model. Arrange delicious additions and decorations in the same way as on the original version. The game consists of several levels, and gradually the process will become more complicated, the number of details will increase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invisible Whispers</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/invisible-whispers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/invisible-whispers/</guid>
      <description>Help the girl friends take pictures of funny ghosts. Ghosts will constantly appear on the screen, and you just have to capture them so that the pictures are the clearest. All those ghosts whose pictures you need to get are shown on a special panel. There are also bonus ghosts!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kim K Busy Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kim-k-busy-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kim-k-busy-day/</guid>
      <description>Kids games for girls for two will introduce you to the brave Mario, who is trying to help the princess escape from the domain of the evil dragon. It is proposed to manage both Mario and the princess, so it is best to play together. The game consists of a large number of levels designed for two, on each of them it is necessary to overcome all obstacles and get to the exit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindergarten Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kindergarten-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kindergarten-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>The game Kindergarten in Russian offers free to play for everyone. In it you can turn into a real nanny who brings small children to look after. Your task is to take care of the kids, fulfilling all their desires. Keep a close eye on each child, tracking his behavior. Children may want to eat, sleep, play. Sometimes you have to change the diaper, after washing the baby - everything is like in a real kindergarten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Ear Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mini-ear-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mini-ear-doctor/</guid>
      <description>For girls 5 years old</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Dolphin Show 7</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-dolphin-show-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-dolphin-show-7/</guid>
      <description>An interesting game invites you to try your hand at dolphin training. These smartest animals are able to show many interesting tricks, and spectators constantly come to see them. You need to control the dolphin in such a way that it demonstrates the given actions. Two modes are available: normal and night show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pig Family Dress Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pig-family-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pig-family-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>In the game for kids 5 years old for girls you will need to help Belle return the prince to his normal appearance. To do this, you have to resort to magic. The problem is that no one knows the exact composition of the monster transformation potion. Therefore, in the children&amp;rsquo;s game, you will have to act experimentally. Mix any four of the proposed components to end up with a bubbling drink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixie Pregnant Check Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixie-pregnant-check-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixie-pregnant-check-up/</guid>
      <description>Today you have to take care of princesses Rapunzel and Elsa. They are both going to be mothers. First you need to choose one girl and play mini-games with her. Find your mom-to-be&amp;rsquo;s favorite food, sing a lullaby for your baby, make a vitamin cocktail. At the next level, you will play the role of a doctor performing a medical examination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plasticine Bubbles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/plasticine-bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/plasticine-bubbles/</guid>
      <description>Help the funny ball go through all the dangerous levels and save your little brothers! Control the round character without falling into traps or touching enemies. If this suddenly happens, then one game life will be lost. But their supply can be replenished by picking up a heart. Keys open the door to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Poppins</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-poppins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-poppins/</guid>
      <description>For girls 7 years old</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Slumber Party Funny Faces</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-slumber-party-funny-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-slumber-party-funny-faces/</guid>
      <description>Girls for 9 10 years old</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess St Patricks Party</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-st-patricks-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-st-patricks-party/</guid>
      <description>Now you have to dress up a charming flower fairy. The game is implemented in a rather unusual way. In order to change the girl&amp;rsquo;s clothes, you need to click on the flowers surrounding her. Each of them hides a certain category of wardrobe. There you can find clothes, shoes, hairstyles, and jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princesses Spring Style Design</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-spring-style-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princesses-spring-style-design/</guid>
      <description>With this game, big and small wonders become available. A mouse-controlled magnifying glass will help you find everything you need and see everything extraordinary, going to the world created by the great wizard. You have to help a little girl color a picture, try local dishes and dress up for a walk around Disneyland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puppy Cupcake</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/puppy-cupcake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/puppy-cupcake/</guid>
      <description>For girls 5 6 years</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superhero Pregnant Emergency</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-pregnant-emergency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-pregnant-emergency/</guid>
      <description>During the game Give birth to children you have to become an obstetrician of a charming princess. Not afraid? Then go ahead! You will end up in a hospital where the heroine of the game is almost ready to become a mother. All the necessary medical instruments have already been prepared on the screen to help the baby be born. Start the operation, throwing all the bad thoughts out of your head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Angie Fashion Dressing Room</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweet-angie-fashion-dressing-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweet-angie-fashion-dressing-room/</guid>
      <description>The kids game for girls takes you to London where the streets are full of trendy shops. You are given a certain amount of money that you can spend at your own discretion, purchasing clothes, shoes and accessories. Please note that from time to time you will be invited to parties with a strict dress code. In this case, look for things with the indicated icon among the whole variety in order to successfully enter the event and increase your gaming level.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
