<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cooking ice cream on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/cooking-ice-cream/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cooking ice cream on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/cooking-ice-cream/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crystals Ice Cream Maker</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crystals-ice-cream-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crystals-ice-cream-maker/</guid>
      <description>Cooking Ice Cream Cafe will turn you into a real pastry chef who knows a lot about cold treats. In it you need to create ice cream in accordance with the wishes of customers. Each dessert has its own original recipe, and you must strictly follow it during preparation, otherwise nothing will work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emilys Ice Cream Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/emilys-ice-cream-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/emilys-ice-cream-shop/</guid>
      <description>The Ice Cream Maker game invites you to try your hand at creating a cold dessert. In it, you can easily create a treat in a waffle cup. Choose a variety of elements that will achieve an original result. The game is available to change the type of cup, ice cream itself, various additives and decorative elements. You can save the finished image if you wish, and then come up with a couple more options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Ice Cream Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/homemade-ice-cream-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/homemade-ice-cream-cooking/</guid>
      <description>After starting this exciting game, you will go to the kitchen, where you are invited to try to make ice cream from the available ingredients. All the necessary components are already on the table, and you just have to connect them in accordance with the recipe. Rely on the hints so as not to get confused and prepare a great dessert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cream Sandwich Cake</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-cream-sandwich-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-cream-sandwich-cake/</guid>
      <description>Prepare cool ice cream using the suggested ingredients. You can choose a glass for dessert, ice cream itself, a variety of toppings and sprinkles. Do not forget about a couple of decorative elements to make the delicacy not only tasty, but also pretty in appearance. You can add a drink to ice cream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice O Matik</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-o-matik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-o-matik/</guid>
      <description>Make delicious and beautiful ice cream! To do this, you do not have to perform any complicated steps. Just choose the look of the ice cream scoops, add sprinkles, toppings and other decorative elements that will perfectly decorate the dessert. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to pick up the cutest plate as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony Ice Cream Cone</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-ice-cream-cone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-ice-cream-cone/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game, you will meet a charming girl named Sofia. She invites you to make great ice cream together. Choose any kind of dessert, add toppings, sprinkles, berries, and other decorative elements. If you create three ice creams according to the proposed sample, then a secret bonus awaits you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Halloween Ice Cream</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-halloween-ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-halloween-ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>Make ice cream for the cute monster school girls! Choose a glass or a vase, place the chosen dessert there, and then proceed to decorate it. You can use a variety of additives that will make the delicacy even more tasty and attractive. You can also choose a background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spooky Halloween Ice Cream</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/spooky-halloween-ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/spooky-halloween-ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>Vampires love ice cream too! In this game, you have to work in a cafe where cute vampire girls will constantly drop by. They will place orders, and you just have to prepare the appropriate desserts for them. The game consists of several levels, and on each you need to earn the specified amount.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
