<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cooking food on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/cooking-food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cooking food on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/cooking-food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bff Traditional Thanksgiving Turkey</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bff-traditional-thanksgiving-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bff-traditional-thanksgiving-turkey/</guid>
      <description>The game Cooking a turkey with mom will teach you how to properly process a bird. In it, you will learn what needs to be done in order to end up with a delicious turkey. Detailed instructions await you, which includes a large number of steps, starting from buying a bird in a store. Just follow the prompts of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boyfriend Spell Factory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/boyfriend-spell-factory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/boyfriend-spell-factory/</guid>
      <description>In the process of the game for girls Cooking a Potion for the Prince, you can perfectly train your memory. For a limited time, you are invited to prepare three potions. For five seconds, the necessary ingredients will be shown on the screen, and then you will need to place them in the flask.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olivias Magic Potion Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/olivias-magic-potion-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/olivias-magic-potion-shop/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game, the Witch is preparing a potion, you will see Gulia, a student of the school of monsters. She decided to make a cocktail according to a secret recipe. And you are invited to know this very recipe. Throw the ball into the proposed design so that it collects as many fruits and other ingredients as possible during the flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pie Realife Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pie-realife-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pie-realife-cooking/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to make ice cream, but not in the usual way. Control a girl holding a waffle cup in her hand to catch falling ice cream balls and ice cream decorations. Try to move in such a way that nothing falls on the floor. For successful actions you will receive points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Soup Kitchen</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-soup-kitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-soup-kitchen/</guid>
      <description>The Soup Cooking game takes you to a virtual kitchen where an experienced chef, Sarah, is already waiting. She has no problem teaching you how to make a great lentil soup. Just follow Sarah&amp;rsquo;s instructions and do whatever you need with the provided ingredients. The faster you complete the task, the more reward points you get. The most detailed tips will constantly be displayed on the screen, which will allow you not to get confused in the culinary process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
