<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>spongebob adventure on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/spongebob-adventure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in spongebob adventure on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/spongebob-adventure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nick Surfs Up</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/nick-surfs-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/nick-surfs-up/</guid>
      <description>SpongeBob decided to learn how to surf and turned to the great surfer Jack Kahuna for help. But first, the yellow baby needs to harmonize his mind and the spirit of the sea. Help Bob learn the intricacies of the science of surfing and then demonstrate his skills in conquering the waves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nickelodeon Omg Zombies!</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/nickelodeon-omg-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/nickelodeon-omg-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Before starting the game, you should watch a colorful introductory video. From it you will learn many funny legends associated with its main characters. This will be followed by a visual instruction (in Russian, by the way, language) and, finally, the game itself. As a matter of fact, this is far from a walker, but a real race with a bucket of sauce, which must be saved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spongebob Squarepants Lights Out Patrick</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/spongebob-squarepants-lights-out-patrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/spongebob-squarepants-lights-out-patrick/</guid>
      <description>In this game, SpongeBob participates in an underwater race on a slippery surface. Developing almost space speed, the character runs forward, jumps over chasms and collects hamburgers along the way. But besides that, you still need to overtake the snail (it is shown at the top of the screen on the strip). If the snail reaches the finish line first, the hamburgers won&amp;rsquo;t come in handy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpongeBob SquarePants Tracks Of Terror</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/spongebob-squarepants-tracks-of-terror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/spongebob-squarepants-tracks-of-terror/</guid>
      <description>SpongeBob and Patrick boarded a ghost ship in search of treasure. But something unexpected happened and Bob got lost. Patrick is looking for him and asks for your help. Roam the ship, collect coins and look for Bob. For protection from ghosts there is a flashlight. But use it carefully - there are not many batteries. To go to the next level, you need to collect all the coins.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
