<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pony on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/pony/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pony on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/pony/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cute Pony Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-pony-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-pony-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>There is no easier pony game for girls 8 years old than this one. It does not require anything but imagination and taste when choosing an outfit for the main character. Who will he be: a pony or a unicorn, you decide. Use the virtual buttons on the screen to change its appearance. At the end, the picture can be saved or printed. You can invent and create several different fairy tale characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equestria Girls First Day At School</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/equestria-girls-first-day-at-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/equestria-girls-first-day-at-school/</guid>
      <description>During the game Pony Equestria you will be asked to create a variety of compositions with the participation of cartoon horses. To do this, choose one location from Equestria, where the ponies will have fun, and then add various elements there: cakes, other goodies, territory decorations. Selected parts can be rotated and resized. As a result, you should get a nice picture that you can even print. If the way some object looks doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit you, then you can always delete it by clicking on the eraser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equestria Girls High School Uniform</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/equestria-girls-high-school-uniform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/equestria-girls-high-school-uniform/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to dance in the company of the heroines of the famous animated series? Then start the process of playing Pony girls from Equestria. In it, you are invited to come up with an excellent dance, which the girls will then show on stage. The game has two modes. The first option is a repetitive dance in which you have to carefully watch how the girls from Equestria dance and then correctly reproduce their movements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Pony 5</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-pony-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-pony-5/</guid>
      <description>Equestria is in danger, and you need to urgently take action to save it! To do this, help Applejack find apples while playing Pony 5. In it, you will find an analogue of the well-known thimbles: there are three covers on the table, and under one of them there is an apple. To win, you need to point to the correct cover three times in a row. If you make a mistake these three times, then the pony game, unfortunately, will end in a loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Pony Frozen</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-pony-frozen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-pony-frozen/</guid>
      <description>The heroes of the game Pony Frozen - Anna and Christoph, go in search of Elsa, a beautiful princess, who, due to a terrible curse, retired to a snowy castle somewhere in the expanses of the northern lands. Elsa has a unique gift to freeze everything around, but, unfortunately, it is very dangerous for others. Help the brave couple go through all the trials on the way, find out where the castle of the frosty princess is located and convince the heroine of Frozen to return home as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony Fly In A Fantasy World</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-fly-in-a-fantasy-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-fly-in-a-fantasy-world/</guid>
      <description>Pinkie Pie and Fluttershy are in trouble, they are put in a cage by a villain. While playing Mighty Ponies, you will need to control horses that have taken the form of superheroes and save their comrades. There are many exciting levels ahead, in each of which you need to find several comics while avoiding attacks by enemy ponies. In order to stop powerful opponents, try to shoot them with a magic charge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony game to collect the elements of harmony</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-game-to-collect-the-elements-of-harmony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-game-to-collect-the-elements-of-harmony/</guid>
      <description>According to the plot of the Pony game to collect the elements of harmony, the sorceress Gloomy Sparkle read, in the presence of her girlfriends, an ancient spell that broke the precious stones of the fragile world harmony. Now the little sorceress has to find all the pieces and restore the stones. The game Friendship is a miracle elements of harmony invites you to help her in her search. On your journey you will visit five locations, in each of which you will need to demonstrate dexterity and good reaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony song game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-song-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-song-game/</guid>
      <description>During the game Pony Song you will see all the heroines of your favorite animated series who are going to celebrate the victory over evil. On this occasion, they are going to have a dance party! Help the pony learn all the necessary moves by clicking on the objects at the moment when they merge with the template. The game has two scales: one of them displays the duration of the song, and the second displays your successful attempts and mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
