<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Baby for 6 years old on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/baby-for-6-years-old/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Baby for 6 years old on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/baby-for-6-years-old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Balls Rotate</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/balls-rotate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/balls-rotate/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to get acquainted with the amazing work of engineer Ruby Goldberg. Thanks to his design talent, Ruby created unique machines that perform very simple tasks with the help of intricate designs. In this game you have to fix one of these wonderful devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carl Transforms Truck</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/carl-transforms-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/carl-transforms-truck/</guid>
      <description>Do you like to collect pictures from many fragments? Then it&amp;rsquo;s time to start the process of playing Jigsaw puzzles for children 6 years old. On its screen you will see a huge number of confused elements that need to be connected together in the correct order. For an educational game, you only need a mouse: grab any piece with it and connect it with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinema Lovers Hidden Kiss</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cinema-lovers-hidden-kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cinema-lovers-hidden-kiss/</guid>
      <description>A couple of students hide their relationship from others. Help the lovers stay alone and kiss a little. Carefully follow the borders of the clearing that the couple has chosen, and warn the guys in those cases when curious classmates try to find out what is happening between them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cooking-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cooking-challenge/</guid>
      <description>After starting the game for two for children 6 years old, you will meet a couple of charming characters who are going on a dangerous journey. You and your friend need to go through a huge number of levels, each of which is waiting for intricate locations with lots of obstacles. Various boxes, levers, buttons will help you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Shooters 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-shooters-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-shooters-2/</guid>
      <description>The city is captured by the terrible dead, and only you can stop their invasion and free the metropolis from zombies. The specialists of the Special Forces have prepared you for the landing, and now it depends only on your abilities how successful this military operation will be. Destroy monsters with the help of firearms and clear the areas of the metropolis from nightmarish monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Fast Pixel Bullet</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-fast-pixel-bullet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-fast-pixel-bullet/</guid>
      <description>This game is a continuation of the comic dispute between the players boys and girls. Choose one of the parties to the conflict and go to the battlefield. Make your way through crowds of dangerous opponents and try to capture a precious artifact, thanks to which you can prove that you are the strongest player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Miner Bros</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gold-miner-bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gold-miner-bros/</guid>
      <description>A famous gold miner discovered a small mine with huge deposits of the precious metal. He goes out to mine gold and invites you to join him. The old mine is fraught with a lot of dangers, in the tunnels through which your path will pass, collapses constantly occur. Try to use the special hook to pull out the gold nuggets before the tunnel collapses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidjigs Game Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hidjigs-game-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hidjigs-game-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to this toy, you will have the opportunity to prepare a greeting card that you can give to your friends for the New Year. To get started, choose an original story from a special book. After you decide on the layout, start coloring the black and white card. Try and make the best greeting card for your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highway Bike Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/highway-bike-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/highway-bike-simulator/</guid>
      <description>The world motorcycle racing championship needs new heroes, and one of the teams decided to invite you as a pilot of a new bike. You have to take part in 3 races of the bronze tournament. Try to win in all races of the championship and get the opportunity to move to a more prestigious class of motorcycle racing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miners Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/miners-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/miners-adventure/</guid>
      <description>The old miner was looking for a gold mine for a long time, and finally, luck smiled at him. The prospector has discovered huge reserves of the precious metal and is going to mine it. Help the lucky gold digger collect all the gold nuggets with a special hook. Hurry up, the work shift is limited and you need to earn a certain amount of money before it ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paw Patrol Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/paw-patrol-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/paw-patrol-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>All drawing lovers will enjoy the process of the game for children Coloring for 6 years. In it, you need to work on the image of a strongman lifting a barbell. All available colors are displayed at the bottom of the screen, and you can select any of them, and then click on the piece of the picture you want to color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Gun Apocalypse 6</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-gun-apocalypse-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-gun-apocalypse-6/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you become a recruit for a special forces unit and go to the training ground in order to prepare for combat missions. Follow the instructor&amp;rsquo;s recommendations, try out your new weapons in training battles and learn how to throw grenades correctly. Complete all the tasks offered to you by the leadership, and prepare for action in combat conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-memory/</guid>
      <description>Logic games for kids 6 years old will make you rack your brains. On the screen you will see a large number of cards with images of different cars. Try to remove them all from the field, gradually removing paired pictures from the edge of the layout. A great game that develops thinking, for everyone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safari Chef</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/safari-chef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/safari-chef/</guid>
      <description>The famous chef Matthew deservedly won the championship of masters of culinary arts and received a gold medal. He invites you to be his assistant. Make it so that as many as possible of the restaurant where you work taste unique dishes from the recipes of the famous chef.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xmas Catcher</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/xmas-catcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/xmas-catcher/</guid>
      <description>A young married couple had a very strong fight, and the angry girl decided to throw all her husband&amp;rsquo;s things from the second floor. Help the unfortunate man to save everything that the beauty throws from above. With the help of a pillow, try to catch falling objects and put them in a small box, which is located on the right side of the playing field.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
