<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Runners on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/runners/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Runners on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/runners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angry Gran Run Xmas Village</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/angry-gran-run-xmas-village/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/angry-gran-run-xmas-village/</guid>
      <description>crazy grandma</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angry Gran Run: Turkey</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/angry-gran-run-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/angry-gran-run-turkey/</guid>
      <description>Angry grandma escapes from prison</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bear Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bear-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bear-run/</guid>
      <description>Considering that the main character of the game is an elephant, it is very difficult to call the process runners. But that&amp;rsquo;s not the point. The goal of the game is to go as far as possible and score as many points as possible. By the way, you can arrange a competition in this with friends. Instructions can be viewed before starting. But if in a nutshell, then jump over the pits and collect bananas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Alien Dog</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-alien-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-alien-dog/</guid>
      <description>If you like horror movies even a little, then you will like this toy too. The main character in it is a rabbit who got lost on a dark night in a dark forest. But the eared has a flashlight. Use it to blind the monsters. And they won&amp;rsquo;t be slow to show up, so be ready to run. Along the way, you still need to jump over all sorts of obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Roll 3d</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-roll-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-roll-3d/</guid>
      <description>Runners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Floor Is Lava Runner</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/floor-is-lava-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/floor-is-lava-runner/</guid>
      <description>This game has very attractive graphics. As for the plot, it is extremely simple. All you need is to run forward, jump over fences, slide under barriers and, of course, kill enemies by jumping on them from above. Well, you should not forget about collecting bonuses. And before the start there will be a short but interesting introductory video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forest Runner</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/forest-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/forest-runner/</guid>
      <description>The Running Boy game will help you escape from everyday problems, forget about bad grades at school and the upcoming parent-teacher meeting. And all thanks to its dynamism and cool graphics. So, in the game you will control a boy (third person view), who runs through the streets and collects coins. Along the way, you have to overcome various obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freddys Escape House</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/freddys-escape-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/freddys-escape-house/</guid>
      <description>At the very beginning, you can register on the official website and then take part in the online multiplayer game. But you can also play as a guest. In this case, it is possible to compete with a friend who will control the second game character from the same keyboard as you. The point is to run with obstacles. Side view. You have to run through the forest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Run with a crazy old lady</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-run-with-a-crazy-old-lady/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-run-with-a-crazy-old-lady/</guid>
      <description>The main character of this game is a mischievous old woman who escaped from a madhouse. This is where you will be in control. This is not difficult, but it will require a good reaction and attention. The point is to run as far as possible. Points are scored for knocked down pedestrians. You can play in turns with friends, competing in the set of points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Running Fred - parkour</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-running-fred---parkour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-running-fred---parkour/</guid>
      <description>Do you feel an acute lack of adrenaline in a series of dull everyday life? Running Fred will make up for the lack of this miraculous substance in your body. This time the restless boy decided to do parkour on the roofs of the skyscrapers of the virtual metropolis. Your task is not to let him fall out of there before the end of the current level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Running Fred 5</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-running-fred-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-running-fred-5/</guid>
      <description>The protagonist of the game Running Fred 5 years ago was just a boy. Since then, his hobby - running around the castle from death, has turned into a professional occupation. He still rushes through the labyrinths (though not in the castle anymore) and collects treasures. The task of the user is to press the right button in time and score the maximum number of points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Running Fred in the Army</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-running-fred-in-the-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-running-fred-in-the-army/</guid>
      <description>Online action &amp;ldquo;Running Fred in the Army&amp;rdquo; will take you to the military unit. Very soon, the main character will have to go to perform a difficult task, but first you will have to undergo training. To do this, follow all the commands of the training stage. The game has three locations - camp, desert and snowy wastelands. For passing you will be given points. But be extremely careful, there are many dangers around: swamps, avalanches and quicksands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ninja Hero Runner</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ninja-hero-runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ninja-hero-runner/</guid>
      <description>Very dynamic and well drawn game. You can&amp;rsquo;t skip the intro video, but it&amp;rsquo;s short. Side view. The main character runs away from the pursuit of enemies. It is necessary to press a certain button in time (at the very beginning, the game itself will suggest which one) so that it jumps or slides. You need to reach the end of the level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Fred game for girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/running-fred-game-for-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/running-fred-game-for-girls/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful toy with a third-person view. The plot is extremely simple: the main character runs through the streets of the city and collects sweets. The more he collects them, the more points he gets into his account. In addition to sweets on the way, he encounters a lot of obstacles, as well as space aliens. You need to jump over them and slide, as well as pick up useful bonuses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Ninja</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/running-ninja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/running-ninja/</guid>
      <description>Before you is an excellent toy in all respects (graphics, animation, plot, and so on). The young ninja had to embark on a dangerous journey on his own two (see introduction). Along the way, you will have to traditionally jump and slide. But besides this, it will be necessary to fight enemies who, by the way, are armed, unlike your character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Tooth Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweet-tooth-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sweet-tooth-rush/</guid>
      <description>Funny toy. From the name it may seem that it has something to do with the cartoon about training the dragon. But it is not so. The essence of the game is as follows. Viking (that is, you) gets the task to run a certain distance. He will move on his own. Your task is to remove obstacles and collect coins. If the character hesitates, then the dragon will devour him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temple Quest</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/temple-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/temple-quest/</guid>
      <description>The Egyptian pyramids are full of mysteries and, one must understand, treasures that are guarded by dead pharaohs and their numerous servants, who, as you know, were buried with their owners and often alive. In this bright game, by the way, made in 3D, you have to control (rear and top view from a third person) either an explorer or a tomb robber who is running away from mummies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom And Jerry Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tom-and-jerry-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tom-and-jerry-run/</guid>
      <description>Catcher Tom and Jerry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Temple Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tomb-temple-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tomb-temple-run/</guid>
      <description>Some crazy Viking will run and collect coins on the go in this game. Judging by the color of the body, completely frostbitten. Even when it crashes into an obstacle, it shatters into pieces, like ice. For the collected coins, buy all sorts of stray and upgrade opportunities. The controls are simple, side view of the character. You can take turns playing with your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
