<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Baby for boys on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/baby-for-boys/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Baby for boys on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/baby-for-boys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angry Ducks</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/angry-ducks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/angry-ducks/</guid>
      <description>Children&amp;rsquo;s games for boys Balls can easily captivate for one hour and not only children. The gameplay is a kind of Tetris. Shooting multi-colored birds, you need to try to make it so that you get clusters of elements of the same color from three or more pieces. In this case, they will &amp;ldquo;burn out&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Hero</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</guid>
      <description>And here is everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite game about crazy birds who entered the battle with arrogant pigs. It is built on the principle of &amp;ldquo;from simple to complex&amp;rdquo;. At the first level, you need to launch a bird from a slingshot (Greenpeace people hang themselves out of anger), gouging the pig&amp;rsquo;s shelter along with the pig itself. At the next level, the task becomes more difficult, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santas Real Haircuts</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/santas-real-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/santas-real-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>Mario grew up and became an uncle. Now he has a big beard. Today he wants to shave and trim his mustache to please Princess Peach. Help Mario to clean up. The task is very responsible and requires an appropriate attitude from you. After all, the appearance of a virtual character will depend on the work done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soldiers Combat</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/soldiers-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/soldiers-combat/</guid>
      <description>The game is a shooting range in which targets can shoot back. It&amp;rsquo;s simple: point the sight at the enemy and fall. Infantry falls down on two hits, so don&amp;rsquo;t try to headshot. But there is also an important task. For example, on the first level, you need to shoot down two helicopters. Ammunition is limited, but sometimes ammo and first-aid kits fall from the sky. Shoot down boxes and get bonuses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
