<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cool on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/cool/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cool on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/cool/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Cool Ninja Fruit Mission</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cool-ninja-fruit-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cool-ninja-fruit-mission/</guid>
      <description>The goal of this game is as simple as possible - you need to cut as many fruits that appear on the screen as possible. Move the mouse across the screen so as to be able to hit the fetus. Sometimes bombs will come across, they cannot be touched, otherwise an explosion will occur. Any three unsuccessful actions will lead you to a loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Cool Turns</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cool-turns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-cool-turns/</guid>
      <description>The game Cool Turns invites you to take part in a fast race. It is necessary to control the machine, which is created from the Lego constructor. Move along the track, overtaking rivals and collecting precious coins. You need to come to the finish line first to become a real winner of the virtual race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gone Fishing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gone-fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gone-fishing/</guid>
      <description>Go fishing with a funny panda armed with a special fishing rod that sucks up fish. Take her to the river inhabitants and catch them to get money for it. Sometimes the device will fill up and then you need to clean it so that you can continue the exciting fishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorbike Puzzle Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/motorbike-puzzle-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/motorbike-puzzle-challenge/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have the opportunity to take part in the competitions of the best motorcycle racers on the planet. The goal is to reach the finish line as quickly as possible and move on to the next level. All that is required of you is to correctly use the arrow keys on the keyboard to control the motorcycle. During the race, collect power-ups that increase your speed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
