<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fights for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/fights-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fights for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/fights-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Death Fight</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/death-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/death-fight/</guid>
      <description>According to the terms of the Fighting for two with weapons game, you have to defend yourself from hooligans on the streets of the city. As you probably already guessed, you have a knife for this purpose. However, the enemy is armed no worse. In order to defeat him in a fight, you need to be very dexterous and resourceful. Constantly move around the screen and try not to let the bully get too close.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickman Fighter Epic Battles</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-fighter-epic-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stickman-fighter-epic-battles/</guid>
      <description>Great fights are held in the backyard of the virtual bar. You can take part in them and earn some money. Your character is well trained and quite fluent in boxing techniques. But the fights are coming without restrictions and rules, you can fight both with your hands and with your feet. Try your best to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Fight</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/street-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/street-fight/</guid>
      <description>Dozens of characters are offered to you to choose from to participate in the fighting tournament. While you go through levels of varying difficulty, previously hidden fighters will open. They differ from each other in speed, strength, an arsenal of specific techniques and skills. The game allows you to choose different modes, each of which has its own rules.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
