<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Equestria girls on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/equestria-girls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Equestria girls on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/equestria-girls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Friendship is magic game - create your rock girl Equestria</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/friendship-is-magic-game---create-your-rock-girl-equestria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/friendship-is-magic-game---create-your-rock-girl-equestria/</guid>
      <description>After launching this game, you will be asked to try on the image of a girl from Equestria who plays in a musical group. Upload your photo and then create an image using various details. After that, you will need to fill out a short questionnaire with interesting questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Equestria Girls fight for the crown 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-equestria-girls-fight-for-the-crown-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-equestria-girls-fight-for-the-crown-2/</guid>
      <description>In the game Equestria Girls Fight for the Crown 2 you have to help the cartoon characters defeat their rivals at the final concert. To do this, you need to choose the same musical instruments that rivals demonstrate. The game consists of a large number of levels, and each of them will be given a certain number of tasks. For the correct answer you will get a point, if you indicate the instrument incorrectly, the point will go to your opponent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Friendship is a miracle Archery girls Equestria</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-friendship-is-a-miracle-archery-girls-equestria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-friendship-is-a-miracle-archery-girls-equestria/</guid>
      <description>During this game you will learn how to shoot a bow. Choose one of four Equestria girls to play as. On the screen you will see three targets, and in each round you need to shoot at one of them. Your task is to apply your accuracy and knock out as many points as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Friendship is Magic Repeat Equestria Girl&#39;s Melody</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-friendship-is-magic-repeat-equestria-girls-melody/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-friendship-is-magic-repeat-equestria-girls-melody/</guid>
      <description>Train your memory and attentiveness with the musical group of girls from Equestria. Their group will be displayed on the screen, and some girls will make notes. You just need to memorize the sequence of sounds, and then play it back. For the correct answer you will receive bonus points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Legends of Equestria</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-legends-of-equestria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-legends-of-equestria/</guid>
      <description>The game Legends of Equestria will take you to the magical school of Canterlot, where the heroines of the animated series study. To begin with, it is proposed to get to know the girls who gathered in the large hall before the start of the concert. Click on any heroine, and she will ask you a question, which is accompanied by three possible answers. Choose the one that seems the most suitable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
