<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For children 2 years old on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-2-years-old/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For children 2 years old on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-2-years-old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel New Year Party</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-hazel-new-year-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-hazel-new-year-party/</guid>
      <description>Today is the holy evening before Christmas. Baby Hazel is looking forward to this holiday, because the girl knows that there will be surprises and guests. You, as always, will help the heroine - just do whatever Hazel asks you to do. First, help wrap the gifts and put them on the Christmas tree. Then put on a smart dress and get ready to welcome guests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Animal Shapes</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-animal-shapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-animal-shapes/</guid>
      <description>Any game for a 2 year old child is, first of all, entertainment associated with learning or acquiring any skills. So today, together with Dasha, you will go to visit her grandmother, in the village. The girl always helps the old woman with the housework, and this time she can choose any of the premises on the farm and get to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Pony Caretaker</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-pony-caretaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-pony-caretaker/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you can make all your fantasies about your favorite horse come true. Today you will create hairstyles, but not for a girl, but for a cute pony. Choose a new color for her mane, braid it and decorate it with bows. In addition, do not forget to pick up colored reins and a few stylish accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Soldier Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-soldier-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-soldier-memory/</guid>
      <description>Mindfulness game. In front of you are five multi-colored light bulbs that light up alternately. You have to remember where the flashes were and repeat them one after the other in the correct sequence. There are no time limits in the game, so you have a lot of chances to win. But keep in mind, with each new level the game becomes more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roller Splat</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/roller-splat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/roller-splat/</guid>
      <description>Puzzles train the brain in an easy, fun and relaxed way, which is extremely important. Your goal in this game is to complete as many different tasks as possible. For example: put the correct time on the clock, write down a combination of numbers from memory, win the game &amp;ldquo;Rock, paper, scissors&amp;rdquo;, etc. And all this in only two minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild Memory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wild-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wild-memory/</guid>
      <description>This game will help the child in the development of spatial thinking and memory. On a small screen, you will be given some geometric shapes and given a few seconds to memorize them. Then on the board you must repeat their exact outlines and location in relation to the axes. You can draw with the mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
