<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>horror on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/horror/</link>
    <description>Recent content in horror on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/horror/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned Forest House</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/abandoned-forest-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/abandoned-forest-house/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to wander around the old house, completing various tasks. But first you need to find some useful items that you will need to solve puzzles. It can be a key, an old lamp, or an ordinary hamburger. And be careful, there are many traps and hidden places in the house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Zombie Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/funny-zombie-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/funny-zombie-shooter/</guid>
      <description>Get behind the wheel of a car and start your journey through a strange world, where knights dressed in iron armor will lie in wait for you at every step. They are even ready to die under the wheels, just to prevent you from reaching the end of the level. Crush everyone you meet on the way, because you need to somehow move in order to complete the mission in the minimum time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of Roses</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/garden-of-roses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/garden-of-roses/</guid>
      <description>The events of the 3D horror game are developing in a dark dungeon. You woke up on death row, and you need to get out of this little pleasant place as soon as possible. First, try to find a torch and light it. Then carefully inspect every corner of the room and listen to the clues left unknown, otherwise you risk never finding a way out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost City</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ghost-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ghost-city/</guid>
      <description>Your only goal in this game is to get to the helipad in as little time as possible. In the garage, you will find an old Volkswagen Beetle that you will crush zombies on. Money is dropped for each killed monster, they can be spent on upgrading a brave car. Get to the helicopter and leave this dangerous place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of Celestina</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/house-of-celestina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/house-of-celestina/</guid>
      <description>The Dispatcher Horror game is a cool first-person walker. Mankind has opened the way to the depths of space. The first daredevils went in search of an unknown mind, but he found people earlier. The action of the horror game takes place in the near future on the spaceship Dispatcher, whose crew, as a result of an accident, was trapped in a trap with alien monsters. The few surviving employees have been infected and are now also a danger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infected Wasteland</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/infected-wasteland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/infected-wasteland/</guid>
      <description>The goal of the game is to use the mouse to move a small blue square through the yellow labyrinth without touching the walls. As soon as you get to the red zones, click on it and you will be transferred to the next level of the game. But then the route will be even more confusing and narrow. The game is short and has only three levels. Once you pass them all, there will be a surprise waiting for you at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knife Hit Horror</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/knife-hit-horror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/knife-hit-horror/</guid>
      <description>A huge crowd of the resurrected dead is moving towards the city. It is up to you to save its inhabitants from terrible zombies. Quickly start this difficult mission, try to survive and destroy all the monsters. Set up towers with automatic guns, launch airstrikes - do whatever comes to mind, but don&amp;rsquo;t let the zombies into the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama 4 Player Parkour</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-4-player-parkour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-4-player-parkour/</guid>
      <description>A little boy has a terrible dream. In it, he wakes up and wanders through some ruins, over which terrible pictures appear, and somewhere in the distance a heartbreaking story sounds. Your task is to lead the boy to an imaginary door that will lead him out of this nightmare. The game is a 2D platformer, and when you get to the edge of the level, you enter a new reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Horror Story</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/office-horror-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/office-horror-story/</guid>
      <description>The events that take place during the game Horror 2015 take place in an abandoned old house. You have to get into the building late at night, find twenty bags of money and escape. But problems, as always, arise suddenly, as the house may not have guards or surveillance cameras, but it is full of ghosts that kill everyone indiscriminately. The idea of ​​Horror 2015 is to explore every corner of the building, collecting finds while trying to avoid strange situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pirates vs Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pirates-vs-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pirates-vs-zombies/</guid>
      <description>While playing Horror 2, you have to fight with square-headed zombies that have filled all the surroundings. They attack in crowds, so do not stand still, but constantly move, choosing a convenient position for shooting. Try to hit the red barrels - they explode and destroy all the dead that are nearby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portal of Doom: Undead Rising</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/portal-of-doom-undead-rising/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/portal-of-doom-undead-rising/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever had scary dreams? Another nightmarish night is coming soon, but not for you. Residents of a large house will be its victims, and you will get the role of a monster that frightens them. You will need to manage monsters and ghosts, create a real poltergeist and move things. The goal is to make the residents of this house scared to death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Blockfare Of Future</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-blockfare-of-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-blockfare-of-future/</guid>
      <description>In the game you will be busy looking for a way out of a large castle consisting of many rooms. Along the way, you will meet different items, among which there are those that must be collected. Below is a panel on which the finds are placed. To apply the found object, just click on it on this panel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
