<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Racing for girls on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/racing-for-girls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Racing for girls on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/racing-for-girls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Cardboard Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-cardboard-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-cardboard-racing/</guid>
      <description>The famous cartoon character Tsypa decided to take up motorsport, bought himself a sports car and went on a trip. Help the little chicken get back home by overcoming all the obstacles that await him on the way. Thanks to your help, the cute racer will have a great time, and at the same time he will test his sports car for strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Madness</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-madness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-madness/</guid>
      <description>Kids Games Racing games for girls are very popular. In this one, you will go on a bike ride together with the famous traveler Dasha. Help the baby get to the end point of the journey. Watch the road carefully and warn the girl about steep ascents and descents. Thanks to your help, Dasha will not only enjoy the walk, but will quickly get home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Fury</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/road-fury/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/road-fury/</guid>
      <description>Angry Berds decided to organize a wild race - a tournament that will reveal the fastest bird. Decide on behalf of whom you will play, and join the fight for the honorary title. The competition is divided into a huge number of stages, each of which you need to win. Thanks to your efforts, the selected bird will definitely become a champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uphill Rush 7 Waterpark</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/uphill-rush-7-waterpark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/uphill-rush-7-waterpark/</guid>
      <description>During Water Racing game for girls you will try your hand at driving a jet ski. Collect the maximum number of points in your trip.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
