<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tamagotchi on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/tamagotchi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tamagotchi on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/tamagotchi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kitty Hospital Recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kitty-hospital-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kitty-hospital-recovery/</guid>
      <description>The Tamagotchi game is designed for those who want to have a pet, but do not know how to handle it. At the very beginning, the user is prompted to choose who he will take care of: a kitten or a puppy. Then you can start the game itself. At the disposal of the player will be a modern home - a private house. The pet can wander both inside and outside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Cat Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-cat-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-cat-doctor/</guid>
      <description>Tigers are big and strong animals. But until they grow up, they need care. So your task is to provide the tiger cub with everything it needs. In the upper left corner of the screen are images of various objects. For example, milk bottles. By clicking on it, you will be taken to another screen, where you will need to hold down the mouse button on the animal so that the bar on top is filled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magical Pony Caring</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/magical-pony-caring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/magical-pony-caring/</guid>
      <description>The game was originally designed for girls, judging by the characters. However, it may be of interest to gamers of any gender and age. The goal is to keep the vital signs of the main characters (looking at the wall behind the pet) at a high level in the allotted time. There are ten of them in total, so for a successful passage you will have to sweat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moana Cute Zoo</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/moana-cute-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/moana-cute-zoo/</guid>
      <description>The first thing that pleases, even when loading, is the game interface in Russian. And this means that there will be no problems with understanding the instructions. So, a toy is a kind of training for those who decide to get a pet. So that users are imbued with how many problems await them. And the execution is quite serious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pet Salon Kitty Care</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pet-salon-kitty-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pet-salon-kitty-care/</guid>
      <description>Like all other Tamagotchi games, this one involves taking care of pets. First, the user needs to choose a cat. The whole process of passing comes down to meeting the needs of the fluffy. Pay attention to the top of the screen: three sets of symbols with stripes. Try to make sure that the stripes do not decrease to zero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webimon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/webimon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/webimon/</guid>
      <description>Hamster is a small animal. But he still needs a lot of attention. You can verify this by the example of the character of the game. He has a whole bunch of needs, which are displayed on the panel at the bottom of the screen. Near each of them there is an indicator strip. Don&amp;rsquo;t let it drop to zero. The instructions are clear and without translation, if you think a little.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
