<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Action games on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/action-games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Action games on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/action-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Pixel Adventure Vol</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/a-pixel-adventure-vol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/a-pixel-adventure-vol/</guid>
      <description>After starting the Castle Adventure game, you will meet a mouse that lives in the royal palace. Your task is to help her get from point A to point B, avoiding obstacles and avoiding all-seeing servants. If you suddenly get caught, you will have to go through the current level again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ariel Princess Vs Mermaid</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ariel-princess-vs-mermaid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ariel-princess-vs-mermaid/</guid>
      <description>A cute mermaid decided to see what is on the other side of the world and went on a long but exciting journey. On the way, she will meet different marine life, which will both help her and hinder her. You should help the queen of the seas overcome all obstacles, collect magical notes and find the keys to mysterious chests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eg Little Strawberry</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-little-strawberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-little-strawberry/</guid>
      <description>In this game you are going to the fairytale farm of cute Strawberry. Every day the girl spends in caring for animals and caring for the harvest. Sometimes she needs help. This time, for example, chickens escaped from the aviary. Help the heroine of the game to collect all the fugitives by catching them with the help of a magic lasso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Action Zombie</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-action-zombie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-action-zombie/</guid>
      <description>Not a very colorful game and without any detailed plot. Everything is very simple. You were alone in a car in the middle of the highway. The transport is broken, and there are zombies on all sides. Shoot them and throw grenades at them. If they get to you, it&amp;rsquo;s game over. Spare no cartridges and spin in all directions. But grenades are tough. View from above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Prototype 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-prototype-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-prototype-2/</guid>
      <description>A very unusual first-person shooter game. She has original graphics without frills, but cool special effects and tasks. At the first level, you need to kill a certain number of opponents. Ammunition is limited. The next level will begin even when you kill the enemies at the cost of your life. At the second stage, the task becomes more difficult and you have to run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goldblade</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldblade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/goldblade/</guid>
      <description>The plot of the adventure game Alice knows what to do is based on the well-known fairy tale about a girl who got into a strange parallel world. You are invited to help the heroine cope with all local difficulties and return home. Move around locations avoiding enemies. Of course, you can just jump on the enemy to destroy him. For this, Alice will receive bonus points. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect coins that are just in the air or hidden in blocks with question marks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gravity Falls Li’l Gideon Shrinks Back</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gravity-falls-lil-gideon-shrinks-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gravity-falls-lil-gideon-shrinks-back/</guid>
      <description>The process of playing the Gravity Falls walker is dedicated to the famous mystical animated series, which has gained a large number of fans among both children and adults. Dipper and Mabel found another strange diary in Uncle Stan&amp;rsquo;s cabin, after which they ended up in an equally strange place. How to get out of here? Only you can help the twins! Start the action game for two right now, so as not to bring even more problems to the characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Cat Parkour</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-cat-parkour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-cat-parkour/</guid>
      <description>During the adventure Cats Warriors you are invited to help a cat in love. He wants to get to his kitty. Mustachioed Romeo has a long way to go, on which various dangers await him: puddles, dogs, evil rivals &amp;hellip; Use the items at hand to eliminate problems and clear the way for the character in love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Heart Flying</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-heart-flying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-heart-flying/</guid>
      <description>Tim worked on a farm, and Anna organized her own business in the heart of a huge metropolis. Once the girl went out of town to relax and had an accident. It was then that the guys met for the first time and fell in love at first sight. Help the couple in love pass all the tests and create their own family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Mermaid Mystery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-mermaid-mystery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-mermaid-mystery/</guid>
      <description>A cute little mermaid fell in love with a human prince. By all means, she decided to turn into a girl and turned to the underwater witch. In order for the witch&amp;rsquo;s spell to work, the little mermaid must find magical notes at the bottom of the ocean. Help the brave heroine of the game complete the task of the insidious witch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paw Patrol Smash</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/paw-patrol-smash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/paw-patrol-smash/</guid>
      <description>While playing Paw Patrol, you have to control a superhero dog. He needs to free his people from the cats who seized power by deceit. Move around the locations trying to collect as much dog food as possible. A certain number of packages of the specified color will give you superpowers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopping Cart Hero HD</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/shopping-cart-hero-hd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/shopping-cart-hero-hd/</guid>
      <description>The young emperor Kuzco received a letter from his beloved Malina. He went to the laboratory of the insidious Izma to meet the girl there. Unfortunately, the naive romantic fell into a trap and you must help him get out of the trap. Control the movements of the emperor&amp;rsquo;s cart and try to get away from the chase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spongebob Squarepants Spongemania</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/spongebob-squarepants-spongemania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/spongebob-squarepants-spongemania/</guid>
      <description>The mermaid princess from the pink kingdom went on a small expedition, and when she returned to her castle, she discovered that an evil sorceress had turned all the inhabitants of her kingdom into stone statues. Help the heroine of the game to find and free 4 mermaid princesses who have colored pearls that can dispel the magic of the insidious witch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fishercat Online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-fishercat-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-fishercat-online/</guid>
      <description>During the game Adventure Cats you will control a funny kitten traveling through the fairy kingdom. Help him overcome all the obstacles that will meet on the way. Sometimes it will be necessary to think carefully about actions in order to be able to move on. Otherwise you&amp;rsquo;ll be stuck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Ball Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/yellow-ball-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/yellow-ball-adventure/</guid>
      <description>The process of playing Balls walker includes the passage of a huge number of levels, each of which is an original location. Your task is to control the blue ball and help it get to the star sign. Try to collect bonus balls along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
