<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About the war with the Germans on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/about-the-war-with-the-germans/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About the war with the Germans on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/about-the-war-with-the-germans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Combat Blocky Strike</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-combat-blocky-strike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-combat-blocky-strike/</guid>
      <description>During the game Lego war against the Germans, you have to become a military leader who is tasked with organizing the offensive of the allied troops that have landed in Western Europe, occupied by the Nazi troops. Try to repel your opponent&amp;rsquo;s attacks, build up enough strength and defeat enemy units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Combat</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/heavy-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/heavy-combat/</guid>
      <description>Hitler&amp;rsquo;s troops captured a small island in the Atlantic Ocean. As one of the best special forces warriors, you go there and must free the island from the invaders. Destroy enemy soldiers, earn gold coins and improve your combat performance to face the invader commander in the last deadly battle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insurgents</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/insurgents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/insurgents/</guid>
      <description>The developers of this game invite you and your best friend to a huge military training ground. It is on it that you must demonstrate your warrior talents and find out in a bloody duel which of you is the best fighter. Watch your opponent&amp;rsquo;s movements carefully and try to destroy him as quickly as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partisans</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/partisans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/partisans/</guid>
      <description>While playing War Shooters 1941 1945 you get to know one of the experienced scouts who is ordered to get into the enemy&amp;rsquo;s secret base. Go on a mission together with a brave warrior. Try to go through all the stages of this exciting shooting game 1943 war against the Germans, destroy the maximum number of enemy soldiers and destroy the ammunition depots. Be careful and hide from the eyes of vigilant guards until the last moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WWII Warzone</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wwii-warzone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wwii-warzone/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you become a pilot of a legendary squadron that fought against the Nazi troops all over Europe. You have to take part in some of the most famous battles in the sky over a huge continent. On your fighter you must destroy the maximum number of enemy aircraft in each of the battles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
