<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>5 nights with freddy on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/5-nights-with-freddy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 5 nights with freddy on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/5-nights-with-freddy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game 5 nights</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights/</guid>
      <description>In front of you is the famous game 5 Nights at Freddy&amp;rsquo;s. It belongs to the horror survival genre and has a very original performance. Your hero is a security guard of an entertainment center and a pizzeria. The task is to be on duty for five night shifts and not become a victim of animatronic robots. Throughout the game, the character sits in the office and watches the premises with the help of video cameras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game 5 Nights at Freddy&#39;s 1 Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-1-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-1-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>Before you is a children&amp;rsquo;s version of the game (monsters are not so scary) about the adventures of a security guard in a night eatery. He is not as scary as all the others, but no less difficult. It is necessary to monitor the rooms with surveillance cameras. The doors can be closed, but in this position their batteries are discharged. No power - the doors are open. You can hide in a mask, but also temporarily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game 5 Nights at Freddy&#39;s 2 Catcher</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-2-catcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-2-catcher/</guid>
      <description>This game looks not at all scary and even somehow small. In the sense that all the details and characters in it are small. Side view. Keyboard control. Your hero is a little golden teddy bear. He needs to find and enter all the codes for the lock that locks the elevator doors. So, passing through all the rooms, look for clues. The elevator, of course, is located at the farthest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game 5 Nights at Freddy&#39;s 2 Scary Stories</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-2-scary-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-2-scary-stories/</guid>
      <description>In some way, in front of you is a parody or banter on the game about Freddie the bear. At first glance, everything is exactly the same: you are a night guard, you sit in a closet and monitor the premises through security cameras. But instead of crazy monsters, there are soft toys here. You can hide from their embrace under a mask. The goal is to last all night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game 5 Nights at Freddy&#39;s 3 - Dungeon</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-3---dungeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-3---dungeon/</guid>
      <description>Before you is a very interesting interpretation of the famous horror about 5 nights with Freddie. A kind of cross between this game and Minecraft. View, as before, from the first person. You are sitting in a mine, and 4 tunnels stretch ahead. Watch the torches in them so that they do not go out, and sometimes drive away the monsters. You also need to turn on the fan in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game 5 Nights at Freddy&#39;s 3 - Terrible Candy</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-3---terrible-candy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-3---terrible-candy/</guid>
      <description>Here is a continuation of the terrible game Five Nights at Freddy&amp;rsquo;s, created by fans. And the main negative character in it is a cat doll named Candy. He loves the little man, and your hero, the night watchman, is a very tasty dish. You can follow him with the help of TV cameras and take measures in time so that the creature does not get closer. Stay 5 nights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game 5 Nights at Freddy&#39;s 4 Mystery Adventures</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-4-mystery-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-4-mystery-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Today you have to control a cartoon teddy bear who went on a journey and wandered into a strange house. Now he needs to get out of here, solving puzzles along the way. Help the bear cope with all the tasks and find a way to leave the terrible place. Use arrow keys to control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game 5 Nights at Freddy&#39;s 4 Spooky House</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-4-spooky-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-4-spooky-house/</guid>
      <description>No luck for that security guard who dares to get a job at Freddy&amp;rsquo;s Pizzeria - the most famous and most terrible place in the city. This cafe was once popular until a few children entered and disappeared. At night, really scary things happen in the corridors of a pizzeria, and you have to figure out what&amp;rsquo;s the matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game 5 Nights at Freddy&#39;s 4 Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-4-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-4-survival/</guid>
      <description>It is worth starting the game only if you have strong nerves and are not afraid to shake them. You have to defend yourself from bloodthirsty monsters, armed only with a powerful flashlight. It is necessary to examine all the dark corners of the room and destroy the attacking monsters. Watch out, don&amp;rsquo;t let them take you by surprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game 5 Nights at Freddy&#39;s Bear 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-bear-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-5-nights-at-freddys-bear-2/</guid>
      <description>5 Nights at Freddy&amp;rsquo;s Bear 2 is the sequel to the very popular survival horror game. As in the first part, the gamer will have to control the night guard of the pizzeria, where animatronics roam. This time, you can save yourself from them not only by watching through the cameras, but also with the help of a flashlight and a Freddy bear mask. Playing at 5 nights is also scary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Bear Freddy 1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-bear-freddy-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-bear-freddy-1/</guid>
      <description>Imagine that you had to get a job as a security guard in a hotel. However, already on the first watch, it became clear that something strange was happening in the building, and monsters from nightmares - animatronic robots - were hiding around every corner. Your task, controlling only the mouse, is to monitor all the corridors of the hotel and, at the slightest danger, abruptly lock the doors. Fortunately, there are security cameras on the floors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Bear Freddy 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-bear-freddy-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-bear-freddy-2/</guid>
      <description>Yes, the job of a night watchman can be difficult. Especially if you work in a cafe with crazy killer dolls. Whoever wants to make sure of this, let him launch the game as soon as possible. But it is worth stocking up on sedatives. The atmosphere is still there! First-person view. Your character doesn&amp;rsquo;t actually move. Follow the monsters through the cameras and take action in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Garis mod 3d</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-garis-mod-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-garis-mod-3d/</guid>
      <description>Tired of playing Garis mod 3d? No problem! Try for a change to have some fun with the Freddy bear. You will know what fear and horror are. In the story, you will again be a night guard in an old pizzeria. All the same dolls that come to life at night live there (it is strange that they have not been thrown away yet). Watch the monsters through the cameras, cut off their air and survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Garis mod 5 nights at Freddy&#39;s 5</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-garis-mod-5-nights-at-freddys-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-garis-mod-5-nights-at-freddys-5/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third part of the adventures of the night guard of the pizzeria, in which Freddy bear cub lives! Stock up on diapers and start playing. This time the scene has changed a bit. You are not sitting in a cramped closet, not in a dull nook, but in a spacious room. You will have to fight the creatures with the help of not only light, but also imitation of sounds, as well as a ventilation system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
