<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jurassic Park on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/jurassic-park/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jurassic Park on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/jurassic-park/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dino Island Rampage</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-island-rampage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-island-rampage/</guid>
      <description>Huge reptiles, created by the genius of unknown scientists, escaped from a secret scientific center. Together with two brave warriors, you need to make your way to the radio station, which will allow the laboratory workers to contact the leadership. Try to get to the place as quickly as possible, destroying the maximum number of dinosaurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dino Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-survival/</guid>
      <description>In this game you meet a small tribe of cute monsters who need your help. From the details suggested by the developers of the toy, try to create a shelter that can protect cute game characters from nightmarish monsters who dream of feasting on these careless rounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dino Transport</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-transport/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-transport/</guid>
      <description>According to the plot of this toy, you find yourself on an island completely destroyed by huge dinosaurs. You need to go around all the local scientific stations and help the scientists. Be careful, there are a lot of obstacles on the way. Try to overcome the track as quickly as possible, because the station workers need your help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jurassic Dino Hunting</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jurassic-dino-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jurassic-dino-hunting/</guid>
      <description>The Jurassic Park game turns you into an ancient reptile recreated in the laboratories of a fantastic science center. You need to escape from the test tube and break away from the pursuers. Try to run as far as possible across the park and collect the maximum number of bonus coins. It is thanks to them that you can increase your speed and overcome the maximum possible distance. Be careful, along the way there is a chance to meet special badges that you need to mutate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>L.A. REX</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/l.a.-rex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/l.a.-rex/</guid>
      <description>The Jurassic Park 3 game invites you on a long journey into the past with the famous professor who created the time machine. Unfortunately, the invention of the hero of the game is out of order, and now you have to defend the scientific station from nightmarish monsters who dream of getting to you and your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
