<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Barboskins on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/barboskins/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Barboskins on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/barboskins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Barboskin&#39;s game Covering up traces</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/barboskins-game-covering-up-traces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/barboskins-game-covering-up-traces/</guid>
      <description>The puppies in this apartment have done something again, and therefore, covering their tracks, the Barboskins distract your attention with all sorts of puzzles. On the other hand, the fun they offer is very useful for the development of attention and memory. The point is this. Pictures are displayed for a short time. You need to remember their location and open the same ones in pairs. There are many attempts, as you can play online for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Barboskiny Words</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-barboskiny-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-barboskiny-words/</guid>
      <description>This game will be very useful for those who are just starting to learn how to write words. Although on the other hand, and people more experienced in it will be interesting. An object is shown on the screen, and at the bottom there is a line where you need to enter its name. The letters are next to each other. It is necessary to choose the appropriate ones from the proposed set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosa Barboskin game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rosa-barboskin-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rosa-barboskin-game/</guid>
      <description>Rosa fits perfectly into the scenario of Barboskin&amp;rsquo;s game, because this is not a flower, but the heroine of the cartoon of the same name. This time, the task is intended primarily for girls, since they will have to deal with dressers. The heroine is going on a date, and users are invited to prepare her for this event. First, brush her teeth: choose a paste, a brush and start this simple quest with the left mouse button pressed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
