<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Car coloring pages on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/car-coloring-pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Car coloring pages on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/car-coloring-pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Boys Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/boys-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/boys-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>In this toy you have to color the drawing of the popular Toyota Prado SUV. Using the huge palette provided by the game developers, apply paint to the image of a huge jeep. Try to turn the car in your drawing into a real supercar with the help of an electronic brush.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coloring Monster Machines</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/coloring-monster-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/coloring-monster-machines/</guid>
      <description>This game is suitable for those who dream of becoming a design engineer and creating fantastic supercars in the future. Paint one of the most beautiful sports cars of our time with a virtual brush and paints. Do not forget to print your creation on a printer or save it to your computer&amp;rsquo;s memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamborghini Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lamborghini-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lamborghini-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>An ice cream company decided to paint their cars in original colors. Representatives of the company organized a competition. The winner will receive a small reward and the opportunity to come up with a design for Volkswagen transporters. Try to create an original coloring for your car and win this competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Coloring</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-coloring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-coloring/</guid>
      <description>The animation studio invites you to take part in the creation of an animated film about dinosaur island. You will take the place of one of the animators who color the frames. Use the electronic brush to color in the picture of the tourists meeting the giant monster for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-truck-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Another client of your tuning studio asks to turn his BMW 4 into a powerful monster. Create a unique car design, come up with a new original color for it, which will give the sports car the look of a wild predator. Use the virtual brush to paint the car and don&amp;rsquo;t forget to save your work to your computer&amp;rsquo;s memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/my-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to color a frame from a new animated film showing a Lada 99 crashing into a lake. Using a color palette and an electronic brush, apply paint to the frame. Try to color the picture as quickly as possible, because the movie premiere is coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racing Cars Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/racing-cars-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/racing-cars-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you have to become the leading designer of a car tuning studio. This time you need to repaint the huge SUV of the German company Audi. Using a virtual brush, apply original paints to the car that can turn it into a real work of art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robocar Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/robocar-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/robocar-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>The famous supercar racing world champion asks you to prepare his new car for the next Grand Prix. Use the electronic brush to apply war paint to the sports car, which will bring good luck to the driver and allow him to become the most recognizable participant in the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Cars Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-cars-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-cars-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>The famous German automotive concern is preparing to present its new supercar. The management of the company offered you, as one of the best designers in the world, to color the presentation copy. Show maximum imagination and apply a unique color to the car that will delight all automotive industry specialists.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
