<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bunnies on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/bunnies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bunnies on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/bunnies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Pet Care</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-hazel-pet-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-hazel-pet-care/</guid>
      <description>After starting this exciting game, you will find yourself in a forest where funny bunnies live. You will have to manage one of these eared ones. Move around the locations, jumping over chasms and avoiding enemies so as not to lose health points. Otherwise, the bunny will die, and the game will end in a loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Chungus Bubble Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/big-chungus-bubble-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/big-chungus-bubble-shooter/</guid>
      <description>A little bunny needs to protect his possessions from a crowd of enemies, and you need to help in this. At your disposal is a firearm, use it to destroy the advancing enemies. For completing each level you will receive money that you can spend on improving your performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bunny Skater</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bunny-skater/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bunny-skater/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to control a cute bunny who goes on a long and exciting journey. Collect coins and carrots along the way to earn as many reward points as possible. Avoid abysses and other traps, otherwise you will lose game lives. And if they run out, you lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Differences Bunny</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/find-differences-bunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/find-differences-bunny/</guid>
      <description>An excellent game Hares invites you to help a cartoon character - Bugs Bunny the rabbit. He needs to get as high as possible by jumping on the platforms that appear in different places. Try to make jumps as accurately as possible so as not to fall down, and avoid birds flying past the rabbit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Bunny Logic</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/funny-bunny-logic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/funny-bunny-logic/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to work in a bar located in the forest. Bunnies constantly come here, wanting to drink delicious juice. Carefully follow the orders of visitors and fulfill them exactly, choosing the right berries and glasses. For fast and correct execution you will receive money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giant Rabbit Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/giant-rabbit-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/giant-rabbit-run/</guid>
      <description>During the game Walking Bunnies you will find yourself in a forest where many eared animals live. You have to manage one of them - a bunny warrior, who is entrusted with an important mission. You need to travel through the forest, communicate with other characters and receive tasks, and then fight with enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Bubble Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rabbit-bubble-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rabbit-bubble-shooter/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to control a funny bunny who needs to destroy enemies. It provides a large number of levels, each of them presents the original location. Move along it and attack opponents, making sure that they do not touch you. You can also play together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
