<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>House on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/house/</link>
    <description>Recent content in House on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/house/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Build houses around the world</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-build-houses-around-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-build-houses-around-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Being a builder is not so easy, and you will see it now. We urgently need to build a tower, but as high as possible. The difficulty is that each subsequent block intended for installation is constantly moving. You need to seize the moment and stop it in time. The more often you successfully place blocks, the higher the tower will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Building houses and apartments</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-building-houses-and-apartments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-building-houses-and-apartments/</guid>
      <description>During the game Build houses and apartments you have to build a multi-storey building from separate parts, installing them on top of each other with a crane. The wind will interfere with you, so try to put the blocks more evenly. The more reliably you install each subsequent structure, the more people will move into a new house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game For girls Peppa Pig builds a house</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-girls-peppa-pig-builds-a-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-for-girls-peppa-pig-builds-a-house/</guid>
      <description>During the game for girls Peppa Pig to build a house, you find yourself in a magical world created based on the cartoon series about a funny pig and her friends. This time Peppa&amp;rsquo;s family decided to build a new house for themselves. They traveled around the surroundings of the green meadow for a long time until, finally, they found a great place for arranging a family nest. Daddy Pig invited a professional builder, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House robbery game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/house-robbery-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/house-robbery-game/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever tried to play House Robbery, Burglary or any other crime related games? If not, it&amp;rsquo;s time to try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money Movers 3 Guard Duty</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/money-movers-3-guard-duty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/money-movers-3-guard-duty/</guid>
      <description>Do you like songs about the Vladimir Central, golden domes and other opuses in the same vein? Oh, then you will get real pleasure from playing Thief in the House. So, as you might have already guessed, your character will be &amp;hellip; well, draw your own conclusions. By the way, the view is from the first person, so you will have a complete identification. Your task is to clear the house and the conscience of its owners from the ballast in the form of money and jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nightmare house game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/nightmare-house-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/nightmare-house-game/</guid>
      <description>House of Nightmares is a game that can tickle your nerves, but at the same time, captivate for a very long time. The atmosphere in it is simply creepy, in the best traditions of horror: you light the way with only a lantern, the wind howls and there is no one in the strange building except &amp;hellip; However, you will still meet her. Try not to die and get out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
