<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shooting games 3d on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting-games-3d/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shooting games 3d on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting-games-3d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Archery Blast</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/archery-blast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/archery-blast/</guid>
      <description>The authors of this game offer to try their hand at a unique archery competition. You have to compete with Robin Hood himself, and it depends only on you who will raise the Golden Arrow of the best shooter of the tournament over his head. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to use the money earned from the performance to buy items that will improve your shooting efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cave War</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cave-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cave-war/</guid>
      <description>During the game Shooting 3D for boys, you meet two super agents who, by the will of fate, have united to complete a special task. KGB agent Kuryakin and CIA agent Solo take part in an operation to destroy an international criminal group that is spreading weapons and technologies capable of destroying the entire world. Choose one of the heroes of this exciting shooting game for boys and go on dangerous missions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commando Attack 1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/commando-attack-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/commando-attack-1/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to become a specialist in the fight against drug mafia. Try to destroy all the mafiosi who have settled in the base in the depths of the tropical jungle. Go through the territory of their secret hideout, look into each of the buildings and shoot all the criminals. During the battle, do not forget to reload your machine gun in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counter Battle Strike SWAT</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/counter-battle-strike-swat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/counter-battle-strike-swat/</guid>
      <description>The famous crime fighter Robocop is sent to the dungeons of one of the research laboratories, where several scientists got lost. Having descended to the lowest level of the catacombs, the Super Cop discovers a huge number of bloodthirsty mutants. Help the hero of the game to destroy the monsters and find out what happened to the scientists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counter Terrorist Strike</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/counter-terrorist-strike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/counter-terrorist-strike/</guid>
      <description>This game invites you to a huge online field where you have to fight nightmarish monsters and other players. The toy is divided into many stages, on each of which you need to repel the attacks of otherworldly creatures. Destroy monster bots, but don&amp;rsquo;t forget that you will meet real opponents ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Critical Combat Battle Royale</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/critical-combat-battle-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/critical-combat-battle-royale/</guid>
      <description>The special forces brigade in which you are serving had to go to one of the hot spots on the planet. You and your squad have been ordered to take control of an abandoned terrorist research base. When approaching the object, your group comes face to face with a huge detachment of mercenaries. Try to destroy them all and complete a deadly task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devastator Arena</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/devastator-arena/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/devastator-arena/</guid>
      <description>The fantasy world you find yourself in is filled with a huge number of bloodthirsty monsters who dream of feasting on you. Try to fight off all the attacks of evil monsters and find an ancient artifact belonging to a dead race of space conquerors in the labyrinths of a huge alien temple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Shooter 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-shooter-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/halloween-shooter-3d/</guid>
      <description>During the day of all saints, a huge army of monsters decided to take over our world. Only you can stop the monsters. From a huge cannon that shoots huge pumpkins, try to destroy all the evil spirits flying out of the crypt in an abandoned cemetery. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect the prizes that fall out of defeated opponents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hammer 2 Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hammer-2-reloaded/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hammer-2-reloaded/</guid>
      <description>A huge office for the development of children&amp;rsquo;s toys was captured by a group of terrorists. You have to go alone into a huge building and destroy the criminals. Carefully move from location to location and don&amp;rsquo;t forget to reload your weapons. After your heroic victory, the firm&amp;rsquo;s designers will surely create a toy that looks like you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost Alone: Zombie Land</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lost-alone-zombie-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lost-alone-zombie-land/</guid>
      <description>The developers of this game send you to a farm filled with a huge number of dead people. Unfortunately, you cannot run away or call someone for help. The only way to survive in this nightmarish place is to take a gun and go hunting for zombies. Show your abilities in the field of fighting evil spirits and destroy all the monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masked Shooters Single Player</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/masked-shooters-single-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/masked-shooters-single-player/</guid>
      <description>A special task force was abandoned on a tropical island. According to intelligence information, it is here that a terrorist training base is organized. Together with two of your subordinates, comb the entire island and destroy the bandits you meet. Be careful and try to save your brothers in arms from death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mob City</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mob-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mob-city/</guid>
      <description>Three professional killers decided to take some rest and took a short vacation from their &amp;ldquo;employer&amp;rdquo;. The friends went to Chicago, where they dreamed of spending time walking around nightclubs and discos. But at the entrance to the city, the car of the heroes was blown up. Choose one of the characters in the game and take revenge on the attackers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paintball Gun Pixel 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/paintball-gun-pixel-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/paintball-gun-pixel-3d/</guid>
      <description>While playing Shooting 4D, you meet a boy who loves to collect candy for Halloween. Unfortunately, his younger brother ruined his costume, and the hero of the game had to go hunting for his favorite treat with a single water gun. Walking through the streets, he accidentally wandered into the farthest part of the city, where there was an abandoned house. Going inside, the character of the game fell into another dimension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protect Zone</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/protect-zone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/protect-zone/</guid>
      <description>This game invites you to the distant future. Our planet is attacked by a huge fleet of space pirates. Their main task is to enslave mankind and pump out all the resources of the Earth. Try to fight off the attacks of the galactic invaders while your brothers in arms gather an army that can stop the hordes of aliens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stellar Shooters</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/stellar-shooters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/stellar-shooters/</guid>
      <description>In this futuristic game, you join the ranks of the united army of the Earth and become the pilot of a combat starship. Go to one of the training bases of earthlings and take a course there to prepare for battles in extreme conditions. Show all your abilities to the maximum and become a space pilot of the Earth Guard, which is just being put forward to study one of the solar systems of the galaxy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toon Off</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/toon-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/toon-off/</guid>
      <description>This shooter will appeal to all fans of the popular Minecraft game. A dynamic toy sends you to the battlefield, where it invites you to take part in online battles with other players. Gamers participating in the competition are divided into two groups. The winner is the team that destroys the most opponents in the allotted time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
