<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fast and furious on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/fast-and-furious/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fast and furious on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/fast-and-furious/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>4x4 Truck Car Hill Race 3d</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/4x4-truck-car-hill-race-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/4x4-truck-car-hill-race-3d/</guid>
      <description>A jeep is such a car that you can go on a trip on any, even the most difficult roads. And it doesn’t matter if the path is paved or there is loose sand under the wheels. The &amp;ldquo;correct&amp;rdquo; jeep will not be stopped by pits or stones on the way. Even oncoming cars are not a hindrance to him - none of them simply will survive a collision with this cool car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drift Club</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/drift-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/drift-club/</guid>
      <description>During the game Fast and Furious 1 you have to participate in survival races. True professionals know that such a ride is associated with a risk to life. And this statement is ideal for describing this game. You have to drive through the city streets, completing various tasks, in which only speed is a priority. During the Fast and the Furious 1 races, you will need to drive through the oncoming traffic lane for 1 minute or catch up with a motorcyclist in a very dense stream of cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Rider Racing Cars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-rider-racing-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-rider-racing-cars/</guid>
      <description>At your disposal is a four-wheel drive sports car, in which you participate in a rally on ice. You will have to show real driving skills to keep the car on the track and win the race. During the race, collect bonus chips that will later give you the opportunity to upgrade your car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offroad Racer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/offroad-racer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/offroad-racer/</guid>
      <description>Racing in the countryside is gaining popularity, and today you decided to try for yourself what it really is. Now you have to drive along a dirt road, overcoming the required number of laps and trying not to let your rivals overtake you. To do this, you need to ideally take turns, without flying off the track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police Stunt Cars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/police-stunt-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/police-stunt-cars/</guid>
      <description>Sitting behind the wheel of your car, you need to make every effort to get away from the police. The game consists of several levels with different race conditions. But in each of them, you must definitely pass through several checkpoints and not be caught. But remember, if you hesitate for a second, the cop cars will immediately block you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police Traffic</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/police-traffic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/police-traffic/</guid>
      <description>You have to overcome the circles of the race track for a while. The track is considered passed if it is possible to break the set record. But the competition takes place in different conditions: wet asphalt, gravel, snow and ice, and sometimes all together in one race. Only a true professional can win them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Car Driver HD</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-car-driver-hd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-car-driver-hd/</guid>
      <description>Prepare your car for a serious race. Paint it in the most threatening color so that the other participants even at the start begin to doubt whether it is worth messing with you at all. In this game, you have no way to overtake your opponent on the track. This means that you will have to jump over it by pressing the spacebar in time. Change the lane by pressing the left and right buttons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Race Takedown</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/street-race-takedown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/street-race-takedown/</guid>
      <description>Autobahns allow you to travel at very high speeds and usually run between big cities. In this case, you will have to travel along such a road. It, alas, does not have sufficient width, so you will have to carefully overtake cars moving slowly in different rows. If you allow a collision with one of them, you will lose bonus points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SuperMoto GT</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/supermoto-gt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/supermoto-gt/</guid>
      <description>Only the fastest and most famous riders participate in this motocross. Try to leave them all far behind. Pay close attention to the road, there are many sharp turns on the track. The most important thing on the track is to collect temporary acceleration bonuses. This will give you the opportunity to get ahead and be the first to cross the finish line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Drift Tour</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/world-drift-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/world-drift-tour/</guid>
      <description>According to the terms of the game Furious 7, you have to participate in underground races in high-speed cars. Enjoy driving cool cars, feel the breakneck speed by driving in different game modes. Here you will find many supercars and a large number of tracks: from the streets of Tokyo to deserted roads. Earn money, which later you can buy new cars. There are more than ten of them in the game, and some are simply unique developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Derby</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-derby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-derby/</guid>
      <description>Not quite ordinary races are waiting for you. They will not only have to go fast, but also destroy zombies on their way. At the very beginning, you will have an ordinary car at your disposal. But the more monsters you shoot down, the more money you earn, after finishing the level you can go to the garage and improve your car.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
