<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Surgery on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/surgery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Surgery on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/surgery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Baby Goldie Injured</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-goldie-injured/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-goldie-injured/</guid>
      <description>Princess Sofia felt a sharp pain in her stomach and went to the royal doctor. You have to become an assistant surgeon who will perform an operation on her abdominal cavity. First, carefully examine the patient and do the necessary tests, and then go to the operating room and follow all the doctor&amp;rsquo;s instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Puppy Rescue</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-puppy-rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cute-puppy-rescue/</guid>
      <description>In Surgery surgery for girls you will become one of the best specialists in a small private medical center visited by the famous model Barbie. The beauty is waiting for the birth of her first child and is terribly worried about this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Panda</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/doctor-panda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/doctor-panda/</guid>
      <description>The game Surgeon invites gamers to try their hand at the role of the chief physician of the fairy kingdom. It is you who will be the first to help Princess Sofia, who fell off her horse and was badly hurt. Put the baby on the surgical chair and carefully examine each of the wounds. Then try to clean the abrasions with the help of special tools, apply medicines and special bandages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ella Hip Surgery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ella-hip-surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ella-hip-surgery/</guid>
      <description>Little Liza suffers from scoliosis, every day she suffers terrible pain. That&amp;rsquo;s why you have to operate on the baby. Together with the senior nurse Lara, go to the operating room. Carefully follow the tips of your assistant, try to perform all the necessary manipulations and save the little patient from a terrible disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Surgery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/emergency-surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/emergency-surgery/</guid>
      <description>Princess Anna, the heroine of the famous animated film &amp;ldquo;Frozen Heart&amp;rdquo;, noticed that she began to hear badly. She turned to the royal hospital for help. Carefully examine your patient, determine what is causing the deterioration of her hearing and carry out the manipulations necessary to clean the ear from pathogenic microbes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Princess Hospital Recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-princess-hospital-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-princess-hospital-recovery/</guid>
      <description>The famous little mermaid fell in love with an earthly prince and now dreams of going to land for her chosen one. She turned to the old witch for help, and the witch agreed to help her. Together with an insidious sorceress, create a unique potion that will turn a mermaid&amp;rsquo;s tail into beautiful female legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Heart Surgery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-heart-surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monster-heart-surgery/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you get into the city hospital of a huge metropolis and become a surgeon. Together with the best sister of the hospital - Lara, you have to perform a very difficult heart surgery on one little patient. Follow Lara&amp;rsquo;s prompts carefully and follow all the necessary procedures. Thanks to your efforts, the operation will be successful, and very soon the baby will recover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinary Girls Cosmetic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ordinary-girls-cosmetic-surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ordinary-girls-cosmetic-surgery/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you become a famous plastic surgeon who is going to have a very difficult operation. An overweight girl came to your clinic, dreaming of correcting her figure with the help of surgery. Carefully examine the patient, conduct all the necessary tests, and then proceed to the operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Anna Arm Surgery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-anna-arm-surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-anna-arm-surgery/</guid>
      <description>In this game you meet a pretty girl named Brittany. She is a professional dancer. From overloads at rehearsals and concerts, the beauty&amp;rsquo;s legs are covered with a mesh of veins and hurt terribly. The girl is terribly worried about her health and asks you for help. Carry out the necessary medical manipulations and make Britani&amp;rsquo;s legs perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princy Throat Surgery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princy-throat-surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princy-throat-surgery/</guid>
      <description>In one of the battles with evil, SuperBarbie was seriously injured. Immediately after the end of the battle, she turned to you for help. Carefully examine the wounds of the famous heroine and try to fix your patient&amp;rsquo;s leg as soon as possible. Barbie will be grateful for your help and will definitely contact you next time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superhero Doll Hospital Recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-doll-hospital-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/superhero-doll-hospital-recovery/</guid>
      <description>The plot of the game An amateur surgeon invites you to try your hand at the role of a veterinarian. Try to examine the funny puppy as soon as possible, conduct the necessary tests and perform an operation that will save the baby&amp;rsquo;s life. Thanks to your help, the puppy will recover very quickly and will soon have fun running around the street.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
