<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shooting Minecraft on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting-minecraft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shooting Minecraft on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/shooting-minecraft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Combat Pixel SWAT &amp; Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/combat-pixel-swat--zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/combat-pixel-swat--zombies/</guid>
      <description>This time you have to play the role of a soldier who is attacked from all sides by terrible zombies. It is necessary to shoot at them in time, trying to destroy them as soon as possible. If the zombies get too close, they can bite you and eventually your character will die. This should not be allowed, because then who will be able to destroy all the enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doomcraft</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/doomcraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/doomcraft/</guid>
      <description>To enlist in the elite troops, you must pass an exam, which is taken by instructors at the training base. In one of the buildings there will be armed opponents, and you have to break through to the exit, destroying all the enemies. They can attack from anywhere, so try to be very careful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FPS Clicker</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fps-clicker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fps-clicker/</guid>
      <description>You find yourself in a night city, on the streets of which you will not meet a single living soul - only empty cars and gray houses. You have to find 8 pages with drawings of children abducted by the monster. Carefully look around and try to notice any little thing that does not fit into the overall picture of the city. And remember, the villain can appear at any moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Gun Apocalypse 7</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-gun-apocalypse-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-gun-apocalypse-7/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will go in search of an ancient Minecraft artifact that is hidden in the depths of a huge labyrinth. Load your gun and explore the huge rooms of the ancient temple, where nightmarish monsters lurk. Try to destroy all the monsters and find the greatest treasure of the pixel world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strike Combat Pixel Arena 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/strike-combat-pixel-arena-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/strike-combat-pixel-arena-3d/</guid>
      <description>This game will take you to a real army unit, where you will need to show all your dexterity and skill in order to become a brave defender of your country. Shoot at the enemy and look around with the mouse. To use the item you like, press &amp;ldquo;Tab&amp;rdquo;. Use the W, A, S and D keys to move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Farsh</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-farsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-farsh/</guid>
      <description>You will have to control a little hero, who knows the techniques of hand-to-hand combat, as well as all types of firearms and melee weapons. Gangsters of various stripes and professional thugs have long dreamed of settling Crazy Gamess with him. They are ready to do anything to win the upcoming battle. Your task is to destroy everyone and get to the boss.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
