<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For children 5-6 years old on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-5-6-years-old/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For children 5-6 years old on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-5-6-years-old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Baby Princess Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-princess-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-princess-halloween/</guid>
      <description>A cute schoolgirl wants to dress up for class. The process of the dress up game for girls 5 6 years old implies that you need to come up with a cool look for going to school. Use for this all available wardrobe items and accessories. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to also do makeup that will fit into the overall style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Running</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/banana-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/banana-running/</guid>
      <description>An interesting game for children aged 5-6 invites you to solve some exciting spatial puzzles. You need to arrange the items on the level in such a way that in the end the task is completed. If even the first time it doesn’t work out, it doesn’t matter, because you can always try again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Piano Helix Jump</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/piano-helix-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/piano-helix-jump/</guid>
      <description>If you like good music, then this game will give you a chance to try yourself as a musician or even a composer. By pressing the piano keys, you can repeat a simple melody or play something of your own. The game will also help develop hearing and show musical abilities at any age. The only drawback is the ability to press the keys only one at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruin</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ruin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ruin/</guid>
      <description>An excellent smart game for children aged 5-6 will capture your attention for a long time. The screen displays a playing field on which 16 chips are placed. You need to move them in such a way that each of the four corners ends up with chips of the same color. You can only move them to an adjacent empty cell. The point of the game is to complete the task as quickly as possible, while making the minimum number of moves.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
