<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For children 10 years old on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-10-years-old/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For children 10 years old on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-10-years-old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alien Town</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/alien-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/alien-town/</guid>
      <description>An insidious villain has created a small black hole that sucks in cute aliens. To save the inhabitants of the planet, you need to seat them in rescue capsules. Try to match the aliens so that the sum of the numbers on their backs matches the numbers indicated on the teleporter, otherwise they will remain on the planet and be swallowed up by the black hole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Defence</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-defence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-defence/</guid>
      <description>To win this game, you need to find all pairs of the same color balls as quickly as possible. According to the rules of the toy, they can be connected only horizontally or vertically, while the connection should not pass through other balls. As soon as you connect the right balls together, they will instantly disappear. Try to make sure that not a single pair of balls remains on the playing field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chopstick Cooking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/chopstick-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/chopstick-cooking/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you become employees of a small cafe where visitors are offered to try a variety of hamburgers. Carefully follow the wishes of your customers, cook delicious burgers for them and get a well-deserved cash reward. At each level you need to earn a certain amount in a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Ball Adventures</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-ball-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crazy-ball-adventures/</guid>
      <description>In this wonderful game you have to destroy colorful balls with a small cannon. Try to remove all the balls before the moment when the huge plate falls on the playing field. Shoot balls from a cannon so that they form one-color chains of three or more pieces with balls located at the top of the screen, while all of them will disappear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fruit Farm</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fruit-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fruit-farm/</guid>
      <description>Harvesting is taking place in a fairyland, and you have to help its inhabitants to collect as many wonderful fruits as possible. Using a small platform, try to transfer the fruits falling from the tree into a huge basket. Carefully watch the flight of each of the fruits and try to make sure that not one of them falls to the ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Mine</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gold-mine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gold-mine/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to become a miner who is engaged in the extraction of precious nuggets. Try to correctly calculate the flight path of a special anchor with which you will draw gold. At each level of the game, you need to draw a certain number of nuggets in a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gummy Blocks</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gummy-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gummy-blocks/</guid>
      <description>In order to win this toy, you have to remove all colored cubes from the playing field. Use the mouse cursor to point to chains of three or more cubes of the same color, and they will disappear. Try to find and destroy chains of cubes as quickly as possible, because every second more and more new cubes appear on the playing field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helicopters Puzzle Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/helicopters-puzzle-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/helicopters-puzzle-challenge/</guid>
      <description>The authors of this toy tried to create a puzzle game simulator as close as possible to the original, and they succeeded. In the shortest possible time, try to assemble a wonderful picture from separate pieces. Move the pieces of the puzzle from place to place, pick up matching pieces with the mouse cursor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snake</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/snake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/snake/</guid>
      <description>This toy is another variation of the world famous Zuma. Try to stop the chains of colored balls with the help of a cannon that tend to fall into the hole. Fire projectiles of different colors from a magic weapon and form lines of 3 or more identical pieces from them, which will instantly disappear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed Pool King</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/speed-pool-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/speed-pool-king/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to this wonderful simulator you will be able to learn the basic rules of playing billiards. Carefully inspect the location of the red balls on the table. Find the right place to place the striker and try to drive them into the pockets. Strive to correctly calculate the trajectory of impact and the force that needs to be applied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Monkey Legend</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-monkey-legend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-monkey-legend/</guid>
      <description>The little monkey loves bananas. In this game, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to help her get to her favorite treat by climbing the bamboo branches. Choose the right branch so that the baby finds the right path to the banana. For each successful attempt, you will earn reward points. Try to score the maximum number of points using 10 attempts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Eternal Temple</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-eternal-temple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-eternal-temple/</guid>
      <description>During the mindfulness game for children 10 years old, you have to correctly arrange the individual pieces of the image in a large picture. Carefully inspect all the fragments and the large image, looking for places that match. After that, with the help of the cursor and the mouse, move the pieces to the desired parts of the picture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
