<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fashionistas on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/fashionistas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fashionistas on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/fashionistas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>100 Crop Top Looks for Princess</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/100-crop-top-looks-for-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/100-crop-top-looks-for-princess/</guid>
      <description>The online game Fashionista invites you to try your hand at the role of a stylist and help a cute girl bring her appearance into perfect order. The process consists of three stages. First you need to take care of the face of the heroine of the game to make her even more beautiful. You will be asked to use various useful cosmetics that will transform the skin of her face into a clean and radiant one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dress Up Competition</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dress-up-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dress-up-competition/</guid>
      <description>The girl was invited to an important event, but she has absolutely nothing to wear. Your task is to create a festive dress for the heroine of the game from scrap materials. Find in the room those objects and things that can be used to achieve your goal. Decorate the finished dress with decorative elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dress Up Who Bonnie Coachella</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dress-up-who-bonnie-coachella/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dress-up-who-bonnie-coachella/</guid>
      <description>The girl is going to an important event, but she does not have a suitable outfit. You need to help the heroine of the game. To do this, go to the studio and choose any four items there that will determine the appearance of the future product. But the result can be very unpredictable, it will not always please the heroine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous Fashion Designer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/famous-fashion-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/famous-fashion-designer/</guid>
      <description>Create new attractive images in this wonderful game. But first you need to drive through the streets of the city and collect all the necessary items. Next, move on to applying makeup. For this, you have a lot of cosmetics at your disposal. And the final stage is the choice of hairstyles and a great outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Shoes</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/galaxy-shoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/galaxy-shoes/</guid>
      <description>During this interesting game, you will be asked to sew fashionable sneakers for a girl by yourself. Choose a style, paint with any colors you like and add decorative elements. Then go for an eye-catching look by pairing your new sneakers with cute clothes and stylish accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motor Model Dressup</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/motor-model-dressup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/motor-model-dressup/</guid>
      <description>During this game, you will turn into a stylist who knows a lot about fashionable images. Here you need to take care of the appearance of the girl. At your disposal will be a huge wardrobe, which includes only the cutest and most fashionable things. Choose any clothes, shoes and complement the image with accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Band Tees</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-band-tees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-band-tees/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you have to create entries for a fashion blog. To begin with, it is proposed to come up with a nice set for an autumn walk. Next, you will receive a task, the essence of which is to design a table with refreshments. And finally, at the end of the game, you will have to create four different looks with one dress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Eskimo</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-eskimo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-eskimo/</guid>
      <description>The girl is preparing for the celebration of the New Year, and you need to help her choose an outfit. First, find in the room all the items that are listed at the bottom of the screen. Then all that remains is to choose a suitable dress, as well as complement the look with cute jewelry that will perfectly match her festive outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Fashion Competition</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-fashion-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-fashion-competition/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to take care of the appearance of a cute girl. She doesn&amp;rsquo;t look very attractive right now, but you can quickly fix the situation. To get started, arm yourself with useful cosmetics and bring the face of the heroine of the game in order. Next, apply makeup and choose a stylish outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Vs Villains Selfie Contest</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-vs-villains-selfie-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-vs-villains-selfie-contest/</guid>
      <description>The girl does not look the best, but she really wants to be photographed. Your task is to create an attractive image for the heroine of the game. First, try on the role of a beautician and carry out various useful procedures that will help the heroine&amp;rsquo;s face to shine. And then choose a cute outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Vs Villains Tug Of War</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-vs-villains-tug-of-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-vs-villains-tug-of-war/</guid>
      <description>The girl is going on a trip, and you have to help her pack her luggage. First, choose clothes, shoes and accessories for the trip, and then start packing things in your suitcase. When everything is ready, decorate it with decorative elements, placing them in any suitable places. The size of the parts can be changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow White Mommy Real Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-white-mommy-real-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/snow-white-mommy-real-makeover/</guid>
      <description>After launching this game, you have to create fashionable outfits for mom and daughter. First, choose the style of the dress, and then take measurements that will help in the further process of tailoring. Sew cute dresses that will make the heroines as stylish and attractive as possible. The hints will help you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Fashion Street Snap</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/winter-fashion-street-snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/winter-fashion-street-snap/</guid>
      <description>The clothes of the heroine of the game are hopelessly outdated, and she is going to update her wardrobe. Help her order things in the online store, choosing the models she likes the most. But the order received may not live up to expectations, and then you will have to use your wit and improvised items to correct the situation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
