<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Truck racing on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/truck-racing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Truck racing on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/truck-racing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Army Cargo Driver 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/army-cargo-driver-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/army-cargo-driver-2/</guid>
      <description>A very addictive game with nice graphics that will surely seem familiar to those who remember the first part of &amp;ldquo;Truckers&amp;rdquo;. First you choose a car (SUV or truck) and the type of race. When the race starts, try not only to keep the car on the track, but also collect useful items (money, fuel, nitrogen). Getting to the finish line, and even more so to win, will be very difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cargo Drive</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cargo-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cargo-drive/</guid>
      <description>Not particularly difficult, but nevertheless an interesting game. You drive a truck that speeds along the track from left to right. Your competitors are trying to overtake you. You can block them with your car or turn on the nitrous oxide at the right time. Along the way, collect canisters, magnets (help collect bonuses from a distance) and coins. If you win, you move on to the next stage, and upgrade your truck with the points earned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Car Driver ZIL 130</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-car-driver-zil-130/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-car-driver-zil-130/</guid>
      <description>There can only be one winner in this race. And rivals understand this, so don&amp;rsquo;t expect an easy finish. If you win a few races, you will be transferred from beginners to the professional league. The stakes are great. Bypass competitors on bends, pressing them to the curb. In this game, all means are good to achieve victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Offroad Pickup Driver</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-offroad-pickup-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-offroad-pickup-driver/</guid>
      <description>Off-road truck racing game invites you to drive a huge and powerful car. In it you will find an exciting competition on a track full of obstacles, which is difficult to drive on a normal car. That is why powerful jeeps are used here, which can overcome any obstacles. Drive the selected car, overtake your rivals and aim for the finish line. You need to come first by all means!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
