<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For children 5 years old on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-5-years-old/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For children 5 years old on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/for-children-5-years-old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Falling Ice Creams Match</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/falling-ice-creams-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/falling-ice-creams-match/</guid>
      <description>Logic games for children 5 years old will help you develop spatial thinking and quick wits. Try to complete the sequence of items correctly. The screen will display three pictures and free space for the fourth. This is where you need to drag one of the four images located at the bottom of the screen. If you make the right decision, the picture will fall into place, after which a new logical task will open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helix Ball Bounce</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/helix-ball-bounce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/helix-ball-bounce/</guid>
      <description>Mermaid Ariel dreams of legs. Entertaining games for children aged 5 offer you to help a girl. To do this, you need to prepare a magic potion. But here&amp;rsquo;s the problem: no one knows its exact composition. Therefore, mix any four ingredients at random and see what happens in the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiss Cat</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kiss-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kiss-cat/</guid>
      <description>Go to the Wild West immediately after the launch of Shooting games for kids 5 years old. There you have to be in the shoes of a cowboy and fight the bad guys. They will attack from all sides, you just have to shoot at everyone in time. After each round, it will be possible to upgrade weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Arrow Scatter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/watermelon-arrow-scatter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/watermelon-arrow-scatter/</guid>
      <description>Find a few differences between the two images dedicated to the noble robber Robin Hood. At first glance, the pictures seem the same, but in fact, some details on them are clearly different. They need to be found by carefully examining the screen. For each correct answer you are entitled to 30 points, for a mistake 5 points are deducted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
