<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spinner.io on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/spinner.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spinner.io on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/spinner.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Create your own spinner</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-create-your-own-spinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-create-your-own-spinner/</guid>
      <description>The game offers you to spin the spinner not just like that, but for money. The longer you spin, the more coins fall into your game account. Money can be spent on upgrading toys. For example, buy her several accelerators, put oil on the core for better rotation, or change the color of the blades (the last option is the cheapest). The spinner spins with the mouse. Set the cursor to the center of the screen with it, and then sharply swipe it down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Fidget Spinner: High Score</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-fidget-spinner-high-score/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-fidget-spinner-high-score/</guid>
      <description>High Score is the most exciting and realistic spinner simulator you&amp;rsquo;ve ever played. It is even cooler than the real one, because it has a pumping option. After launching, you will see a fidget on the screen, and a vertical scale to the left of it. It captures the force with which it was possible to spin the toy. This is done as follows: a cursor is set on the screen on the image of the spinner, and then it sharply drops down with the mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game spinner hero</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-spinner-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-spinner-hero/</guid>
      <description>This spinner simulator is primarily designed for girls. It is impossible to pump over the technical parameters of the toy in it, but you can bring beauty. In part, it is already present in the form of blades of an unusual shape and a contrasting core. But you can create a really unique fidget (and more than one!) using the menu at the bottom of the screen. There are plates with different decor options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spinner clicker game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/spinner-clicker-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/spinner-clicker-game/</guid>
      <description>Despite the name, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to rotate anything in the game. After launch, a spinner will appear on the screen, but to make it spin, just click on the screen with the mouse. For each complete rotation of the toy around its axis, a coin is awarded. At first, the fidget rotates slowly and brings little money. But if you pump it, everything will change dramatically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
