<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Roblox on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/roblox/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Roblox on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/roblox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kogama 3D PacMan</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-3d-pacman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-3d-pacman/</guid>
      <description>Before you is a quest, a bit reminiscent of a retro walker with Pac-Man. There is nothing difficult in passing. After the launch, you will traditionally find yourself in the launch hall. From here, 3 portals lead to the game locations. The main events will unfold in a huge maze. You can get here through the third teleport. But until you pass additional mini-games, the entrance to it is closed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Amazing Candy World</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-amazing-candy-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-amazing-candy-world/</guid>
      <description>Immediately after the launch, you will find yourself in the city - the dream of the sweet tooth. All buildings, alleys and tracks in it are assembled from sweets, cookies and other desserts. Go explore the surroundings and collect gold stars. The goal of the game is to get 400 (or more!) of them. The game is multiplayer, which means that other participants will try to get ahead of you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Bendy And The Ink Machine</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-bendy-and-the-ink-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-bendy-and-the-ink-machine/</guid>
      <description>Roblox: Slender Escape is a pretty creepy game. Not only does the action take place in an ominous labyrinth stuffed with traps, but also all users are divided into two teams. The victory goes not to the team that leaves the corridors of the Slender Castle, but to the one who first commits the required number of kills of opponents. Of the weapons, only swords are immediately available, but you can also find radioactive blocks that will turn your character into a walking bomb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Boys vs Girls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-boys-vs-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-boys-vs-girls/</guid>
      <description>Fans of the most honest PvP will love the game &amp;ldquo;Roblox: Hello Neighbor Alpha 1&amp;rdquo;. First, the gamer needs to choose one of the two teams for which he will fight. Opponents are in equal conditions. Everyone starts the passage from their base, where there are the same sets of first-aid kits and weapons. There are also additional blocks for the construction of fortifications. Robots have a decorative value and do not take part in battles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Christmas Park</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-christmas-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-christmas-park/</guid>
      <description>In order for the game &amp;ldquo;Roblox: Escape from the Evil Santa Claus&amp;rdquo; to be considered completed, the user needs to collect exactly twenty-four stars. But they are scattered across the territory of a simply gigantic, albeit beautiful, location. Everything here looks like a New Year&amp;rsquo;s amusement park. The first star can be found in the house of Santa Claus, where you will find yourself right after the start. To do this, go up to the second floor and exit to the balcony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Crazy Parkour</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-crazy-parkour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-crazy-parkour/</guid>
      <description>New rich opportunities are opened by the Roblox Parkour game for fans of the series about the funny man in the vest. This time, users are waiting not only for the main passage, but also for entertainment in several additional locations that are not related to the main plot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama CS And Fortnite</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-cs-and-fortnite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-cs-and-fortnite/</guid>
      <description>Roblox hide and seek is not a game for the faint of heart. Especially if you have low internet speed. Not only is a long load terribly annoying, but also lags during the passage are guaranteed. But if the Internet is in order, you will get a powerful adrenaline rush.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama D-Day</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-d-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-d-day/</guid>
      <description>Roblox: 5 Nights at Freddy&amp;rsquo;s is an exciting game, of course. But if you want to take a break from horror, it&amp;rsquo;s better to do it by storming the enemy fortress. Two teams participate: one of them is defending, and the second is trying to attack, simulating a landing from the sea. This operation can be called &amp;ldquo;Freddy Bear&amp;rdquo;, as there will be a lot of blood. The task of the attackers is to turn off all the alarms and capture the flag in the allotted time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Death Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-death-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-death-run/</guid>
      <description>Fans of tickling their nerves will appreciate this deadly parkour. But not everyone can survive in it. Before you start testing yourself for strength, choose one of the two teams. The one who finds the skull first and collects the specified number of points wins. Rivals don&amp;rsquo;t have to kill each other. The action unfolds in labyrinths located almost in parallel. The red squad runs along the red corridors, the blue one, respectively, along the blue ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Escape From Prison</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-escape-from-prison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-escape-from-prison/</guid>
      <description>The Roblox Jailbreak game invites users to join the new adventures of the square-headed man. There will be no deadly parkour in it - it will be successfully replaced by no less cool entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Escape From The Sewer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-escape-from-the-sewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-escape-from-the-sewer/</guid>
      <description>The game &amp;ldquo;Roblox FNAF 5&amp;rdquo;, as an exception, does not offer users to plunge into the world of team battles. Instead, you have to overcome an unusual obstacle course. It starts at the end of the sewer, where there are statues in the form of robots. To reach the end, the user will need composure and accurate calculation. Otherwise, there is a great risk of falling on acid blocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Escape School</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-escape-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-escape-school/</guid>
      <description>Playing Roblox: School Escape will be interesting not only for long-time fans of the series of adventures of a man with a square head. The game will pleasantly surprise with its versatility and users unfamiliar with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Fidget Spinner Escape</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-fidget-spinner-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-fidget-spinner-escape/</guid>
      <description>The real fans of the Roblox series will be pleased with the new most difficult mazes and deadly rides. Of course, there is an opportunity for PvP. But you can only implement it if there are other users on the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Five Nights at Freddys</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-five-nights-at-freddys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-five-nights-at-freddys/</guid>
      <description>The game &amp;ldquo;Roblox FNAF Tycoon&amp;rdquo; is a team battle of players online. The action takes place in locations that simulate rooms from different parts of the FNAF bestseller. To win, the team must destroy a certain number of players from the enemy squad. Initially, you don’t have a weapon - you have to find it. If the user does not want to fight, he can simply go on a tour and see the locations from the horror about the Freddy bear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Freddie</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-freddie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-freddie/</guid>
      <description>The Roblox FNAF game offers users to try their hand at deadly parkour, the scenery of which is dedicated to the mega-popular horror. Already at the start, gamers will meet with the infamous heroes - robots that kill children and guards. Fortunately, this time the mechanical monsters are just for show. There are several paths from the main room. Through portals, you can get to locations with mini-games, among which there are even PvP battles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Haunted Hospital</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-haunted-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-haunted-hospital/</guid>
      <description>You can turn a beauty salon into a bloodbath by starting to resemble the game Roblox: Barbershop Escape. True, this is not an ordinary barber shop. It is full of rooms, and the corridors are intertwined into a labyrinth. There are no traps in it, but this does not mean that the game will be easy and simple. To escape from the hairdresser, you will have to collect twenty-two gold stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Hell Parkour</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-hell-parkour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-hell-parkour/</guid>
      <description>If you love playing parkour or escaping deadly mazes online, Roblox: The Floor Is Lava 3 is just the game for you. Already after the start, it will be possible to watch how the character burns alive in lava or falls into a bottomless abyss, taking a step in the wrong direction. Well, if by some miracle he managed to get to the portal without hitting the acid blocks, the hero will face even more deadly traps: eternal fire, alien robots, and even other players armed with flamethrowers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Hello Neighbor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-hello-neighbor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-hello-neighbor/</guid>
      <description>Tired of those around you, and you&amp;rsquo;re about ready to explode? The game &amp;ldquo;Roblox: Hello Neighbor&amp;rdquo; will save you from a nervous breakdown in real life. In it, you can splash out everything that has accumulated on the inhabitants of the virtual town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Hello Neighbor 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-hello-neighbor-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-hello-neighbor-3/</guid>
      <description>The game &amp;ldquo;Roblox: hello neighbor alpha 2&amp;rdquo; offers to cut your neighbor to pieces with impunity and relieve stress in such a fun way. After downloading, the user needs to choose which team to play for. There are only two options: blue and red. The team that first collects the required number of stars and takes possession of the checkered flag wins. The action takes place in a small town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Horror</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-horror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-horror/</guid>
      <description>If you want variety, the Roblox FNAF 3 game will provide it in abundance. After downloading, you will find yourself in the main game room. From here, through portals, you can get to several locations with different mini-games. For example, take part in battles against other players, or build something using blocks like in Minecraft. And at your disposal will be a shooting range, where alien combat robots act as targets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Humans vs Sharks</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-humans-vs-sharks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-humans-vs-sharks/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Roblox FNAF 2&amp;rdquo; is a game for those who are insanely tired of work or school. In it, you can throw out all the accumulated negativity by taking part in team skirmishes. The game arsenal pleases with variety: from a throwing knife to a plasma gun. Flying packs are also available. You can drag blocks to build fortifications. The robots don&amp;rsquo;t move, they&amp;rsquo;re just decorations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama I Five Nights At Freddys</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-i-five-nights-at-freddys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-i-five-nights-at-freddys/</guid>
      <description>The game &amp;ldquo;Roblox FNAF 4&amp;rdquo; will cause real delight among those gamers who are a bloody maniac at heart. Only here you can chase other users with a pistol or sword through the labyrinths, trying to kill them. The atmosphere is ominous: there are robots from the Freddy Bear game everywhere. The most important thing is to be the first to find a block with a weapon, so as not to become a victim of the killer yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Imperial</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-imperial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-imperial/</guid>
      <description>Many users will play Roblox Escape from Oreo, as well as other projects in this series. But they are unlikely to compete with each other. Rather, they can even cooperate. For example, if you take a cannon at the start, which shoots blocks with a single mouse click, you will be able to neutralize the acid on the obstacle course. It is with her that the escape from Oreo begins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Jurassic World</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-jurassic-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-jurassic-world/</guid>
      <description>You have a unique opportunity to visit the Jurassic Park and take a closer look at all those who inhabited the Earth a thousand years ago. To get inside, just come close to the gate. Dinosaurs and tyrannosaurs are in enclosures - they are motionless and do not pose a danger. The game has no specific goal. All you need is to move around the locations and explore the surroundings in the company of other users&amp;rsquo; characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Love Land </title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-love-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-love-land/</guid>
      <description>In order for the game &amp;ldquo;Roblox: hello neighbor alpha 5&amp;rdquo; to work as correctly as possible, and there were no problems with it when loading, the developers recommend using the Fire Fox browser. It is also recommended to clean the C drive from everything superfluous. The action takes place in the city of Roblox. It is full of houses that form residential blocks, there is a cinema, a university, robotic statues and other strange buildings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Mega Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-mega-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-mega-wars/</guid>
      <description>A cool toy for fans of team fights and PvP mode. Immediately after the launch, you will enter the launch hall, from which several portals lead. Before heading towards them, choose one of the three teams. You cannot play alone. Then, passing through the museum of old military equipment, you will find yourself on a huge map, where the battles unfold. The goal of the game is to bring your team more points by killing representatives of the opposing squad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Minecraft Mltiplayer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-minecraft-mltiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-minecraft-mltiplayer/</guid>
      <description>The game &amp;ldquo;Roblox: Escape from the Sweet World&amp;rdquo; is relatively peaceful compared to other projects in the series. The main task in it is to collect the maximum number of lilac medals. There are weapons, but it is better to take a cannon that shoots blocks. They will be needed to build bridges. All robots are just decoration, and other gamers should be afraid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Minions Parcour</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-minions-parcour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-minions-parcour/</guid>
      <description>The game &amp;ldquo;Roblox: Despicable Me 3&amp;rdquo; will allow gamers to meet several of their favorite characters at once. Firstly, with a man with a square head in a striped T-shirt, and secondly, with minions from the famous cartoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Minions Parkour</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-minions-parkour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-minions-parkour/</guid>
      <description>Roblox: Minions is no more difficult to play than other projects in this series. However, no other game offers such an amount of entertainment. Two dozen portals will take anyone to locations where you can do parkour, killing your own kind, racing jetpack flights and other interesting things. You won&amp;rsquo;t have to escape from the minions anywhere. These characters are everywhere, but they are immobile, like ordinary blocks. Combat robots are also safe and inactive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Parkor 30 Levels</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkor-30-levels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkor-30-levels/</guid>
      <description>Roblox: Granny Escape will be interesting to play for those who love parkour. Here it is more than in any other toys of the Roblox series. Battles with real players are also provided. To take part in them, you need to move through the portal to the PvP location. There you can collect three of the fifty stars. And when you have collected the entire collection, the game will be over, which means that you will succeed in escaping from your grandmother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Parkour 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkour-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkour-2019/</guid>
      <description>Unlike other Roblox quests, you will find yourself alone on the maps of this game. Ahead lies the most difficult and dangerous parkour ever played. The passage is divided into small segments with different locations and tasks. There is nothing worth dying on each. The character has one life, and there is no autosave in the game. It will only be possible to pass the trap if you turn off logic and try to think in paradoxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Parkour 27</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkour-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkour-27/</guid>
      <description>The concentration of traps and adventures in this game is over the top. The task of the user is to survive, no matter what. At the same time, you will have to get the specified number of stars, the flag and destroy as many aliens as possible, similar to bulging eyes with wings. The game is multiplayer, which means that you can meet other users on the locations. You can interact with them in two ways: arrange competitions or help each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Parkour 31 Levels</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkour-31-levels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkour-31-levels/</guid>
      <description>If you like 3rd person virtual parkour, you will love Roblox Scary Elevator too. Moreover, it is always full of rivals controlled by real players. At certain points, they can even become allies if they wish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Parkour 45 lvl</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkour-45-lvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkour-45-lvl/</guid>
      <description>When the Roblox Scissor Escape game starts, you will be able to be in the shoes of a maniac victim. He will chase you, dreaming of cutting you into pieces. Use concrete blocks to hide and try to find weapons. Robots won&amp;rsquo;t help you, but they won&amp;rsquo;t hurt you either - they&amp;rsquo;re just part of the scenery. But other users can become either allies or enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Parkour Batman 17lvl</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkour-batman-17lvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-parkour-batman-17lvl/</guid>
      <description>This game is a witty mix of puzzles and parkour. Immediately after the launch, you will find yourself in a huge hall. From it through the portals you can get to the game locations. On each one you have to play a separate mini-game. The central exit from the starting room is hidden behind a smokescreen. Right behind it begins the main obstacle course. It consists of many stages in which you will have to run, jump and use weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Phoenix vs God</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-phoenix-vs-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-phoenix-vs-god/</guid>
      <description>The game &amp;ldquo;Roblox Titanic&amp;rdquo; is designed for fans of hot battles with real opponents online. The action takes place at a training ground bearing the same name as the sunken ship. Before starting, the user needs to decide which team to fight for. The final victory will be won by the one who kills a certain number of opponents. The arsenal of weapons is the same as in other projects of the Roblox series: from a sword to a plasma gun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Plants VS Zombies</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-plants-vs-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-plants-vs-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Roblox: Plants vs Zombies is a great team shooting game. Before starting battles, you need to decide who to play for. Even if there are only two gamers on the server, you won&amp;rsquo;t be bored. There are plenty of weapons. It is scattered at spawn points, as well as throughout the game location, the relief of which, by the way, is typical for other similar projects of the Roblox series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Sonik Parkour </title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-sonik-parkour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-sonik-parkour/</guid>
      <description>In this game, the trouble starts right after launch. You won’t even have a second to look around and understand what’s what. As always, from the launch hall you need to get to the portals leading to the game locations. The trouble is that the path to them lies through a field with poisonous blocks. To survive, you need to jump from one safe area to another without touching the acid ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Straszna Mapa</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-straszna-mapa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-straszna-mapa/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Roblox: Witch Escape&amp;rdquo; is a game that will appeal, first of all, to those who love all sorts of secrets and mysteries. The action takes place on a small island with a strange structure like a castle. Inside it is a labyrinth. There is no one in it, not even robots. There are no traps either. But somewhere in the bowels of the golden stars are hidden. The main goal is to find two pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Super Mario N64</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-super-mario-n64/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-super-mario-n64/</guid>
      <description>In the process of passing the game &amp;ldquo;Roblox: Escape from McDonald&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; many gamers take part. They all control characters similar to yours. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to fight each other. Instead, you have to find and collect three dozen gold stars. Only after that it will be possible to raise the flag at the gates of the children&amp;rsquo;s park at McDonald&amp;rsquo;s and announce that the game is over. Heroes are waiting for a lot of dangers: deadly traps, combat robots, bottomless abysses and even self-destructive blocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Teen Titans</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-teen-titans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-teen-titans/</guid>
      <description>Anyone who loves shooters should definitely play. Fans of shooting games are waiting for a super gambling, multiplayer game with shootouts and chases. Before you start, choose one of the two commands. If you ignore this step, the &amp;ldquo;allocation&amp;rdquo; will happen automatically. Then, in the launch hall, take a weapon (there are also plenty of them at the locations, but it’s better not to walk on them unarmed) a jetpack for flights and go to the city to earn points for your team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Temple Of Doom</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-temple-of-doom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-temple-of-doom/</guid>
      <description>An exciting three-dimensional quest will take you to the holy of holies of the Roblox world - the Temple of Doom. Only here you can understand what you really stand for. The game is a team game - before you start, you will have to choose one of several units. Then you can start to act at your own peril and risk. The goal is to destroy as many enemies as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama The Floor Is Lava</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-the-floor-is-lava/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-the-floor-is-lava/</guid>
      <description>Roblox: The Floor Is Lava is not that hard to play. The most important thing is to have a good Internet speed so that the hero - a little man, familiar to everyone from other games of the same series, ideally responds to user commands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama The Floor Is Lava 1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-the-floor-is-lava-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-the-floor-is-lava-1/</guid>
      <description>An exciting quest awaits you in the three-dimensional expanses of the Roblox world. The goal is to collect five gold stars. They can be anywhere - there are four cards in the game, which can be accessed through the portals of the launch hall. At each new location, you need to complete a mini-game to get one star. The last, fifth star will go to those who can complete the final part of the quest in the green portal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama The Floor Is Lava 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-the-floor-is-lava-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-the-floor-is-lava-2/</guid>
      <description>The game &amp;ldquo;Roblox: the floor is lava 2&amp;rdquo; is a continuation of the entertainment series of the same name. This time, the main character needs to collect a collection of four stars to win. The problem is that there is simply nowhere to pick them up. They are issued only for completing mini-games, which can be accessed through the portals of the main room. In the first transition, the character will have to use safe blocks to get to the exit and pick up the prize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Universal Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-universal-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-universal-racing/</guid>
      <description>Roblox: Hello Neighbor Alpha 4 is another opportunity to take part in fierce team shootouts. Unlike other parts of the series, here users received a larger arsenal of weapons, as well as additional blocks - you can hide behind them. As always, it all starts with the choice of the team for which you will fight. There are two options, so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to think long. Killing other players is a mandatory part of the game, but not the main one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama War</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-war/</guid>
      <description>In this game of the Roblox series, survival is the main task. It is not easy to fulfill it, as the opponents are brave and insidious. But you will also have allies. In general, four teams take part in the gaming meat grinder at once. The location is not too big, it is an island. But it has enough open spaces and shelters. Weapons are scattered almost everywhere. This is a typical Roblox arsenal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama West Town</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-west-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-west-town/</guid>
      <description>Before the game &amp;ldquo;Roblox: Hello Neighbor Alpha 3&amp;rdquo; starts, you need to decide which side to fight on: yellow or red. Like a gentleman, choose those who are outnumbered and join the fight. Immediately after the start, you will have group battles on the territory of the small town of Roblox. The robots are long gone, but the adventurers have stayed and are now brainwashing each other. Near the spawn point, you can only pick up a revolver, but if the gamer dares to take a walk, he can get other weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama Work At A Pizza Place</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-work-at-a-pizza-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-work-at-a-pizza-place/</guid>
      <description>The location &amp;ldquo;Roblox: pizzeria&amp;rdquo;, where this time the well-known square-headed character has been brought, amazes with a huge area and intricate labyrinths. Finding a way out of them is the main task that the game poses to gamers. This will not be easy to do. And not only because the corridors are winding and dark. They are full of deadly dangers. For example, robots spitting acid, blocks of burning lava (touching them leads to slow death), and other surprises that this infernal pizzeria is rich in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kogama World Racing </title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-world-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/kogama-world-racing/</guid>
      <description>Roblox Cars 3 invites users to take part in flying car death races for free. Moreover, you can choose not only a sports model, but also some kind of SUV like the Hammer. And in secret places even ancient jalopies are hidden. Of course, the gamer will not play alone. The company and competition will be made up of other racers. And these will not be robots, but live players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkour 30 levels</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/parkour-30-levels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/parkour-30-levels/</guid>
      <description>Get ready to try your luck in super dangerous parkour. You will find a distance of many segments with different decorations and tasks. Before each new test, you can save your progress by touching the flag. If you want to win, you have to be careful. Despite the fact that at any second your character may die, the ultimate goal of the game is not to survive, but to collect five gold stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roblox game: superheroes</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/roblox-game-superheroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/roblox-game-superheroes/</guid>
      <description>In the Roblox universe, superheroes are also popular. Especially such as Thor, Captain America or Tycoon. Unfortunately, the gamer will not be able to choose who to play with. At his disposal, they will be the whole composition - a single team that will have to fight the invasion of alien robots. Each hero has his own superpower, which can be used at the right time. To do this, simply switch between characters, changing one for another right during the battle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Z </title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/world-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/world-z/</guid>
      <description>Roblox: Zombie will appeal to fans of the survival genre. This is a game where you need to monitor not only the health of the character, but the level of fatigue and hunger. Of course, there are a lot of walking dead here who are trying to live like ordinary people, only eating human flesh.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
