<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Autobots on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/autobots/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Autobots on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/autobots/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bumblebee`s Music Mix</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bumblebees-music-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bumblebees-music-mix/</guid>
      <description>Choose your character and set out to unravel the Autobot Matrix Code. To solve it, you need to collect more logos. Decepticon soldiers will hinder you. Deal with them with a cannon or a sword. To replenish your health, collect Energon cubes. Hurry - time to complete the task is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross The Bridge</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cross-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cross-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>If you see the inscription &amp;ldquo;There is no way out&amp;rdquo; - do not believe it. It&amp;rsquo;s always there, and the Autobots will find it. And in this game you will help them. You need to control two robots that can dock to each other (oh, it&amp;rsquo;s so romantic!). Docking is needed in order to overcome some obstacles in principle possible. You can play alone or together, controlling different robots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robo Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/robo-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/robo-racing/</guid>
      <description>Playing Autobots will require precise calculation and patience from you in order to win all the battles. Gunfights between your character and Decepticon soldiers take place over long distances and in limited visibility. Projectiles fly along a hinged trajectory, so you have to calculate the angle of fire and the launch force of the projectile. Enemies have weaker weapons, but Decepticons can fire bursts and, moreover, there are initially more of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robo Twins</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/robo-twins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/robo-twins/</guid>
      <description>No, the Autobots were not captured or arrested on charges of stealing engine oil. It&amp;rsquo;s just that two robot friends were alone on a planet destroyed by a nuclear war and are trying to get out of there. You can help them. But the game will require you to be smart, as well as the ability to work in a team, because robots can overcome most of the obstacles only by merging into a single whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robocar Jigsaw</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/robocar-jigsaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/robocar-jigsaw/</guid>
      <description>Hey, enough to destroy and shoot everything around. Time to spread your brains and train your attention. In this game, you need to turn the fragments of the picture so that they take the correct position relative to each other. At the same time, you need to comply with the standard. When you collect one picture, you get another. Pump your brain!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Robo Fighter 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-robo-fighter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-robo-fighter-3/</guid>
      <description>If you like to tinker with constructors, assembling robots with your own hands, then Autobots 2 games are what you need. So, in front of you is a box with a disassembled transformer. Try to assemble it entirely from individual parts. A translucent image of an Autobot robot acts as an instruction - just take it and put the fragment in its place. You use parts from one board - you get the next one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformers Super Mini-Con Striker</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/transformers-super-mini-con-striker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/transformers-super-mini-con-striker/</guid>
      <description>You would think that the Autobots have missions that are not important to anyone! So this time the importance of the mission just rolls over, as well as the number of enemies. Choose your robot at the very beginning of the game and start saving the world. But first, you should look into the control section and remember the necessary buttons. What&amp;rsquo;s annoying about this game is all the introductory cutscenes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformers: Energon Rally</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/transformers-energon-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/transformers-energon-rally/</guid>
      <description>The Autobots rush to help, but the main thing is that the gasoline does not run out on the way. You can take part in a merciless battle with the Decepticons, of course, if you break through the jungle of instructions and other obstacles. Use the weapons of Bumble BI to stop the flow of enemy robots. Place mines, automatic turrets and crush them with your feet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
