<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tanks Dandy on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/tanks-dandy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tanks Dandy on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/tanks-dandy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eg Tank Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-tank-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/eg-tank-wars/</guid>
      <description>Before you is a logic game in which 2-3 players can fight simultaneously and on the same computer, trying to destroy each other. According to the conditions, your equipment falls into a labyrinth, where the laws of physics do not always apply and shots are reflected from the walls. Use this feature and projectile trajectory hints to be the first to destroy your opponents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank/</guid>
      <description>Your green tank is involved in a fast-paced battle with yellow enemy vehicles. You need to move very quickly within the walls of the labyrinth, moving away from enemy fire and constantly shooting to kill. Break through the walls with shots, clearing the way to the final goal - the transition to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Heroes</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-heroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-heroes/</guid>
      <description>You are waiting for unforgettable tank battles that will take place in one of the Russian cities during the Second World War between the German army and the forces of the USSR. In order to win in each battle, you will need not only to destroy the opponents, but also to protect your base from enemy attacks. You can use various bonuses to defeat the invader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanks Classic</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-classic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-classic/</guid>
      <description>An excellent game Tanchiki Dandy will certainly appeal to children. Well, adults will be completely delighted with it, because it was in it that they once played on consoles. Touch and you to an unforgettable classic by starting to play Dandy Tanks right now! In them, you need to control a tank that needs to get through hordes of enemies to the place marked on the map. You can get acquainted with this map by pressing the space bar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
