<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Poki on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/poki/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Poki on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/poki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1001 Arabian Nights 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/1001-arabian-nights-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/1001-arabian-nights-3/</guid>
      <description>The majestic Amazon River is gradually shallowing and you have to save one of its tributaries. During a scientific expedition, you managed to discover an ancient device created by the scientists of the Inca tribe and capable of cleaning the river. Try with the help of magic balls to free the river from the mule that blocked the flow of water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bear Boom</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bear-boom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bear-boom/</guid>
      <description>Bears in a row game invites you to the cloudy kingdom of magic bears. A terrible sorceress has bewitched all the inhabitants of this fabulous country. To dispel the spell, you need to break the magic tablets on each level of an exciting game, collecting chains of cubs of the same color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossom Crush Legend</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/blossom-crush-legend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/blossom-crush-legend/</guid>
      <description>This toy sends you to a small flower bed. On it it is necessary to make bouquets of flowers of the same species. For each collected bouquet you will have points. Go through all the levels of the game, try to Crazy Games the maximum number and become one of its champions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble/</guid>
      <description>Magic bubbles invite you to go with them to the fabulous land of soap balls. There you need to release trapped bubbles. With the help of a funny gun, collect them in chains of three or more pieces and free them from the trap. Try to rescue all the balls before they fill the playing field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-shooter/</guid>
      <description>Take part in an exciting competition and try to win. You need to make chains of stones of the same color. Try to go through as many levels of the game as possible and get into the leaderboard posted on the developer&amp;rsquo;s website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Shooter Pet</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-shooter-pet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-shooter-pet/</guid>
      <description>Game Bubbles in a row invites you to take part in an exciting competition. Try to destroy all the balls coming down from the top of the playing field. With the help of a cannon that shoots colorful balls, collect chains of three or more pieces. Playing a toy in Russian, try to Crazy Games the maximum number of points for the collected chains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Pop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-pop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-pop/</guid>
      <description>Diamond Match 3 game invites you to take part in an exciting competition that brings together players from all over the world. In this toy, you need to make chains of gems of the same color. At each stage of the game you have to collect a certain number of stones in a limited time. Try to go through as many levels of the game as possible and get into the high Crazy Games table posted on the website of the game developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Rain 4</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-rain-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/candy-rain-4/</guid>
      <description>There is a commotion at a huge candy factory - one of the sorting machines has broken down. Candies of different colors are mixed in the bunker, and you have to sort the sweets by color. Try to complete the task as quickly as possible, because children all over the world are waiting for their favorite treat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Balls</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/christmas-balls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/christmas-balls/</guid>
      <description>In this game you find yourself in the fantastic world of Google Ice. The funny creatures that inhabit it are very curious and often fall into traps because of this. This time they climbed into a huge stone bag, and you have to help them out of the trap. Use the mouse cursor to select chains of big-eyed koloboks and pull them out of the trap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cube Blast</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cube-blast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cube-blast/</guid>
      <description>The game Cubes in a row invites you to become a demining specialist. At each level of this exciting toy, you must turn off the electronic fuse system. Try to remove colorful pixels from the screen in a limited time. If you do not manage to destroy the colored squares, an explosion will occur, and you will have to start the game from the very beginning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diamond Match</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/diamond-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/diamond-match/</guid>
      <description>Game Poki precious diamonds will require you to be attentive and flawless logical thinking. At each of the levels of this rebus, you must open all the cells of the playing field in a limited time. To do this, you must make chains of gems of the same color. As soon as a chain of three or more elements is assembled, all the gems in it will disappear, and the cells on which they stood will open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Match 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-match-3/</guid>
      <description>The Easter Bunny is preparing to deliver decorated eggs to babies all over the world. But when he opened his vault, he found that all the dyes were mixed up. Help the fairy creature sort the eggs. Do it as quickly as possible, because the time to prepare for the holiday is limited, and the rabbit may not have time to congratulate all his friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flowers Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/flowers-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/flowers-rush/</guid>
      <description>In this game you find yourself in a huge flower field. At each stage you have to collect a beautiful bouquet of wildflowers. Making bouquets of three or more flowers, try to break all the prize cells on the field as quickly as possible. There is a limited time to collect a beautiful bouquet, so hurry up and complete the task of each level as quickly as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fruit Match</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fruit-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fruit-match/</guid>
      <description>The game Fruit Country Poki invites you to play a funny puzzle. Try to Crazy Games the maximum number of points by collecting chains of various wild berries and exotic fruits. You have a limited amount of time to complete each level, so try to collect the required amount as quickly as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fruit Match samename 1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/fruit-match-samename-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/fruit-match-samename-1/</guid>
      <description>The Fruit Cocktail game invites you to a farm where all kinds of fruits are grown. Try to collect as many of them as possible in a limited period of time. To do this, you need to make lines of three or more identical fruits. Prize points are awarded for each collected chain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galactic Gems 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/galactic-gems-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/galactic-gems-2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fantastic world of magic and runes! In this game you have to control five magical elements. Collect runes of one of the elements in chains of three or more. Put together as much magical energy as you can, and through it, try to learn the most secret techniques of ancient magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Tales</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/garden-tales/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/garden-tales/</guid>
      <description>In this wonderful game you find yourself in a beautiful garden. At each of its stages it is necessary to grow a magnificent flower. Try to collect chains of cards depicting different types of flowers presented in the most unique botanical garden. Do it as quickly as possible, because the plant must be grown in a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jewel-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jewel-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Scientists of the ancient Mayan civilization invite you to take part in an exciting competition. Try to go through as many stages of this exciting game as possible, scoring the maximum number of bonus points on each of them. To do this, you need to collect lines of gems of the same color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Magic Xmas</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/jewel-magic-xmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/jewel-magic-xmas/</guid>
      <description>While playing mini games of logic Poki you go to a fantastic planet in a distant solar system. In one of the deep gorges, scouts have discovered a strange station, and you need to unravel the access code to it. Try to open all the squares on the playing field by collecting chains of three or more stones in a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match Arena</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/match-arena/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/match-arena/</guid>
      <description>The authors of the game Farms in a row invite you to try your hand at the role of the owner of a farm. Try to develop your possessions by buying pets for gold coins. You can earn them by completing mini-game levels in which you need to collect chains of three or more identical vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monsters Match-3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/monsters-match-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/monsters-match-3/</guid>
      <description>The Match 3 game sends you to the shores of the mysterious Amazon, where you have to unravel the mysteries of an ancient Indian tribe and get to a mysterious artifact. In order to move from stage to stage, you need to destroy all the clay tablets placed on the playing field. To do this, you need to collect three or more gems of the same color in a row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop Stone 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pop-stone-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pop-stone-2/</guid>
      <description>In this game you find yourself in ancient dungeons created by the Mayan people. In order to get out of here, you need to solve a logical puzzle. Try to destroy the colored balls blocking the entrance to the next levels of this exciting toy. To do this, you need to collect chains of the same color balls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tabby Island</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tabby-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tabby-island/</guid>
      <description>Animals Match 3 game invites you to go to the world of Wubbis - funny and very curious insects. So this time, shaggy balls managed to get into a huge press. Use your magic cannon to try to free all the wubbis from the trap for free before the huge top plate crushes the unfortunate babies. Collect chains of three or more balls and release them. Thanks to your help, all the cute shaggy babies will definitely get out of the dangerous trap and go in search of new adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/treasure-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/treasure-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Wonders in a row game invites you to go in search of the treasures of ancient Atlantis. At each stage of the search, you need to get a piece of the map from the ancient mosaic, which indicates the place where the fabulous treasures are stored. Try to lower the artifact to the bottom of the playing field, removing chains of puzzle pieces with the same patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Island</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/treasure-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/treasure-island/</guid>
      <description>The famous traveler Phyllias Fog goes on a trip around the world and you have to help him go around the whole Earth in 80 days. Every day you have to get for your new friend the things he needs on the way. Collect gems in chains and get parts of the items Phyllias needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zuma Blast</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zuma-blast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zuma-blast/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you enter the carousel of Match 3 games. Try to stop the snakes of balls that are trying to get to the holes in the center of the game screen. With the help of a cannon that shoots balls, collect chains of elements of the same color. Hurry up and destroy the snake as quickly as possible, because it is very fast approaching the hole.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
