<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>drift on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/drift/</link>
    <description>Recent content in drift on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/drift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ATV Offroad Trials 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/atv-offroad-trials-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/atv-offroad-trials-2/</guid>
      <description>During the colorful and dynamic Drift 3D game, you have to take part in the drifting world championship, taking place on a small island somewhere in the middle of the Pacific Ocean. In order to become the winner of the tournament, you need to win on 12 tracks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunched Metal: Drifting Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/crunched-metal-drifting-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/crunched-metal-drifting-wars/</guid>
      <description>If you like racing with a view from above and, at the same time, not too dynamic, then you will enjoy playing Car Drift. Despite the small size of all objects, their drawing is not bad. The animation is nothing special, but no one demanded anything of the sort from it. The essence is very simple and pretty standard: drive around the tracks and drift around corners. Of course, it is desirable to come to the finish line before your competitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dare Drift : Car Drift Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dare-drift--car-drift-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dare-drift--car-drift-racing/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to take part in dirt track racing? Then start the game. Management here is simple. But when cornering, you need to press a special button for drifting. The entire route is divided into segments that must be overcome in the allotted time. If you succeed, you get extra time. No, you start over. You can upgrade between levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Car Driving Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-car-driving-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-car-driving-simulator/</guid>
      <description>A good toy, in which, as you progress, not only new levels open up, but also new types of tasks, that is, races. Third person view. Management - using the keyboard. First you have to drive around the city. The goal is to bypass all rivals and come to the finish line first. After passing the first stage, new tasks will become available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Drift</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-drift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/extreme-drift/</guid>
      <description>This game has very unusual controls. Instead of directly influencing the car, you will drag the magnet in front of it with the mouse, as if setting the trajectory of movement. The car should not crash while driving through the distance. You also need to collect stars, earning reward points for upgrading between stages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formula Racing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/formula-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/formula-racing/</guid>
      <description>Drifting is a style of cornering that originated in Japan. Take to the racing tracks of the drift fashion trendsetter and prove that you are the master of this extreme driving style. Control your racing car using the keyboard, and if necessary, send your sports car to drift with the &amp;ldquo;Z&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highway Racer 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/highway-racer-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/highway-racer-3d/</guid>
      <description>The best racers in the world, including you, were invited to an unusual championship. Races take place on an island inhabited by zombies. At your disposal is a car that is not only prepared for these competitions, but also thoroughly armed. Win all the races of the tournament and clear the island of terrible zombies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Fast Driver</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-fast-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-fast-driver/</guid>
      <description>Not a bad game without much meaning, goals and objectives. Having chosen a wheelbarrow, you can change its color to your taste. Then connect to the single player mode or multiplayer mode, where the same players will drive with you at the same location. Then either just drive around the track and perform different tricks, or try to chase your opponents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supercars Drift</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/supercars-drift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/supercars-drift/</guid>
      <description>Wonderful post-apocalyptic racing awaits users after downloading this game. Not only can rivals be destroyed with machine guns, but zombies will also have to be crushed on the road. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to pick up useful bonuses along the way, like ammo, shield (temporary invulnerability) and other goodies. Top view, standard control.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
