<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hunting on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/hunting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hunting on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/hunting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Big Hunter Online</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/big-hunter-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/big-hunter-online/</guid>
      <description>A very funny game. On the edge of the cliff is your character, who is very similar to Robin Hood, only an old one. He has a bow in his hands and needs to shoot flying birds. Arrows &amp;ldquo;up-down&amp;rdquo; adjust the direction of the bow, and &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; - pulls the string. The shot occurs when you press the &amp;ldquo;space&amp;rdquo;. Sometimes birds can take revenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caveman Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/caveman-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/caveman-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Tired of toys in which everything is like in a shooting gallery? The Big Hunt game is somewhat out of the general range. Firstly, here you can move around, while the first-person view, weapons are shown. Secondly, the tasks are quite difficult. So, according to bourgeois concepts of hunting, you will have to shoot from prepared sites. On each you need to get a certain number of trophies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DarkHunt HD: Brutality</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/darkhunt-hd-brutality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/darkhunt-hd-brutality/</guid>
      <description>A simple game in which you need to hunt birds. In fact, there is little to do with hunting here, except for shooting. The character is standing in the middle of the enclosure, and birds are flying around him in the sky. They are drawn, by the way, very conditionally. The weapon is visible, you can aim or shoot at random. The goal is to shoot as many targets as possible in the allotted time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/duck-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/duck-hunter/</guid>
      <description>The game Hunting Season 2 is trying to convey to the gamer the atmosphere of duck hunting. A pathetic attempt, I must say. But the performance is quite interesting. First-person view. Drawn ducks are sitting on a real (photo) swamp. At each stage, you need to shoot a certain number of birds. It&amp;rsquo;s not easy even on the easiest difficulty level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck Shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/duck-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/duck-shooter/</guid>
      <description>Those gamers who have found another eight-bit consoles are probably familiar with the Duck Hunting game. The one in which the dog mockingly crumpled after a miss and everyone tried to shoot her at least once. And now this epic toy is out for fun online for free. So, for those who do not know, it is interesting to know what the point is. And the point is this. The hunter, that is, the gamer (first-person view and only the cursor-sight is visible) went with a dog to hunt ducks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forest Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/forest-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/forest-hunter/</guid>
      <description>To play Deer Hunting, you do not need to know the habits of these animals, the ability to silently sneak up, shoot well, know the killer places on the body of the beast, the bullet hitting which reliably hits the target, and so on. All you need is a working mouse and some free time. Deer hunting here resembles a shooting range, in which the targets move along arbitrary trajectories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hunter/</guid>
      <description>During this game, elk hunting takes place absolutely without killing. You just need to throw and hit the moose with water balls. Points are awarded for each hit. But if you hit the other inhabitants of the forest with a ball, you will get a very serious fine. The goal of the game is to earn as many points as possible in the allotted time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moorhuhn Pirates</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/moorhuhn-pirates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/moorhuhn-pirates/</guid>
      <description>You have never seen such a game as Chicken Hunt! Painted chickens, or rather domestic roosters, fly back and forth across the photographed landscape. And you supposedly hunt them. More precisely, you simply move the cursor and press the mouse button. For reloading - &amp;ldquo;space&amp;rdquo;. If you shoot down an airship, points are removed from you - a fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Hunting</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-hunting/</guid>
      <description>Alas, hunting for a bear with a gun has nothing to do with the game process. Instead of stalking this dangerous predator or luring him out of his lair, you have to do not too difficult target shooting. They imitate polar bears that run around the tent city or just sit behind shelters, popping up for a short time. The Bear Hunt game is designed for one gamer, but you can invite a company and compete in scoring points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolf Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/wolf-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/wolf-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Before you is another game-shooting gallery, which stands out from a number of similar ones for some reason. For example, people with a weak psyche may begin to have nightmares due to a very specific animal animation. They move like they&amp;rsquo;re zombies from a horror movie. Another feature is that when hitting forest birds and animals, points are awarded. When shooting those who do not live in the forest - a fine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
