<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>brain teaser on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/brain-teaser/</link>
    <description>Recent content in brain teaser on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/brain-teaser/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adam And Eve Golf</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/adam-and-eve-golf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/adam-and-eve-golf/</guid>
      <description>Logic games for two offer to play the famous gallows in everything. The screen will display a diagram of the hidden word, from which it is clear how many letters it contains. Also in the game for two you will see the alphabet. Click on those letters that, in your opinion, are in the hidden word. If you correctly point to the letter, it will immediately appear in the word-scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amigo Pancho 2 New York Party</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/amigo-pancho-2-new-york-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/amigo-pancho-2-new-york-party/</guid>
      <description>A very interesting game where you have to think a little to correctly draw a flight path for a paper airplane. True, this must be done in such a way that the pilot, flying along the chosen path, collects all the golden stars. Use the mouse to try to choose the best route option and go to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Farm</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bubble-farm/</guid>
      <description>The puzzle game Bubble Shooter invites you to get rid of a wall of colorful balls. To do this, you need to throw similar balls into it, falling into groups of the same color as the projectile. After that, this whole combination will disappear. The direction of the flight of the ball is determined by the arrow: direct it with the mouse in the desired direction. If several rolls are not successful, the wall will drop one position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HidJigs Spring</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hidjigs-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hidjigs-spring/</guid>
      <description>Puzzle games search for items will turn you into a real detective. Here you need to strain all your attention to find the right things. In fact, these objects are the differences between two identical images of the room. Examine the provided pictures and find all the given elements on them. By the way, initially you will not know exactly what items are proposed to be found. Only their total number is indicated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hit Or Knit</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/hit-or-knit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/hit-or-knit/</guid>
      <description>Logic games Shooters will show you a huge number of colorful balls. They lined up in a massive structure at the top of the screen. At the bottom there is a device that allows you to shoot all the same balls. Throw them into groups of elements of the same color to get rid of them. The toy is available online without restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
