<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tanks 2 on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/tanks-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tanks 2 on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/tanks-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Armored Blasters I</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/armored-blasters-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/armored-blasters-i/</guid>
      <description>In the game, you need to destroy as many enemy vehicles as possible that will appear on the level in the hope of defeating you. Your tank can self-repair - take advantage of this opportunity. To do this, you need to find a special symbol, which activates the desired ability. Dodge projectiles and missiles fired by the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battlesun 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/battlesun-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/battlesun-2/</guid>
      <description>Your tank ended up in an underground tunnel guarded by enemy war machines and ceiling turrets. Will you be able to bring him to the end of the level in this dangerous labyrinth, destroying all the enemies along the way? The most important thing is not to rush and destroy the enemy one by one. Collect coins and buy modern weapons and protection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defend The Tank</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/defend-the-tank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/defend-the-tank/</guid>
      <description>The Tanki 2 game will take you to a world where a terrible zombie apocalypse has taken place. Now the streets are filled with the risen dead, and only a tank will help you survive in this terrible situation. You need to move in your vehicle along a given track, performing only 2 actions: destroying zombies along the way and collecting coins. Fuel is limited, so the tank will stop sooner or later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gunmach</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gunmach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gunmach/</guid>
      <description>All that needs to be done to successfully complete this game campaign is to destroy as many enemies as possible and give the main character the opportunity to transfer intelligence to the headquarters. Blow up every tank that comes your way to get closer to the checkpoint. To control use the W, S, A and D keys and the left mouse button to shoot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plated Glory</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/plated-glory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/plated-glory/</guid>
      <description>The tank division was surrounded, only your car was lucky to remain unharmed. Drive through the minefield, trying to avoid explosive charges. To do this, you will need to solve a math example and guide the tank along a safe road. Click on the box with the correct answer - and this area will be cleared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Forces Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-forces-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tank-forces-survival/</guid>
      <description>The game Tank Destroyer 2 will give you the opportunity to set a record for the destruction of enemies in a fairly large area. You only have one life. And for it you need to have time to ride behind enemy lines and inflict as much damage as possible on him. To do this, try to destroy enemy tanks and guns. But be prepared for return fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanks Battlefield samename1</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-battlefield-samename1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanks-battlefield-samename1/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to ride a very cool Grizzly tank, which was designed and equipped specifically for complex military operations. You can control the armored vehicle using the arrow keys. Switch weapons - press the space bar. Use the mouse to aim and shoot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanksioonline</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanksioonline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanksioonline/</guid>
      <description>Your mission is to go through 5 levels and get to the temple with treasures that have long been planned to be captured. The entire building is like a labyrinth, with enemies guarding the jewels waiting in every room. Be ready for constant battles, move along the perimeter of the room, shooting at checkpoints to protect the precious metal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanque 3D: Sports</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanque-3d-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/tanque-3d-sports/</guid>
      <description>Today you will control a combat train, which, in addition to being able to ride on rails, also has the ability to fly. He was equipped with combat fire missiles, which he can fire at enemies if he wishes. The essence of the game is to get into the enemy base and defeat it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
