<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ever After High on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/ever-after-high/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ever After High on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/ever-after-high/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ever After High game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ever-after-high-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ever-after-high-game/</guid>
      <description>The game Ever After High tells how the heirs and apostates got into Wonderland. Incredible adventures await you in this strange and magical place. Manage the girl, collect apples, which are found here quite often. Beware of dangerous places, for example, moving blue circles, because traps hide behind them. Also, you can not come into contact with opponents - living cards that patrol the territory of a fairy-tale country. The number of apples that you need to collect and that you already have are displayed at the top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Ever After High Adventure at school</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-ever-after-high-adventure-at-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-ever-after-high-adventure-at-school/</guid>
      <description>Start the process of playing Ever After High rpg at school and go to explore Wonderland with Alice. Your task is to travel around the locations and collect apples there. At each stage, it displays exactly how many apples you need to collect, and this number is worth striving for. Enemies will come across on the way, they must be avoided, otherwise the collision will take away your game life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Ever After High Adventure Spring Festival</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-ever-after-high-adventure-spring-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-ever-after-high-adventure-spring-festival/</guid>
      <description>Kitty Cheshire goes to an amusement park for some great fun. You need to walk along the alleys, collect tickets and other useful items. Each attraction requires payment, so you can get on them only after you collect the required number of tickets. Win gifts!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Test who are you from Ever After High</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-test-who-are-you-from-ever-after-high/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-test-who-are-you-from-ever-after-high/</guid>
      <description>The game Quiz who are you from Ever After High offers to learn a little more about your character. With its help, you can quickly determine which of the cartoon school students you look like. Simply answer ten questions, choosing only one answer from the four offered. The result will be an image of the heroine and her description.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Tests Ever After High</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-tests-ever-after-high/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-tests-ever-after-high/</guid>
      <description>The process of playing Ever After High tests will allow you to find out which of the students of the magical school you are most like. Hurry up and start the passage to discover the secrets of your character! Here it is proposed to answer ten simple questions that relate to your interests, hobbies, some life principles. Each question in the game for girls comes with four possible answers, but only one is required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Walker Cherise Hood through the thicket</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-walker-cherise-hood-through-the-thicket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-walker-cherise-hood-through-the-thicket/</guid>
      <description>Four girlfriends get lost in a scary forest, and Cherise Hood goes looking for clues to figure out how to get out of here. It is necessary to move along the paths, avoiding obstacles and collecting stars. You will also come across various bonus items that give additional abilities for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Festival game</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/spring-festival-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/spring-festival-game/</guid>
      <description>Kitty Cheshire is going to impress her mom. To do this, she wants to demonstrate all her talents during the spring festival by participating in various games and competitions. But first you need to collect as many tickets as possible! At the same time, Kitty should not be noticed by other girls.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
