<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simulators for girls on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/simulators-for-girls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Simulators for girls on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/simulators-for-girls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Baby Hazel Royal Bath</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-hazel-royal-bath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/baby-hazel-royal-bath/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting game you have to take care of a small child who needs constant attention. Take a bath using all the objects presented on the screen. Get water in the bath, add foam and my baby there. After that, dry it with a fluffy towel and tell a story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbie Dreamtopia: Wispy Forest Spot the Difference</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/barbie-dreamtopia-wispy-forest-spot-the-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/barbie-dreamtopia-wispy-forest-spot-the-difference/</guid>
      <description>The girl decided to go on an African safari, and you need to help her choose a suit. It should be cute and comfortable. First, choose the details of the outfit, their color and ornament. Next, you will need to do pattern and sewing. The final stage is the choice of suitable accessories, shoes, hairstyles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Day Spa Care</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/beach-day-spa-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/beach-day-spa-care/</guid>
      <description>Work on the image of a cute girl, making her a real beauty. Your task is to carry out various cosmetic procedures with the face and hair. Then choose the shape of the curls, and the final step will be working on a fashionable outfit and accessories. Try to make sure that all the details of the image are harmoniously combined with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BFF Princess Vote For FIFA 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bff-princess-vote-for-fifa-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bff-princess-vote-for-fifa-2018/</guid>
      <description>The heroine of the game decided to go in for sports, and you are invited to choose a cool outfit for her. To begin with, decide on the components of the future tracksuit, choosing not only the style, but also the color and ornament. You will also need to add a hairstyle, shoes, dumbbells and other accessories. The finished image can be saved or printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blonde Princess Hospital Recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/blonde-princess-hospital-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/blonde-princess-hospital-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Princess Rapunzel is used to looking attractive in any situation. Now you have to take care of the appearance of a cute girl. To begin with, put in order her hair and do her hair. Next, move on to applying makeup and choosing a chic dress. The finished image can be saved or printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonnie Gucci And Prada</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-gucci-and-prada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bonnie-gucci-and-prada/</guid>
      <description>Even at work, girls want to look attractive. Your task is to sew a new outfit for the heroine of the game. To begin with, you will need to select the details of future clothing, indicating their color and adding, if desired, patterns. After cutting and sewing, all that remains is to choose a hairstyle and accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellie Get Ready With Me 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-get-ready-with-me-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ellie-get-ready-with-me-2/</guid>
      <description>The girl is going to a party, and you need to help her with this. First, go with the heroine of the game to a beauty salon to carry out various useful procedures and get rid of some troubles with the skin of the face. Then you will need to take care of makeup and outfit in which the girl will outshine everyone at the party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elsa Vs Ariel Fashion Competition</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-vs-ariel-fashion-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-vs-ariel-fashion-competition/</guid>
      <description>In this business simulation game for girls you have to work in a store that sells winter outfits. Customers who want to buy cute things constantly come here. You need to listen to the customers and offer them what they want. At each level, you need to earn a specified amount of money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Show</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mermaid-show/</guid>
      <description>Even underwater inhabitants follow fashion and want to be real beauties. Your task is to come up with a new cute look for the little mermaid. Decide on the appearance of the bodice and tail, choose a color and ornament for them. The final step will be the choice of hairstyles, jewelry and mermaid drawings on the face and body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Spa World</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-spa-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-spa-world/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will meet a cute girl who decided to take care of her face and skin a little. Your task is to help the beauty by using various cosmetics. Treat the girl&amp;rsquo;s face and body, and then move on to applying makeup. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to choose an outfit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
