<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dino on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/dino/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dino on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/dino/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dino Meat Hunt Dry Land</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-meat-hunt-dry-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-meat-hunt-dry-land/</guid>
      <description>In this game you will see how difficult life was for a little dinosaur in the Stone Age. Under your strict control, he will have to get to the very end point of each level. And on the way there are many obstacles and enemies. But there are also useful items. For example, a hammer that breaks stone blocks (they just melt when you are around).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dino Squad Adventure 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-squad-adventure-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dino-squad-adventure-2/</guid>
      <description>Before you is a game in which the teamwork of two players is required to complete each stage. However, you can play alone, but, as they say, in two hands. The bottom line is that dinosaurs (heroes of the game) must reach the exit to another level and collect all the bonuses along the way. Sometimes other characters will come across to meet them. Jump on top of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Dino Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-dino-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-dino-adventure/</guid>
      <description>The Dino game will be very popular with small users because of the main character. After all, this is the same dinosaur from a box of children&amp;rsquo;s lactic acid dessert. Management, however, can cause difficulty for kids. First, it is carried out using the keyboard. Secondly, it is quite difficult to deal with opponents. By the way, the character in the story went on a campaign. He has to jump over the abyss and deal with enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dino King</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-dino-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/the-dino-king/</guid>
      <description>The Dino World game is designed for younger gamers, but it will also be interesting for those who are older. The main characters here are dinosaur friends. One of them is large, and the second is small, in connection with which he loves to ride on a friend. From time to time they have to overcome obstacles. Where the big man cannot pass, the small lizard will pass and open the way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
