<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Doctor on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/doctor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Doctor on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/doctor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elsa Stomach Virus</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-stomach-virus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/elsa-stomach-virus/</guid>
      <description>Running this game will turn you into a doctor working in a city hospital. Your patient becomes a girl who complains of abdominal pain. All symptoms point to inflamed appendicitis, so you need to prepare for surgery. Carry out the necessary procedures and save the girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Princess Hospital Recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-hospital-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/ice-princess-hospital-recovery/</guid>
      <description>After starting this exciting game, you will turn into a doctor. The patient complains of pain in her arm, and it must be urgently examined, and then appropriate manipulations should be carried out. The head nurse has been working in the hospital for a long time and knows all about new treatment methods, so she will be happy to help you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy Ear Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/judy-ear-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/judy-ear-doctor/</guid>
      <description>The Doctor Strikes Back game will clearly show that not all doctors are kind and nice people. You have to control a character armed with powerful weapons. Destroy all the enemies that come across on the way to clear the path to the goal. As you progress, you will receive reward points and increase the level of experience. The buttons on the keyboard are used to control, press the desired keys to move the doctor and hit the enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/little-dentist/</guid>
      <description>In this game you have to play the role of a doctor who is able to cope with any problems. This time the patient complains about his teeth. He was playing baseball and got hit in the jaw. Your task is to examine the boy and carry out all the necessary procedures that will help the patient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operate Now Shoulder Surgery</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/operate-now-shoulder-surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/operate-now-shoulder-surgery/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will transform into a doctor-surgeon who knows a lot about the most complex operations. You were approached by a guy who injured his shoulder. It is necessary to urgently examine the patient, and then carry out an operation that will help to correct the situation and eliminate damage as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony Rarity Baby Birth</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-rarity-baby-birth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pony-rarity-baby-birth/</guid>
      <description>Pregnant women need special attention, and this time you will have to work with the future mom. The task is to examine the patient, carry out all the necessary procedures for diagnosis and prescribe the correct treatment. For this, the necessary items are already prepared on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Doll Ear Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-doll-ear-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/super-doll-ear-doctor/</guid>
      <description>After starting this game, you will turn into an otolaryngologist doctor. A patient came to you with problems with her ears. It is necessary to cure the girl using a variety of tools. Tips will help in this process. After you grab an item, a diagram of its use will be displayed on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vampire Nose Doctor</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/vampire-nose-doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/vampire-nose-doctor/</guid>
      <description>Girl Alina complains of breathing problems due to deformity in the nasal cavity. You are invited to act as an experienced doctor who can quickly perform the operation. The operating room has already prepared those items that will be useful in the process. It remains only to follow the instructions correctly!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
