<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robots 2 on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/robots-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Robots 2 on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/robots-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bionic Race</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bionic-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bionic-race/</guid>
      <description>While playing Lego Robots 2, you meet Lloyd, the Green Ninja and the nephew of the great master Wu, who go in search of an ancient artifact. Parts of the legendary weapons are scattered throughout the world of Ninjago, and in order to get to them, Lloyd decided to use a super-modern aircraft in the form of a dragon. Destroy the enemies attacking you and collect all parts of the artifact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epic Robot Tournament</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/epic-robot-tournament/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/epic-robot-tournament/</guid>
      <description>Killer Robot 2 will appeal to all, without exception, fans of action games. Try to go from beginning to end all the corridors of the abandoned space station, where you were dropped off for reconnaissance. On your way you will meet a huge number of dangerous enemies, deadly traps and obstacles. Destroying the encountered opponents, you will receive new types of weapons and cash to improve the performance of your combat bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Robots 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/go-robots-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/go-robots-2/</guid>
      <description>The robot-hero and savior of the galaxy unsuccessfully calculated the trajectory of his intergalactic flight, collided with one of the satellites and ended up on an unknown planet. Help a brave space explorer get to a small research base located in the depths of the planet. With the help of a huge alien flower, try to throw the android as close as possible to the rescue station.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
