<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fashion designer on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/fashion-designer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fashion designer on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/fashion-designer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bff Wedding Dress Design</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bff-wedding-dress-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bff-wedding-dress-design/</guid>
      <description>Fashion studio - clothes designer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>College Girls New Dress</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/college-girls-new-dress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/college-girls-new-dress/</guid>
      <description>After successful work in the famous fashion houses of Paris, you were offered to try your hand at another fashion capital - New York. Choose one of the city&amp;rsquo;s famous ateliers and start creating your own clothing collection. The head of the agency will appreciate your efforts and send the models you created to the fashion show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dress Design For Princess</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/dress-design-for-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/dress-design-for-princess/</guid>
      <description>In this game, you will get acquainted with the process of sewing women&amp;rsquo;s clothing, going through all its stages: from creating a pattern to finishing fitting. But not everything is as difficult as it seems. First you need to decide on the style of the outfit and place all its details on the mannequin. Here you can choose the structure and color of the fabric. At the next levels, you will have to do pattern and tailoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lolita Princess Party</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/lolita-princess-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/lolita-princess-party/</guid>
      <description>Despite the fact that the interface and all the tips in the game are in English, it will be very easy to understand what is required of the gamer. The process of passing consists in tailoring the dress chosen at the very beginning. Young designers will be able to get acquainted with the main stages of creating clothes and take a direct part in this matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popstar Sneaker Designer</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/popstar-sneaker-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/popstar-sneaker-designer/</guid>
      <description>Another game that will not only entertain girls, but also help them to show all their creative abilities to the fullest. And, in addition, in the process of passing it will be possible to master the main stages of tailoring dresses. So, from the very beginning, it is possible to model an outfit on a mannequin, and then bring the idea to life using multi-colored fabrics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Bff Floss Dance</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-bff-floss-dance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-bff-floss-dance/</guid>
      <description>A famous sportswear company has invited you to participate in a competition, the winner of which will get the opportunity to try his hand at being a company designer. Participants need to create original costumes for representatives of various sports. Try to make comfortable and stylish sports uniforms that will bring you victory in the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Pool Party Floats</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-pool-party-floats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-pool-party-floats/</guid>
      <description>This game is completely Russified, which will allow you to read hints (of course, for those users who know how to do this). The process of passing is quite complicated. Users will have to sew the dress according to the pattern. At the first stage, you need to compile it from ready-made fragments. Then you will need to choose a fabric, cut and so on. The game gives visual clues in the form of arrows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess Urban Outfitters Autumn</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-urban-outfitters-autumn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/princess-urban-outfitters-autumn/</guid>
      <description>Charming Taylor has a terribly busy schedule today. She&amp;rsquo;s going to go shopping, help her mom garden, go to a party, and do a thousand other things. For each of them, she needs a suitable outfit. Help the heroine create it using the possibilities available in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapunzel Wedding Dress Designer 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rapunzel-wedding-dress-designer-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rapunzel-wedding-dress-designer-2/</guid>
      <description>From the name it is clear that young gamers will have to work on the appearance of the princess, but not the usual one, but the oriental one. Therefore, her outfit will be appropriate. First you need to try on the individual parts of the costume on a mannequin. The next step is fabric selection, cutting and sewing. At the end of the game, do not forget about the hairstyle, and then print the finished picture or save it in the computer&amp;rsquo;s memory.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
