<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3d games on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/3d-games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3d games on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/3d-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alpine Ski Master</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/alpine-ski-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/alpine-ski-master/</guid>
      <description>First of all, fans of football battles will like to play the Champions 3D game. Here you can help your favorite team to break into the Champions League of this sport. Use the arrow keys to control the players on the field, pass the ball, defend your goal and score goals as you strive to win the next match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backwater Fishing</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/backwater-fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/backwater-fishing/</guid>
      <description>According to the terms of the Fishing 3D game, you will be asked to choose one of the locations for fishing. Further, everything is simple. Click the left mouse button and the fishing rod will be cast where the cursor is pointing. Wait until a fish appears on the hook, and hook. When pulling out prey, do not forget to control the tension of the fishing line using a special indicator in order to prevent a break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Batman Shadow Combat</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/batman-shadow-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/batman-shadow-combat/</guid>
      <description>While playing Batman 3D, you are faced with the task of modifying a giant bot - one of the best inventions of the Dark Knight. This monster is designed to protect Gotham City from bandits and robbers. After finishing work, feel free to click on the map, choose the difficulty level and start patrolling the streets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cat-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cat-run/</guid>
      <description>The game Cat Simulator 3D will allow you to control a virtual pet. What does a cat do when left at home alone? Hooligan. Your task is to score the maximum number of points (100.000) for the things dropped on the floor in 2 minutes. Climb onto the shelves, table, bed and throw off everything that comes under the soft cat paws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Delivery Parking</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/christmas-delivery-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/christmas-delivery-parking/</guid>
      <description>Rules of the Truck Parking 3D game invite everyone who dreams of becoming a professional driver to play. You have to go through several stages of training, where you need to demonstrate all your abilities and correctly park a huge truck. Try to do it as fast as possible during the game about 3d parking around the city, because the time to complete the task is limited. If you fail to park the car on time, the game will have to be played again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downhill Ski</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/downhill-ski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/downhill-ski/</guid>
      <description>While playing Sports 3d you will have to apply your football skills to prove your title of a football star and win this dynamic duel. Choose one of the six teams that you will play as part of and enter the field. Intercept the ball from the opponent, and then try to break through to the goal or pass the ball to another player on your team to complete the attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Surprise</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/easter-surprise/</guid>
      <description>While playing Hidden Objects 3D you will feel like a real detective. Each person experiences sincere joy when he finds a lost thing, and it doesn’t matter if it is his own or someone else’s. Now, to experience this feeling, it is enough to sit down at the computer and find the items in the abandoned house that are indicated at the bottom of the playing field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endless Helix Jumper</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/endless-helix-jumper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/endless-helix-jumper/</guid>
      <description>4d</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Adventure 3d in the city</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-adventure-3d-in-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-adventure-3d-in-the-city/</guid>
      <description>During the 3d city walker game, you have a unique opportunity to demonstrate your military skills and have several fights on the streets of one of the districts of a huge metropolis. Compete with several players online. In two minutes of combat, try to destroy your opponents as many times as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Charlotte Strawberry Run 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-charlotte-strawberry-run-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-charlotte-strawberry-run-3d/</guid>
      <description>According to the game Charlotte Strawberry Run 3D, you need to help the heroine overcome a certain distance. As you know, Charlotte is very fond of sports and everything connected with it. But today she needs your support. After all, you need to collect all the bonuses on the way and avoid collision with all sorts of obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Fitness and Ferb 3d</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-fitness-and-ferb-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-fitness-and-ferb-3d/</guid>
      <description>The essence of the game Fitness and Ferb 3d is that one insidious genius decided to attack the galaxy. For a long time he worked on an invention that could destroy the entire world in a few seconds. Your task is to help the heroes save the planet from an armed invasion. Develop a strategy, think over a plan - all this will not be superfluous and will allow one step closer to victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Iron Man 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-iron-man-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-iron-man-3d/</guid>
      <description>Under the terms of the Iron Man 3d game, you have to control a universal machine designed to destroy even the most dangerous enemies. Flying over the territory of the enemy, shoot from all available types of weapons and reduce the ground and air equipment of the invaders to ashes. At the end of each mission, you have the opportunity to improve your combat performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Racing 3d driving simulator 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-racing-3d-driving-simulator-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-racing-3d-driving-simulator-2/</guid>
      <description>While playing Racing 3D Driving Simulator 2, you have the opportunity to drive through the streets of a huge metropolis in an ultra-modern sports car. Try to accelerate the iron monster to maximum speed without getting into an accident. It is especially pleasant to play the 2nd part of the 3D driving simulator, because you have to drive one of the best models of the famous Italian automobile manufacturer Ferrari.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mineworld</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/mineworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/mineworld/</guid>
      <description>While playing a 3D adventure game, you meet the famous ape man Tarzan and his girlfriend Jane. A couple in love was resting in their hut when they were suddenly attacked by a pack of wild gorillas. Huge animals smashed the cozy house and stole the girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Apocalypse Infection Bio</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-apocalypse-infection-bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-apocalypse-infection-bio/</guid>
      <description>Zd</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racing Thunder</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/racing-thunder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/racing-thunder/</guid>
      <description>The conditions of the game Racing on the track 3d are quite difficult. You have to drive a powerful jeep with huge wheels. Only on such a machine is it possible to pass the entire route without problems. On one condition - if your opponents allow you. To win, you must overtake all opponents and be the first to reach the finish line after a certain number of laps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Taz Driving</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-taz-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/russian-taz-driving/</guid>
      <description>The authors of the game 3D car simulator offer you a ride on one of the best models of the famous Italian automobile concern Ferrari. Accelerate your red stallion to maximum speed on the wide avenues of the largest metropolis in the world. Unique graphics and realistic sound will give you the opportunity to enjoy the control of this beautiful car to the maximum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skater Girl</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/skater-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/skater-girl/</guid>
      <description>While playing Skateboard 3D, you become a participant in a competition among athletes who are fond of riding a skateboard. Skateboarding appeared in the 30s of the last century in California. The first athletes to get on the board were professional surfers. A few years later, fans of this extreme sport began to hold competitions, which attracted athletes from all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slenderman Must Die Silent Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-must-die-silent-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-must-die-silent-forest/</guid>
      <description>This time the events of the game Slender man 3d are developing in a dense winter forest. You have to survive in difficult conditions, hiding from Slender behind the walls of dilapidated houses and under the branches of huge trees. In order to destroy the ghost, you need to collect all the magic spheres. Overcome your fear and put an end to the adventures of this monster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway Princess Run</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/subway-princess-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/subway-princess-run/</guid>
      <description>According to the terms of the Anime 3D game, your task is to collect the Rubik&amp;rsquo;s Cube, on which the characters of the cartoon about Naruto are drawn. The computer will shuffle the cube into several positions especially for you. At first it will be a couple of moves, then more and more. Your task is to collect the cube completely, keeping within the time allotted for each level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Train Simulator 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/train-simulator-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/train-simulator-2019/</guid>
      <description>The train driver during the game 3d subway simulator is responsible for the life and safety of passengers. Open and close doors using the Q and E keys, and get underway without exceeding the speed limit. Park the train correctly so that it is convenient for people to enter or leave the cars. You earn points for the number of passengers you carry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
