<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>War on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/war/</link>
    <description>Recent content in War on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/war/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bullet Fire 2</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/bullet-fire-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/bullet-fire-2/</guid>
      <description>Territory War is a turn-based strategy game where you have to command the troops of an entire nation. Send detachments of your warriors to capture intermediate points, and then to storm the main fortifications of the enemy. There are many types of weapons at your disposal - you just need to learn how to use them correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cube Arena Zombie Warfare</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/cube-arena-zombie-warfare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/cube-arena-zombie-warfare/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow War is a classic 3D spaceship combat simulator. The plot consists of 34 mandatory missions. Also, if you fulfill certain conditions, you can get access to 7 bonus levels. Radars have detected an alarming number of asteroids approaching Earth&amp;rsquo;s orbit. You are tasked with destroying the cluster before the boulders enter the airspace of the planet. It will be a real war against a huge number of cosmic bodies of different sizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert Force</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/desert-force/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/desert-force/</guid>
      <description>According to the rules of the War Shooters game, you have to control a universal soldier whose goal is to free the hostages. On the way there will be many obstacles and a huge number of enemy forces, including helicopters and artillery. But war is a brutal confrontation, and the success of the operation largely depends on an unlimited number of rounds and a powerful grenade launcher. You can use this superweapon whenever massive enemy forces in the form of tanks or defensive structures block the path in the shooting game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gotia.io</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/gotia.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/gotia.io/</guid>
      <description>According to the rules of the game for two Colorful war, you will have to fight with attacking multi-colored squares. You can play alone or together with a friend. The task is to destroy all enemies, collecting bonuses during the battle, allowing you to open a new type of weapon. The color of the future world depends entirely on you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Warrior Globin Rush</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/legendary-warrior-globin-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/legendary-warrior-globin-rush/</guid>
      <description>Game Goblins war of clans tells about the great confrontation between individual families in the country of the ancient Vikings. As the leader of one of them, you will have to think over a strategy to protect your possessions. Create your own army and earn experience to gain skills and magical powers to repel enemy attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martian Zombie Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/martian-zombie-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/martian-zombie-survival/</guid>
      <description>The Dreams of War game is an exciting aerial shooter from World War II. You have to become a fighter pilot and follow the orders of the command. Playing online, you can choose a plane, equip it with machine guns, missiles or bombs, and go on a mission. Use the mouse cursor to control and attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masked Shooters Multiplayer Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/masked-shooters-multiplayer-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/masked-shooters-multiplayer-edition/</guid>
      <description>During the game about the American Civil War, you have to become an artilleryman of one of the fighting sides. Together with a partner, destroy the advancing enemy units by pouring cannonballs on them. Control your weapon with the arrow keys and try not to let the enemy close to your fortifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Gun Apocalypse 5</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-gun-apocalypse-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-gun-apocalypse-5/</guid>
      <description>The game Infinity War 2 tells about the confrontation of the ancient dynasties. You have to choose one of the commanders and try to expand your own land. Starting from a small province, gradually capture one surrounding settlement after another, creating a new, rich and powerful country. The main task of each battle is to destroy the enemy leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Toonfare 3D</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-toonfare-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-toonfare-3d/</guid>
      <description>The game Infinity War 7 will take you to the battlefield where you need to destroy all enemy forces with minimal damage to yourself. But for starters, it does not hurt to collect the maximum number of lives and stock up on ammunition. For intermediate victories in the endless war, you will receive promotions and unlock new opportunities for your character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Warfare 5</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-warfare-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-warfare-5/</guid>
      <description>War 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Wars Of Hero</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-wars-of-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixel-wars-of-hero/</guid>
      <description>The game Infinity War 5 will give you the opportunity to control a war elephant. In the Middle Ages, more powerful weapons did not exist. With the help of this animal, you can crush any kind of enemy troops. Archers, sitting on a special platform on the back of an elephant, release clouds of arrows. Your job is to give them a target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixelar Vehicle Wars</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixelar-vehicle-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/pixelar-vehicle-wars/</guid>
      <description>War &amp;amp; Peace 2 is a fast-paced shooter set in the distant future. You have to defend your base, sitting in a trench and repelling numerous enemy attacks. It&amp;rsquo;s good that you have an ultra-modern plasma rifle at your disposal. It is also possible to improve weapons, upgrade armor and upgrade skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebel Forces</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/rebel-forces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/rebel-forces/</guid>
      <description>The game war 1941-1945 invites you to take part in a dangerous special operation behind enemy lines. Together with a professional saboteur, you are thrown over the front line by plane, your main task is to prepare a bridgehead for the offensive of army units. By controlling the movements of the hero of the game about the war with the Germans, try to destroy the maximum number of enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slenderman Must Die: Industrial Waste</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-must-die-industrial-waste/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/slenderman-must-die-industrial-waste/</guid>
      <description>The exciting and interesting game Nuclear War will not leave indifferent fans of air battles. Help the Russian soldiers defend the bunker containing the nuclear missile. Enemy planes will try to wipe this deadly object from the face of the earth by attacking it time after time. But in the course of a game about nuclear war, you can use your own anti-aircraft gun to shoot them down without giving them an opportunity to strike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sniper Strike</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/sniper-strike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/sniper-strike/</guid>
      <description>War in Iraq 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storm City Mafia</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/storm-city-mafia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/storm-city-mafia/</guid>
      <description>The Fog of War game immerses you in the bright, tropical world of the wild planet Gloria-6, in the shady forests of which colonists from Earth, cut off from their home, are trying to win back their right to life. For completing missions in the game, experience points are awarded for the hero. Upgrade your character, build buildings that extract resources and develop your army.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valiant Knight</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/valiant-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/valiant-knight/</guid>
      <description>Those who are going to play the Wars of Thrones online should know that the toy for the film of the same name has a very mediocre relationship. But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean she&amp;rsquo;s bad. On the contrary, before you is an excellent example of a logical turn-based strategy, not much inferior to chess. The game of the War of Thrones takes place in the constant battles of your chosen character and various mythical monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World War Pilot</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/world-war-pilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/world-war-pilot/</guid>
      <description>The Fighter War game is an excellent simulator for managing a modern combat vehicle. Rather, sit at the helm of the aircraft and complete a series of training tasks. Only after that the command will entrust you with the first independent mission. Fly to the indicated square, find the target and destroy it with the fire of your cannons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xtreme Demolition Arena Derby</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/xtreme-demolition-arena-derby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/xtreme-demolition-arena-derby/</guid>
      <description>The action of the game Road Wars takes place on a specially prepared training ground. At your disposal is a huge jeep equipped with weapons with terrible destructive power. On it you have to fight your opponents and be the first to reach the finish line. Use arrow keys to control. Button Z - jump, X - attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Arena 3D Survival Offline</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-arena-3d-survival-offline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-arena-3d-survival-offline/</guid>
      <description>The Lego military base game is an exciting strategy game in which you have to take command of the galactic fleet and win back as many planets from the enemy as possible. Under the terms of the game War Lego, you will also have to repel enemy attacks, think over an offensive strategy and win many battles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Mission 3</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-mission-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/zombie-mission-3/</guid>
      <description>The Zombie War game will take you to a limited location where you have to protect important objects from the attack of the dead. Two fighters are walking along with you, who immediately take up positions and prepare for defense. Having beaten off the first wave of attackers, you need to check the availability of ammunition from the soldiers, their health and protection. If necessary, you can replenish ammunition in the store.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
