<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>small pet shop on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/small-pet-shop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in small pet shop on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/small-pet-shop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Little Pet Shop - Talent Contest</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-little-pet-shop---talent-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-little-pet-shop---talent-contest/</guid>
      <description>During this game you have to take part in a fascinating performance with the participation of animals. It is necessary to show different tricks and accumulate reward points. For example, you will be asked to hit the ball or fly through moving hoops. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect decorations to get more points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Little Pet Shop Little Pet Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-little-pet-shop-little-pet-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-little-pet-shop-little-pet-shop/</guid>
      <description>Game process Little pet shop Little Pet Shop is dedicated to the exciting search for animals. It consists of several levels, and on each you will see a new location. The task is to look for all the hidden animals. They can end up in a variety of places. Animals sometimes show up from their hiding places, and thanks to this, therefore, you will be able to understand exactly where you need to move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game My little pet shop - hide and seek</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-my-little-pet-shop---hide-and-seek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/game-my-little-pet-shop---hide-and-seek/</guid>
      <description>Find all the little animals that decided to play hide and seek with you! The task is to carefully follow what is happening on the screen. If an animal appears somewhere, quickly click on it. At each level, the number of pets to find increases. Time to pass is limited.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
