<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Checkers for two on Game6r</title>
    <link>https://www.game6r.com/tags/checkers-for-two/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Checkers for two on Game6r</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.game6r.com/tags/checkers-for-two/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Checkers</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/checkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/checkers/</guid>
      <description>The process of playing Checkers for two black and white will appeal to fans of intellectual pursuits. First, decide whether you will play with a virtual opponent or with a real one. Also indicate the level of difficulty. Then you can safely proceed to the gameplay by moving the checkers on the black cells of the board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checkers Classic</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/checkers-classic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/checkers-classic/</guid>
      <description>Many people love to play checkers. If you are one of the fans of this intellectual fun, then it&amp;rsquo;s time to start the game. You will need a friend in it, you cannot play against the computer. A board with red and white checkers placed on it will be displayed on the screen. Choose your color and start the battle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checkers Mania</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/checkers-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/checkers-mania/</guid>
      <description>Do you like to play checkers? Then you will definitely like this virtual version. The goal is to remove all the opponent&amp;rsquo;s checkers from the board. Move yours one square diagonally, trying not to expose the enemy. Moves are made sequentially. If the checker reaches the opposite edge of the board, it becomes a king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Checkers</title>
      <link>https://www.game6r.com/games/master-checkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.game6r.com/games/master-checkers/</guid>
      <description>Checkers is a game loved by many. She has simple rules. Now you can play checkers with a virtual opponent or with a real one. Choose the desired mode of passage, and also indicate the level of difficulty. Next, a board divided into cells will be displayed on the screen. Move checkers and win!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
